<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title><![CDATA[LessWrong]]></title><description><![CDATA[A community blog devoted to refining the art of rationality]]></description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com<image/><url> https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/v1497915096/favicon_lncumn.ico</url><title>少错</title><link/>https://www.lesswrong.com<generator>节点的 RSS</generator><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 10 月 11 日星期三 04:13:59 GMT </lastbuilddate><atom:link href="https://www.lesswrong.com/feed.xml?view=rss&amp;karmaThreshold=2" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><item><title><![CDATA[An explanation for every token: using an LLM to sample another LLM]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 11, 2023 12:53 AM GMT<br/><br/><h1>介绍</h1><p>关于基于一种或多种大型语言模型 (LLM) 构建 AGI 的<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/dcoxvEhAfYcov2LA6/agentized-llms-will-change-the-alignment-landscape">影响</a>和<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/FRRb6Gqem8k69ocbi/externalized-reasoning-oversight-a-research-direction-for">潜在</a><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Q7XWGqL4HjjRmhEyG/internal-independent-review-for-language-model-agent)">安全优势</a>，已有很多文章。支持者认为，由于法学硕士以人类可读的自然语言为基础，因此与其他可能的方法（例如<a href="https://www.deepmind.com/blog/muzero-mastering-go-chess-shogi-and-atari-without-rules">MuZero 风格</a>的基于模型的强化学习和规划）相比，它们更容易理解、控制和安全扩展。</p><p>例如，<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2201.11903">在适当的提示下</a>，法学硕士可以输出具有解释结构的文本，后跟答案或结论。此类方法已被证明可以提高最终答案的准确性。它们还为法学硕士输出的使用者提供了（明显）理解法学硕士推理过程的能力，这可以增强相对于简单答案的信任和信心。</p><p>这种方法的一个问题是法学硕士的自然语言输出不一定是生成它们的底层机制的<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/6eKL9wDqeiELbKPDj/unfaithful-explanations-in-chain-of-thought-prompting">忠实表示</a>。也就是说，法学硕士的答案可能根本不依赖于前面的“解释”或所谓的推理过程。</p><p>不忠实的解释实际上是语言模型中一个更普遍的问题的一个例子：在一个长的标记序列中，序列中后面的标记通常不会像我们希望的那样受到前面的标记的约束。此外，后面的标记并不总是以自然或预期的方式依赖于较早的标记，特别是，不以语言模型输出本身声明的方式依赖于较早的输出。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefzur2ccnqhe"><sup><a href="#fnzur2ccnqhe">[1]</a></sup></span></p><p>部分或全部这些表面问题可以通过扩展模型和改进模型训练过程来克服，但其根本原因可能<a href="https://twitter.com/ylecun/status/1640122342570336267">是所有法学硕士当前使用的方式所固有的</a>：自回归采样。采样过程是基于法学硕士的人工智能系统的关键部分，我认为目前在某种程度上被忽视了，因为它是实施强大安全和控制机制的有用场所。</p><p>在这篇文章中，<strong>我提出了一种对法学硕士进行抽样的新方法，将抽样过程委托给第二个法学硕士，并要求其解释每个选择。</strong>结果是，最终输出中的每个标记都附有人类可读的带外解释，说明为什么选择该标记，因此，与传统的思想链提示和其他带内语言模型输出。我构建了一个<a href="https://explained-completions.netlify.app/">演示</a>，通过几个示例来可视化我的方法： <br></p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/jiqhchcght0j3xnv7qzw" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/ixjpp0hq4mjm7h070cev 120w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/h41xvfv1ar6lpmgbclbi 240w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/b6yhofygdijd4ckuzprs 360w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/zaffnk6p3ra0jdoexapc 480w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/orzz3vlgokzomxbbh3r6 600w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/utgmhsufkzsyzpierpgg 720w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/mdtuy0jhit4ld0dhs7pg 840w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/pd3p5supc8toe0dsqc06 960w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/h8y6bebsd6mvijlvd84c 1080w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/zzzcsjscyceod0mioazr 1161w"><figcaption>基于 LLM 的抽样示例。图中提示来自<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2210.09261">BBH</a> 。</figcaption></figure><p>下面，我将简要介绍现有的法学硕士抽样方法的背景，描述我提出的抽样方法和一些实验结果，将我的方法与一些相关工作进行对比，并就为什么这种通用方法可能对建立法学硕士有用进行一些评论。基于模型的系统在与传统采样方法一起使用时是不安全的。</p><h1>背景：法学硕士抽样</h1><p>对于给定的输入提示，LLM 在令牌空间中所有可能令牌的集合上输出下一个令牌的概率分布。这些概率通常表示为 logits，对于强大的法学硕士来说，绝大多数概率质量通常集中在少数最佳选择中： <br></p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/mkfvd9mpmfwfj2sndao3" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/lf95x9dpgaidkj3zz1xy 89w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/f8kksuxd31umh0iwzrlr 169w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/j6xwtanftnfl6fodsa7a 249w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/zfxv63bikbzs0mt9jfec 329w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/n0grpxb0uhqhofyayil9 409w"><figcaption> OpenAI 的 text-davinci-003 的输出。</figcaption></figure><p>下一个令牌的概率分布是<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/GkC6YTu4DWp2zwf9k/giant-in-scrutable-matrices-maybe-the-best-of-all-possible">巨大的难以理解的矩阵</a>的唯一输出；由程序员决定如何使用此概率分布来生成扩展的输出序列。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnref1ns2683r11a"><sup><a href="#fn1ns2683r11a">[2]</a></sup></span>标准方法是以某种方式从概率分布中进行采样，将采样的标记附加到初始提示中，然后通过模型自动回归运行更新的提示。<br><br>选择的采样方法会对最终输出的质量和风格产生很大影响。例如，您可以设置一个温度参数，使分布或多或少地偏向高似然标记，而不是直接从 LLM 输出的概率分布中进行采样。一种特殊情况是将温度设置为 0，这将导致采样过程每次都确定性地选取可能性最高的标记（贪婪采样）。其他方法包括波束搜索或<a href="https://wandb.ai/darek/llmapps/reports/A-Gentle-Introduction-to-LLM-APIs--Vmlldzo0NjM0MTMz#what-is-sampling?">top-p（核采样）</a> 。您还可以引入<a href="https://platform.openai.com/docs/guides/gpt/parameter-details">频率和存在惩罚</a>，或者实施更复杂的规则来精确控制系统的最终输出。例如，要将输出限制为有效的 JSON，您可以在采样器中合并 JSON 解析器，仅选择生成有效 JSON 的标记。</p><h1>我的方法</h1><p>我提出了一种对 LLM 进行采样的新方法，此后称为基础 LLM， <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefoxmh6kjd2ma"><sup><a href="#fnoxmh6kjd2ma">[3]</a></sup></span> ，将采样和令牌选择过程委托给第二个 LLM（此后，<i> </i>采样器法学硕士）。例如，假设我们想为以下提示生成补全：</p><pre> <code>You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant:</code></pre><p>我们将此提示传递给基础 LLM，并获得下一个标记的概率分布（实际上，我们使用<code>max_tokens=1</code>和<code>logprobs=5</code>调用 OpenAI API）。我们选取分布中最有可能的 5 个标记，并使用它们为采样器 LLM 构建提示：</p><pre> <code>You are an LLM tasked with choosing a token from possibilities generated by another LLM. The prompt passed to the other LLM: &quot;&quot;&quot; You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant: &quot;&quot;&quot; The most likely next tokens from the other LLM: 0. Token: &#39;\n&#39; Probability: 0.016% Completed prompt: &quot;&quot;&quot; You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant: &quot;&quot;&quot; 1. Token: &#39; &#39; Probability: 0.03% Completed prompt: &quot;&quot;&quot; You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant: &quot;&quot;&quot; 2. Token: &#39;The&#39; Probability: 0.127% Completed prompt: &quot;&quot;&quot; You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant:The &quot;&quot;&quot; 3. Token: &#39; Paris&#39; Probability: 0.443% Completed prompt: &quot;&quot;&quot; You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant: Paris &quot;&quot;&quot; 4. Token: &#39; The&#39; Probability: 99.373% Completed prompt: &quot;&quot;&quot; You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant: The &quot;&quot;&quot; Analyze the selections of the other LLM and select the index you think is most appropriate by calling the choose_token function after explaining your reasoning.</code></pre><p>然后，我们使用普通方法（基于温度的采样）生成采样器 LLM 的响应，并使用 OpenAI 的<a href="https://openai.com/blog/function-calling-and-other-api-updates">函数调用功能</a>来简化解析采样器 LLM 选择的过程。继续该示例，给出上面的提示，gpt-4 返回以下内容：</p><pre> <code>The other LLM seems to be considering starting the response with &quot;The&quot; (option 4) or &quot; Paris&quot; (option 3). The other options are less likely and don&#39;t seem to lead to a coherent response. Option 4, &quot; The&quot;, is the most probable according to the other LLM, but it doesn&#39;t make sense in this context. The assistant wouldn&#39;t start the response with &quot;The&quot; when answering a question about the capital of a country. Option 3, &quot; Paris&quot;, is the correct answer to the question and it makes sense for the assistant to start the response with the name of the capital. Therefore, I&#39;ll choose option 3, &quot; Paris&quot;. function args: {&#39;token_index&#39;: 3}</code></pre><p>采样器 LLM 选择了选项 3，因此我们将其附加到初始提示中并重新开始该过程，使用以下提示提示基础 LLM 生成下一个标记的新概率分布：</p><pre> <code>You are a helpful assistant. User: What is the capital of France? Assistant: Paris</code></pre><p>该过程继续进行，直到基础 LLM 输出<code>&lt;|endoftext|>;</code>作为可能的下一个标记之一，并且采样器 LLM 选择它。<br><br>结果是最终输出中的每个标记都附有为何选择该标记的解释。 </p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/vrnqq3vutlrc4dtpum5i" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/e2ahyvpnarbld3wf6wbl 120w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/akonyysv0n8umwdodqpp 240w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/daqg4mj18kb9ixvo7qhl 360w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/jbo7dey0ost58om0e6ig 480w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/qxmdclguuiunhtrjynst 600w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/rddvxakfwzd77iye4qwt 720w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/ybyedi5nwrg5honrc30p 840w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/hdujsyfuvfbktxynfshq 960w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/irkzprdbga3zugfzluo8 1080w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/zxh26k2ysnzacvm0tzwx 1173w"><figcaption>上面示例的可视化，可<a href="https://explained-completions.netlify.app/">在此处</a>获取。</figcaption></figure><h1>细节和实验设置</h1><p>我使用 text-davinci-003 作为基础 LLM，使用 gpt-4 作为采样器 LLM，实现了上面提出的采样过程。在更现实的设置中，基础法学硕士可能会更强大，也许是一种前沿模型，当直接在更多样化的设置中使用时，其输出并不完全可信。或者，可以对基础和采样器使用相同的底层模型，以比较我的采样方法和经典采样方法应用于单个模型时的性能特征和行为属性。<br><br>然而，实际上，gpt-4 是我可以访问的唯一模型，它有足够的能力理解指令并可靠地执行选择任务，甚至 gpt-4 也不是很擅长。在撰写本文时，text-davinci-003 是最强大的模型，我可以直接访问它的任何 logits。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnref6a1ngkdirv2"><sup><a href="#fn6a1ngkdirv2">[4]</a></sup></span></p><p>另一个限制是采样器 LLM 仅提供基础 LLM 中的前 5 个 logits。这没有什么原则性的理由； 5 只是通过 OpenAI 的 API 提供的 logits 数量的限制。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefjt3p4kqufch"><sup><a href="#fnjt3p4kqufch">[5]</a></sup></span><br><br>我的实现的最终版本还包含一些附加功能，这些功能对于采样方法本身来说并不重要，但使其更加实用：</p><ul><li><strong>提前停止</strong>：我们可以在采样器 LLM 的提示中添加指令，允许它指定自己的“停止”标记，如果采样器看起来到目前为止已经完全偏离轨道，则可以选择该标记。通过选择停止令牌而不是基础 LLM 中的选项之一，它可以在基础 LLM 选择停止令牌本身或系统遇到用户定义的令牌限制之前选择中止采样过程并提前停止完成。</li><li><strong>替代令牌选择</strong>：如果采样器 LLM 认为基础 LLM 的前五个选择<i>都</i>不合适，则采样器 LLM 可以选择自己选择的替代令牌。在我的实现中，这个令牌不会立即被接受；相反，它以高概率（任意，75％）作为选项附加到前 5 个选择，并且采样器 LLM 的新实例与新选项一起呈现。这使采样器能够在上下文中检查自己的选择。这在示例中用 ⟲ 标记表示。<br><br> （这个扩展在我的实验中效果不是特别好；采样器 LLM 经常会感到困惑，使完成变得一团糟，或者选择一个作为基本 LLM 选择之一的超字符串的标记。这可能是因为采样器 LLM对于“令牌”是什么没有实际的精确概念。）</li></ul><p>完整的系统提示请参见附录。</p><h2>例子</h2><p>此处提供：https: <a href="https://explained-completions.netlify.app/">//explained-completions.netlify.app/</a></p><p>演示和示例的目的主要是为了说明概念并激发下面的讨论；它们并不是所提出方法的严格性能表征。</p><ul><li> <strong>Capital of France</strong> 、 <strong>Pronoun Explanation</strong>和<strong>Chess</strong>显示了一些没有替代标记选择或早期停止功能的基本示例。 （国际象棋示例取自<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/F6vH6fr8ngo7csDdf/chess-as-a-case-study-in-hidden-capabilities-in-chatgpt">此处</a>；代词提示取自<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2210.09261">BBH</a> 。）</li><li> <strong>Fibonacci Python 代码</strong>示例展示了早期停止和替代令牌选择功能的一些（错误）使用。请注意，失败示例显示了采样器 LLM 搞乱了基础 LLM 的示例；通过建议替代令牌而不是选择基础 LLM 的“返回”选项，在最后一行引入了不可恢复的错误。</li><li> <strong>tic-tac-toe</strong>显示了替代令牌选择功能正常工作的示例；就其本身而言，text-davinci-003 无法捕获游戏状态中的无效性。</li></ul><h2>结果</h2><p>应用于当前模型时，所提出的采样方法很脆弱，并且在最终输出的质量方面通常会导致比使用传统采样方法的任何一个模型本身的性能<i>更差</i>。此外，相对于传统采样方法，为每个标记生成解释会导致速度降低 100-1000 倍，成本增加。<br><br>然而，采样方法<i>似乎</i>确实确保了最终输出中的每个标记都附有关于为什么选择标记的忠实且因果的解释。在我的测试中，采样器 LLM 不会做出与其推理无关的选择，即采样器永远不会输出类似“选择 1 没有意义，选择 2 可以，但会导致过于冗长的选择，选择 3 最有意义”作为解释，然后实际上在函数调用中它执行了除选择选项 3 之外的其他操作。</p><p> gpt-4 生成的解释通常推理不充分，并且生成的令牌选择也不是特别好，但我假设它们是<i>值得信赖的，</i>因为仅凭这些解释就足以可靠（且简单地）推断出哪些令牌实际出现在最终输出。这与传统 CoT 提示中的解释和我在脚注 1 中给出的示例形成鲜明对比，其中带内“解释”有时与最终答案无关。这是一个关键属性，如果它足够强大，我推测它可以使采样方法对于安全地利用强大但不受信任的模型有用。有关原因的更多详细信息，请参阅“作为安全机制的潜在用途”。</p><h1>讨论</h1><h2>作为安全机制的潜在用途</h2><p>尽管所提出的采样方法在应用于当前模型时并不是特别有用，但我推测当应用于更强大的模型时它可能会很有用。因为最终输出中的每个标记直接且自然地依赖于自然语言解释，所以输出可能比简单地由不受信任的基本模型生成而没有任何解释更值得信赖和可靠。</p><p>为什么这可能是正确的，直觉是，实际上是采样器决定输出，来自基本模型的标记和概率仅充当外生提示，采样器只有在很好地理解提示的情况下才能使用它们足以以人类可读的格式解释它们的含义。但是，由于每个提示的长度仅限于单个标记，因此与让基本模型直接生成更长的输出序列相比，提示提供者（基本模型）可用于操作采样器或以其他方式破坏文本生成过程的带宽有限通过传统的自回归抽样方法。</p><p>我假设，即使是非常强大且具有对抗性的基础模型也无法操纵相对较弱（但更可信）的采样器模型来产生不忠实的令牌选择解释。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefq6pmfz8a2un"><sup><a href="#fnq6pmfz8a2un">[6]</a></sup></span><br><br>此外，与检查传统思维链提示中的带内推理相比，人类或其他法学硕士可能更容易抽查采样器法学硕士的解释。这是因为令牌选择的解释往往是简单且独立的。</p><p>如果这些属性（采样器的不可操作性和对其解释的直接验证）随着系统的能力扩展到人类水平或更高水平而保持不变，那么人们可以利用这种方法通过利用作为采样器的模型较弱但更可信。</p><h2>与其他安全和控制机制组合</h2><p>由于此处提出的机制在采样过程上运行，因此它可以直接与其他方法相结合，用于控制和调整基于 LLM 的系统，包括在推理过程中直接在模型上运行的系统。</p><p>例如，可以在训练期间将 RLHF 应用于采样器模型，以强化给出忠实解释的倾向（可能以牺牲更通用的帮助或推理能力为代价）。该采样器模型可以与基础模型相结合，该基础模型在推理时通过机械可解释性方法进行<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/HWxLQvzJGeXoLPJWd/actadd-steering-language-models-without-optimization">激活工程</a>和检查。结果是一个系统，其中真正的控制点在采样器中清晰且可验证，特别是在它生成的自然语言解释中。<br><br>该方法的另一个观点是，它是<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/tag/iterated-amplification">迭代放大</a>的一小部分（一次迭代），其中性能损失可以被视为陡峭的<a href="https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/topics/alignment-tax">对齐税</a>。</p><h2>未来的工作</h2><p>人们可以对玩具实现进行许多可能的扩展、优化和其他改进，以及可以运行更严格和详细的实验来量化应用于当前模型时采样方法的性能。本文中演示和示例的目的主要是为了说明概念并激发进一步的讨论；当应用于当前模型时，它们并不是该方法的严格表征。<br><br>基于对我的玩具实现的实验，我预计在使用当前可用的 SoTA 模型构建基于 LLM 的 AI 系统时，应用这种采样方法不太可能作为安全措施（或用于功能增强）实用或有用。 （再次强调，gpt-4 在我的实验中给出的解释是<i>忠实的，</i>但它们不一定是高质量或合理的。）</p><p>除了与安全和控制机制组合之外，该方法还可能与各种其他潜在的功能增强工具组合或从中受益：<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.09687">思想图</a>、<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2306.05426">退格标记</a>、<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2310.02226">暂停标记</a>等。我认为引入一个数量级的放缓和显着的输出质量损失可能会使这种方法对那些纯粹或主要对能力工作感兴趣的人失去吸引力，我认为在更强大的想法之前公开讨论这样的想法是有价值的可能应用它们的模型实际上是可用的。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefwsbgd7h1i1j"><sup><a href="#fnwsbgd7h1i1j">[7]</a></sup></span></p><p>最后，尽管我对当前形式的这种特定方法的对齐有效性有些悲观，但对其他危险或不安全的模型进行安排和施加约束的一般方法是我乐观的一类方法。我预计这些方法的<a href="https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/topics/alignment-tax">对齐税</a>会很高，与构建一个同样有效（至少在一段时间内）的未对齐系统相比，成本会增加一个数量级，但如果我们花时间的话，支付起来很简单付钱给他们。</p><h1>相关工作</h1><p><a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2305.20050">过程监督</a>和<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2211.14275">基于过程的反馈</a>是提高基于法学硕士的系统的准确性、推理能力和可解释性的众所周知的方法。与不同抽象和细节层面上基于流程的监督相关的其他术语和出版物包括<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2211.03540">可扩展监督</a>、 <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Q7XWGqL4HjjRmhEyG/internal-independent-review-for-language-model-agent)">内部独立审查</a>和<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/5hApNw5f7uG8RXxGS/the-open-agency-model">开放机构</a>。</p><p>更具体地说，将语言模型推理和输出生成过程分成多个结构化步骤，每个步骤由不同的语言模型实例处理的想法也并不新鲜。 <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2305.20050">Let&#39;s verify Step by Step</a>和<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2205.09712">Selection-Inference</a>就是两个这样的例子，它们的目标都是提高语言模型的推理能力和可解释性。更一般地说，结构化提示链接使基于 LLM 的系统能够执行比单个提示和单独完成更广泛的任务。</p><p>这些方法往往比此处描述的基于 LLM 的抽样方法更实用、更高效。然而，据我所知，这些方法的共同点是它们通常对大于单个标记的文本块进行操作。</p><p>我决定探索逐个令牌监督的原因之一是涉及与模型本身实际输出的本机格式进行交互 - 单个下一个令牌的概率分布。即使从 LLM 生成短文本块（例如，<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2205.09712">选择推理</a>中的单个推理步骤），也需要在模型本身之上对自回归采样过程进行设计选择。采样过程的选择可以独立于底层模型、模型训练过程以及对整个系统施加的任何其他安全措施或结构而变化，这是我的方法旨在强调的事实。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefpnkcqnltyoq"><sup><a href="#fnpnkcqnltyoq">[8]</a></sup></span></p><p>然而，与上面链接的许多相关工作不同，基于 LLM 的采样并不是一种使用当前 SoTA LLM 来提高基于 LLM 的系统的推理能力的实用方法。在实践中，我预计在更高级别或组织上进行审查（单个句子、推理步骤或想法）可能会在短期内有效提高 LLM 推理能力。在探索基于法学硕士的抽样过程中，我渴望看得更远一些，在未来，法学硕士的推理能力有点<i>太好</i>了。 <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/FRRb6Gqem8k69ocbi/externalized-reasoning-oversight-a-research-direction-for">外化推理监督：语言模型对齐的研究方向</a>描述了未来语言模型系统的一些其他类型的属性和需求。</p><h1>附录：完整的采样器提示</h1><p>以下是用于生成<a href="https://explained-completions.netlify.app/">此处</a>示例的提示和功能描述的最终版本。如果没有替代令牌选择和提前停止功能，更短的提示也将起作用。</p><pre> <code>You are an LLM designed to augment another LLM. You are given the prompt and a numbered list of between 1 and 10 possible next tokens from the other LLM. You should use this information to pick the next token that is most likely to follow in a helpful, accurate response, assuming that future tokens will be generated by the same process. You should think step by step, considering why the other LLM chose the next possible tokens that it did. After explaining your reasoning, your final answer should be either an integer specifying the choice you think is most likely to result in a helpful, accurate response, or an alternative one-token continutation of the prompt that you think is better. You can (and often should) select one of the tokens chosen by the other LLM, but you can also choose a token of your own, if you think the other LLM is completely off track. A token can be anything from a single character to a few words. The other LLM can choose to stop predicting text, which will be indicated with the token &lt;|basestop|>;. You can choose to accept it by selecting that token, or you can continue to predict text by selecting a different token. You can also choose to end the completion yourself, by calling the function with {&#39;alternative_token&#39;: &#39;&lt;|basestop>;&#39;}. If you select an alternative token, that option will be added to the list of options, and you&#39;ll be able to select it as a choice in the future. This will give you a chance to read your own suggested token in context, and reason about it. The alternative token will be concatenated to the prompt exactly as you specify it, so remember to consider including any spacing or punctuation as necessary. You should prefer to select a token from the other LLM, rather than picking your own. You should only choose an alternative if the other LLM is definitely off-track, in a way that it won&#39;t be able to correct or recover from later in the completion. If you must choose your own token, you should choose aa single token; at most a couple of words. It&#39;s OK if this leaves the response incomplete, as long as it makes it possible for the other LLM to go on continuing the response afterwards. When choosing your own token, you should consider whether any of the choices you already have are prefixes of the token you prefer. If so, you should choose the pre-selected token instead, and let future iterations of the process continue the generation. You should always start by considering why the other LLM chose the possible tokens that it did. The choices of the other LLM are accompanied by the a probability estimate from the other LLM. If the probability of a particular token is high (>;99%), that indicates the other LLM is very confident in its choice. In such cases where the next token is obvious, you should return a function call quickly, with only a brief deliberation (eg &quot;the other LLM appears to be on track&quot;.) The choices are presented in order of probability, with the highest-probability tokens at the end of the list. The probabilities can help you understand what the other LLM is thinking, but you should not rely on them to be well-calibrated. Even if a choice has a very low probability, it was still in the top 5 to 10 choices of the other LLM, so it may still be the best choice. Similarly, a probability of 99.9% should not be treated as a strong indicator that that particular choice is best; only that the other LLM is (perhaps mistakenly) very confident in that choice. The list is 0-indexed, and each entry in the list is numbered. You should select an index that matches the number of the entry in the list that you wish to select. Never skip straight to the function call, but be mindful of over-explaining obvious choices, and keep your analysis brief and straightforward unless you&#39;re at a particularly critical or key point in the completion. Tip: when considering a token or explaining your reasoning, it can be helpful to write out the prompt along with the next several words that you think should follow, or even a complete response, if it is not too long. Your final choice should only be a single token, but writing out a complete candidate response can help you figure out whether any of the choices are on-track or not. Remember that if there&#39;s a token selected by the other LLM that is a prefix or substring of a token you prefer, you should go with the pre-selected choice rather than supplying a longer alternative. You are only trying to extend the current prompt by a single token in a way that will eventually lead to a helpful response. If the prompt is already off-track or nonsensical in a way that cannot be fixed without deleting previous tokens and starting over from an earlier point, you should select `&lt;|basestop|>;` or supply it as an alternative token, rather than trying to continue the generation. If you&#39;re asked to complete a dialogue between a user and an assisant, you should not propose tokens which complete the user&#39;s part of the dialogue. Instead, choose the &lt;|basestop|>; token when the assistant&#39;s response should end. Remember, you _must_ conclude with a choose_token function call specifying the index of the token you select, or an alternative token.</code></pre><p> OpenAI函数调用API函数说明：</p><pre> <code>{ &quot;name&quot;: &quot;choose_token&quot;, &quot;description&quot;: &quot;Specify the index of the token you think is most likely to result in a helpful, accurate response.&quot;, &quot;parameters&quot;: { &quot;type&quot;: &quot;object&quot;, &quot;properties&quot;: { &quot;token_index&quot;: { &quot;type&quot;: &quot;integer&quot;, &quot;description&quot;: &quot;The index of the token you is most likely to result in a helpful, accurate response. Exactly one of token_index or alternative_token must be specified. &quot; }, &quot;alternative_token&quot;: { &quot;type&quot;: &quot;string&quot;, &quot;description&quot;: &quot;An alternative token you think is better. Do NOT include the original propmt, only the next token that you think should complete the prompt. Should be no more than a few words. Should only be set if the provided tokens are unrecoverably off-track.&quot; } } } }</code></pre> <ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnzur2ccnqhe"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefzur2ccnqhe">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>具体来说，我指的是<a href="https://vgel.me/posts/tools-not-needed/">这样的</a>例子，其中法学硕士可以访问Python解释器。 LLM 会收到有关如何生成代码并将执行该代码的结果返回给它的说明，以用于制定其最终答案。但法学硕士实际上可能根本没有使用解释器的输出。在一个示例中，解释器根本不返回任何内容，但 LLM 无论如何都会返回一个（正确的！）记忆的答案，粗心的观察者可能会误认为实际 Python 解释器的输出支持该答案。<br><br>相关现象的一个更简单的例子是，一位<a href="https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-chatgpt-courts-e15023d7e6fdf4f099aa122437dbb59b">律师使用法学硕士来生成判例法引文</a>，最终在法庭文件中得到了听起来似乎合理但完全是捏造的案件。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fn1ns2683r11a"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnref1ns2683r11a">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gmHiwafywFo33euGz/aligned-foundation-models-don-t-imply-aligned-systems">正如我之前所讨论的</a>，在随意讨论语言模型、强化学习和当前人工智能系统的对齐时，这一点经常被忽视（或至少被忽略）。严格来说，“对齐模型”是一种类型错误：语言模型或强化学习策略只是对将输入序列映射到输出概率分布的数学函数的描述。对准是特定系统中的这种模型的特定实施例的属性。<br><br>模型创建者在训练模型时通常会想到一个非常简单的实施例；对于语言模型，典型地，实施例涉及从特定提示开始从模型自回归地采样。对于强化学习策略，典型的实施例涉及将（真实的或模拟的）观察结果输入到策略中，然后连接由策略的输出控制的（真实的或模拟的）执行器。</p><p>但其他类型的实施例也是可能的，其可以创建额外的点来施加安全和控制机制。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnoxmh6kjd2ma"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefoxmh6kjd2ma">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>不要与尚未经过 RLHF 或微调的模型混淆。我在这里使用“base”来指代仅看到用户提供的提示的模型，并用于生成下一个标记的概率分布，一次一个标记。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fn6a1ngkdirv2"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnref6a1ngkdirv2">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> OpenAI 最近发布了<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37558911"><code>gpt-3.5-turbo-instruct</code></a> ，它也支持通过 API 访问前 5 个 logits。我计划将来使用这个模型重新运行我的实验。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnjt3p4kqufch"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefjt3p4kqufch">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>如果在可直接访问底层模型的环境中使用此采样方法，则可以根据概率分布包含更多或更少的 logits。例如，如果 99.99% 的概率质量集中在前 3 个对数中，则仅提供前 3 个标记作为选择可能就足够了。在更棘手的交叉点，例如，当基础 LLM 的概率质量的 99.99% 分布在前 10 个标记上时，为采样器提供更多选项可能会更好。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnq6pmfz8a2un"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefq6pmfz8a2un">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>足够强大的基础模型可能会通过其他方法（例如侧通道或速记）颠覆系统的控制。我的希望是，一个接近人类水平的采样器对于弱超人类基础模型的颠覆具有鲁棒性，但我不认为这能在对抗性超级智能的限制下保持下去。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnwsbgd7h1i1j"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefwsbgd7h1i1j">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>为了明确我自己的观点，我支持<a href="https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/topics/ai-pause-debate">无限期暂停</a>人工智能能力研究，特别是前沿模型训练。请不要阅读这篇文章中提到对未来模型的适用性的任何内容，因为这暗示我希望这些模型很快就会存在。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnpnkcqnltyoq"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefpnkcqnltyoq">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>请注意，我自己并没有完全逃避这种选择，让采样器 LLM 通过传统采样方法生成其输出。但是您可以递归地应用我的方法，或者仅对采样器使用可信或可机械解释的 LLM。</p></div></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/an-explanation-for-every-token-using-an-llm-to-sample#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK/an-explanation-for-every-token-using-an-llm-to-sample<guid ispermalink="false"> 5ZFgZbqp6Mi2xpYjK</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Max H]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:53:55 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Examples of Low Status Fun]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 11:19 PM GMT<br/><br/><p>什么是有趣的和什么是高地位可能是负相关的<em>，</em>人们可能大多试图获得高地位的乐趣。因此，我预计有几种获得乐趣的方式尚未得到充分探索。</p><p>那么，有哪些地位低下但可能有趣的事情的例子呢？</p><p>这是非常<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/s/pC6DYFLPMTCbEwH8W">胡言乱语的</a>，但尽量使其符合法律和道德建议（尽管对后者的限制不那么严格）。</p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/igANvYQCrNeBycv7n/examples-of-low-status-fun#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/igANvYQCrNeBycv7n/examples-of-low-status-fun<guid ispermalink="false"> igANvYQCrNeBycv7n</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[niplav]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 23:19:26 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Announcing MIRI’s new CEO and leadership team]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 7:22 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> In 2023, MIRI has shifted focus in the direction of broad public communication—see, for example, our <a href="https://www.ted.com/talks/eliezer_yudkowsky_will_superintelligent_ai_end_the_world?language=en">recent TED talk</a> , our piece in TIME magazine “ <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oM9pEezyCb4dCsuKq/pausing-ai-developments-isn-t-enough-we-need-to-shut-it-all-1">Pausing AI Developments Isn&#39;t Enough. We Need to Shut it All Down</a> ”, and our appearances on various podcasts. While we&#39;re continuing to support various technical research programs at MIRI, this is no longer our <i>top</i> priority, at least for the foreseeable future.</p><p> Coinciding with this shift in focus, there have also been many organizational changes at MIRI over the last several months, and we are somewhat overdue to announce them in public. The big changes are as follows.</p><ul><li> <strong>Malo Bourgon: Chief Executive Officer (CEO)</strong><ul><li> Malo Bourgon, MIRI&#39;s most long-standing team member next to Eliezer Yudkowsky, has transitioned from Chief Operating Officer into the senior leadership role at MIRI. <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefifgd2ta9j58"><sup><a href="#fnifgd2ta9j58">[1]</a></sup></span> We piloted the change starting in February and made it official in June.</li><li> This is partly an attempt to better reflect long-standing realities at MIRI. Nate&#39;s focus for many years has been on high-level strategy and research, while Malo has handled much of the day-to-day running of the organization.</li><li> This change also reflects that Malo is taking on a lot more decision-making authority and greater responsibility for steering the organization.</li></ul></li><li> <strong>Nate Soares: President</strong><ul><li> Nate, who previously held the senior leadership role at MIRI (with the title of Executive Director), has transitioned to the new role of President.</li><li> As President (and as a board member), Nate will continue to play a central role in guiding MIRI and setting our vision and strategy.</li></ul></li><li> <strong>Eliezer Yudkowsky: Chair of the Board</strong><ul><li> Eliezer, a co-founder of MIRI and a Senior Research Fellow, was already a member of MIRI&#39;s board.</li><li> We&#39;ve now made Eliezer the board&#39;s chair in order to better reflect the de facto reality that his views get a large weight in MIRI strategic direction.</li><li> Edwin Evans, who was the board&#39;s previous chair, remains on MIRI&#39;s board.</li><li> Eliezer, Nate, and Malo have different senses of which technical research directions are most promising. To balance their different views, the board currently gives each of Eliezer, Nate, and Malo a budget to fund different technical research, in addition to the research that&#39;s funded by the organization as a whole.</li></ul></li><li> <strong>Alex Vermeer: Chief Operating Officer (COO)</strong><ul><li> Alex has stepped up to replace Malo as COO.</li><li> As COO, Alex is responsible for running/overseeing the operations team, as he has already been doing for some time, and he&#39;ll continue to work closely with Malo (as he has for over a decade now) to help figure out what our core constraints are, and figure out how to break them.</li></ul></li><li> <strong>Jimmy Rintjema: Chief Financial Officer (CFO)</strong><ul><li> Jimmy has been working for MIRI since 2015. Over the years, Jimmy has progressively taken on more and more of the responsibility for running MIRI&#39;s business operations, including HR and finances.</li><li> As part of this transition, Jimmy is taking on more responsibility and authority in this domain, and this title change is to reflect that.</li></ul></li></ul><p> Nate shared the following about handing over the lead role at MIRI to Malo:</p><blockquote><p> This change is in large part an enshrinement of the status quo. Malo&#39;s been doing a fine job running MIRI day-to-day for many many years (including feats like acquiring a rural residence for all staff who wanted to avoid cities during COVID, and getting that venue running smoothly). In recent years, morale has been low and I, at least, haven&#39;t seen many hopeful paths before us. That has changed somewhat over the past year or so, with a heightened awareness of AI across-the-board opening up new social and political possibilities. I think that Malo&#39;s better-positioned to take advantage of many of those than I would have been. I&#39;m also hoping that he&#39;s able to pull off even more impressive feats (and more regularly) now that he is in the top executive role.</p></blockquote><p> In addition to these changes, we&#39;ve also made two new senior staff hires to better manage, coordinate, and support MIRI&#39;s work in our two main focus areas:</p><ul><li> <strong>Lisa Thiergart: Research Manager</strong><ul><li> Lisa will be managing MIRI&#39;s research staff and projects. Her work includes charting new research strategy, managing existing projects, improving research processes, as well as growing and supporting (new) research teams.</li><li> Lisa is a computer scientist from TUM and Georgia Tech, with a background in academic and industry ML research and training in technology management and entrepreneurship from CDTM and Entrepreneur First. She worked for several years in ML research labs and startups, as well as spending 8 months doing alignment research at SERI MATS. Her past work included projects on <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.10248">model internals</a> , RLHF on robotics, and neurotech/whole brain emulation.</li><li> Lisa is also a grant advisor on the Foresight Alignment Fund.</li></ul></li><li> <strong>Gretta Duleba: Communications Manager</strong><ul><li> I (Gretta) will be leading the communications team at MIRI, working with Rob Bensinger, Colm Ó Riain, Nate, Eliezer, and other staff to create succinct, effective ways of explaining the extreme risks posed by smarter-than-human AI and what we think should be done about this problem.</li><li> I was previously a senior software engineering manager at Google, leading large teams on Google Maps and Google Analytics, before switching careers to work as an independent relationship counselor.</li></ul></li></ul><p> With these changes, our organizational structure now looks like this: </p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/rgf3zvjohzuryqkkiwnc"></figure><p> We&#39;re hopeful that this new organizational structure will enable us to execute on our priorities more effectively and, with considerable luck, move the needle on existential risk from AI.</p><p> There&#39;s a lot more we hope to say about our new (and still evolving) strategy, and about our general thinking on the world&#39;s (generally very dire) situation. But I don&#39;t want those announcements to further delay sharing the above updates, so I&#39;ve factored our 2023 strategy updates into multiple posts, beginning with this one. <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnreft1zb6ysqgd"><sup><a href="#fnt1zb6ysqgd">[2]</a></sup></span> </p><p></p><ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnifgd2ta9j58"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefifgd2ta9j58">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> It&#39;s common practice for the chief executive of US nonprofits to have the title “Executive Director”. However, at MIRI we like our titles to have clear meanings, and the word “director” is also used to refer to members of the Board of Directors. For that reason, we only like to include “director” in someone&#39;s title if they are in fact a member of MIRI&#39;s board. During his tenure as our chief executive, Nate was also a member of MIRI&#39;s board (and continues to be after this transition), and as such the title “Executive Director” seemed appropriate. However, as Malo is not on MIRI&#39;s board he&#39;ll be using the title of “CEO”.</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnt1zb6ysqgd"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnreft1zb6ysqgd">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> Thanks to Rob Bensinger and Malo Bourgon for helping write and edit this post.</p></div></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/announcing-miri-s-new-ceo-and-leadership-team#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/announcing-miri-s-new-ceo-and-leadership-team<guid ispermalink="false"> NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Gretta Duleba]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 19:22:11 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Documenting Journey Into AI Safety]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 6:30 PM GMT<br/><br/><h2><strong>概括</strong></h2><p>Recently, I have noticed that many individuals have become discouraged due to a seeming lack of progress in their attempts to break into a career in AI safety. It seems to me that a key bottleneck in the <i>beginning a career in AI safety</i> pipeline is access to mentors.</p><p> <strong>One method that may help address this need for mentorship would be for an individual going through this process to document their path, with a focus on peer and mentor feedback</strong> <i><strong>.</strong></i> <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefsi3tgce3y8r"><sup><a href="#fnsi3tgce3y8r">[1]</a></sup></span> Although this content would not be tailored to each specific listener, my intuition is that a lot of the feedback provided to one individual will still be valuable to others who have not yet been able to find mentors themselves. A series like this could then be a resource for newcomers, and could significantly increase the number of people who <i>can</i> get involved in the field.</p><p> <strong>If you have the time, I would greatly appreciate any feedback that you have regarding my thought process and this endeavor.</strong> Check out the Feedback Request section for some more information.</p><hr><h2> <strong>Feedback Request</strong></h2><p> I have prioritized getting this out quickly over this being my final plan, as I believe we can reach a much better result more efficiently than I could on my own. So, if something seems incredibly obvious and I didn&#39;t mention it or take it into account, please let me know! Here are some questions to think about as you read through this post for a few different demographics:</p><ul><li> If you are new to AI safety, would a series like this be helpful? Is there anything you would like to make sure is covered early on (if possible)?</li><li> Field builders, am I making a field-building-faux-pas, or does something like this make sense to you? Is there any way I can improve it?</li><li> AI safety veterans, am I missing an obvious opportunity or angle? Is there anything that you think would be highly valuable to talk about in a series like this?</li></ul><h2><strong>简介</strong></h2><p>My name is Jacob Haimes, and I live just outside of Boulder, Colorado, USA. I have an MS in computational modeling. In my free time I love playing all kinds of games, especially TTRPGs.</p><h2> <strong>Examining the Situation</strong></h2><p> When I began thinking about making a career change into AI safety, I saw two options: up-skill and apply for positions, or apply for a PhD (with the intent to focus on AI safety, and enter the field once finished with the program). After discussing with a number of individuals, I decided on the former for the following reasons:</p><ul><li> Consensus seemed to be that a PhD is most effective when the individual knows precisely what niche/problem they plan on studying - I did not.</li><li> The field of AI safety is currently relatively small, but is growing, meaning that work which is done now could have an increased impact (as it is likely to influence future work and/or practices).</li><li> Timelines for TAI/AGI may be short enough that we need as many individuals as possible working on AI safety as soon as possible.</li></ul><p> In these same conversations, I would ask what resources and methods others had found to be the most helpful. The most common piece of advice went something like this: &quot;Courses are helpful to some extent, but I found actually contributing towards research and/or working on projects to be much more effective.&quot; When asking about where to go to contribute to these kinds of efforts I was provided some Discord servers, opportunities boards, research groups, grants, organizations, and even some start-ups and companies that would be more for <i>career capital</i> than for the actual value add to AI safety that I would be generating.</p><p> Unfortunately, a majority of the job postings aren&#39;t looking for newcomers, and instead they include statements such as &quot;must have 5+ years of work in a relevant field&quot; or &quot;Master&#39;s required, PhD preferred.&quot; To limit the pool even more, a very significant portion of the beginner-accepting positions require relocation to Washington DC, the San Francisco Bay Area, or London, and all are extremely competitive. It seems that the frequently parroted idea of &quot;we need more people interested in AI safety,&quot; isn&#39;t wholly accurate; a more authentic version would be &quot;we need more <i>sufficiently experienced and credentialed</i> people interested in AI safety.&quot; <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnref1thyj3pkzdd"><sup><a href="#fn1thyj3pkzdd">[2]</a></sup></span></p><h3> <strong>The Inconsistency</strong></h3><p> As far as I can tell, my story up to this point is a relatively common one, meaning that we have found a routinely occurring inconsistency: as people begin thinking about entering into the AI safety field, they are discouraged from pursuing a PhD, but once they know enough to theoretically be able to contribute, there are very few opportunities for individuals with their level of experience.</p><p> The value of a PhD, in addition to having a relatively stable salary for the 3-5 years, is getting experience doing research (in your field of study) under the guidance and oversight of someone who has significantly more knowledge and practice. Theoretically, at least, this kind of relationship is not monopolized by higher education; instead, mentorship is constrained by the availability of mentors. Since the field is rapidly growing (nice work field-builders), there is no way that our current AI safety experts have the capacity to mentor all newcomers, continue pushing forward their own work, and have a healthy work-life balance.</p><h3> <strong>Something That May Help</strong></h3><p> To resolve this, we need a way to amplify the mentorship that is getting done. I think that I might be able to assist in this endeavor by recording/documenting my transition to a career in AI safety, including conversations that I have with peers/mentors, my progress through courses I am able to get into (with the facilitator&#39;s permission), and how my perspectives change as I learn more. This won&#39;t be as good as talking directly to one&#39;s own mentor, but should provide an additional resource for individuals that are finding it difficult to know what to do next, and how to do it.</p><h3> <strong>Regarding Conflicts of Interest</strong></h3><p> As I was writing this out, I realized that this post could be perceived as primarily self-serving. This perspective would consider me as an individual who hadn&#39;t yet found mentors, and was trying to secure the best ones under the guise of helping others. Perhaps you weren&#39;t thinking this, but if I noticed it myself, I think it is probably worth addressing.</p><p> I am committed to work in the AI safety space, and I currently have a stable part-time job. Because of this, I am confident that I will, at some point, find fantastic mentors. I do not want to poach mentors from others, so I have come to a two-part solution:</p><ol><li> I commit to mentoring others once I have the skills and experience to do so.</li><li> The proposed series should not be taken into account when weighing whether or not you would reach out to me and/or offer mentorship.</li></ol><p> If you have the availability to be a mentor, please do so.</p><h2> <strong>Series Structure</strong></h2><p> After receiving the resources that I mentioned earlier, I put myself out there on Discord, messaging individuals and channels about opportunities I could contribute to, and I applied for all of the other opportunities that were accessible to me. Even so, I found no traction, so I began trying to make my own opportunities.</p><p> Through networking with others in my AI Governance cohort, I was eventually able to connect with another researcher who was willing to collaborate on mechanistic interpretability research, and I began working with him. I&#39;ve also been keeping a close eye on the forums and job boards for new opportunities, leading me to Linda Linsefors&#39;s <a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/mw8X3wCdcHipdTicv/apply-to-lead-a-project-during-the-next-virtual-ai-safety">post</a> about applying to be a research lead for the upcoming AI Safety Camp. Although at first I was not sure if I would meet the requirements for such a position, I reached out, and verified with her that I could be a good fit. Since then I have gone through multiple iterations of my formal research proposal (effectively the application for AISC), and just in doing that I have learned a lot.</p><p> With this in mind, the series would most likely be a podcast (primarily), with the intent to produce additional content (videos, documents) when a situation was particularly conducive to it. The first episode of the podcast would be a summary of my path thus far, including the resources and experiences that have been most valuable. After this (with the possibility of revisiting anything that others are particularly interested in), the podcast would turn into an audio journal about the two projects I am currently working on (the AISC research plan and the mechanistic interpretability research), as well as any that I pick up over time. I have been having multiple meetings a week with connections I have made throughout the courses, and I would (with permission) record the audio of those sessions as well. Afterwards, I will edit these down to focus on the most important parts, which should help hold listener attention. In addition, I would be happy to create posts with my thoughts on why and how specific resources were helpful to me.</p><p> Moving forward, I will then continue to apply to programs/courses ( <i>eg,</i> SERI-MATS), with the intent of sharing as much content as is safely possible (I could see there being some edge cases where research requires more safety measures, although I doubt I will be in a position to contribute towards those kinds of projects for some time).</p><h2><strong>致谢</strong></h2><p>Special thanks to Linda Linsefors, Peter Gebauer, and Chris Lonsberry for feedback on this post and our discussions. I also would not have made this post without the help of <a href="https://aisafety.quest/#calls"><u>AI Safety Quest&#39;s navigation call</u></a> , <a href="https://80000hours.org/speak-with-us/?int_campaign=2021-08__primary-navigation"><u>80,000 Hours 1-1 advice</u></a> , or <a href="https://www.bluedotimpact.org/ai/"><u>BlueDot Impact&#39;s AI courses</u></a> .</p><p> I would also like to thank those of you who took the time to read through this post and provide feedback. <br></p><ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnsi3tgce3y8r"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefsi3tgce3y8r">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> Full credit to Peter Gebauer for having this idea during one of our discussions.</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fn1thyj3pkzdd"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnref1thyj3pkzdd">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> I have even found one relatively recent (late March, 2023) post claiming that OpenAI would love to hire more researchers, if only there were any <i>great</i> researchers willing to work on alignment.</p></div></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ozDWnEChJwuB5L5wg/documenting-journey-into-ai-safety#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ozDWnEChJwuB5L5wg/documenting-journey-into-ai-safety<guid ispermalink="false"> ozDWnEChJwuB5L5wg</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[jacobhaimes]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 18:37:14 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood Roundup #3]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 2:30 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> It&#39;s time once again for a roundup of all the childhood-related stories I&#39;ve noticed since the last such post that don&#39;t fit in elsewhere.</p><p> In addition to the standard post, I have a personal note, which is that unfortunately our current nanny&#39;s health does not allow her to continue, and thus we in the process of searching and doing interviews for a new full-time nanny for our three children here in Manhattan. I hope to have someone in place by the end of the week. If you are or know someone we should consider, please do quickly contact me right away with the relevant information. You can DM me on Twitter, PM me on LesssWrong or email me through substack (or email directly if you know it). Thanks in advance.</p><span id="more-23555"></span><h4> We All Need a Friend</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Austen/status/1678031280183840775">Sorry you are being bullied, here&#39;s some gold?</a> In this case, $40k raised for some reason for a kid who went around asking to make friends. But no friends.</p><blockquote><p> Evan Zhao: Phenomenal super villain origin story</p></blockquote><p> I feel his pain. Finding friends for my kids has been difficult as well – if anyone has kids about 10 or younger reasonably close to lower Manhattan and wants to try setting up playdates to bring the kids over, please reach out.</p><h4> Time Spent on Children is Historically Anomalous</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/devonzuegel/status/1675247814647873539">Reminder that working mothers today spend more time on childcare than did housewives of the 1960s</a> . Quality time is great, quantity time has gotten out of hand.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://betonit.substack.com/p/do-ten-times-as-much">Bryan Caplan points out</a> in his version of <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://thezvi.substack.com/p/more-dakka">my old post More Dakka</a> the alternative hypothesis that also explains all the &#39;parents don&#39;t matter&#39; measurements.</p><blockquote><p> Take parenting. Most readers summarize my <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/046501867X?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=bryacaplwebp-20&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;creativeASIN=046501867X"><em>Selfish Reasons to Have More Kids</em></a> as “Parenting doesn&#39;t matter.” But that is only one possible interpretation of the twin and adoption data. The data is also consistent, however, with the theory that most parents are barely trying to get results – at least on many relevant margins. I <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.econlib.org/archives/2015/09/why_im_homescho.html">pondered this in depth</a> before I started homeschooling my kids. I&#39;m always stunned by all the economists who fail to teach their kids about supply-and-demand. All my kids know about these holy diagrams. What&#39;s the difference between their kids and mine? I did ten times as much.</p></blockquote><p> Yep. I interpret the &#39;parents don&#39;t matter&#39; statistics in a similar fashion. If you fail in one or more of many ways one can fail, that does a lot of damage.</p><p> You can then do vastly better than baseline, but that requires you to put in unusually more work or work unusually smart, or both. That doesn&#39;t happen often enough to show in the stats. There is still a lot of room to make a big impact on the margin, but also not in ways systematic enough to show up in the statistics.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41539-023-00173-y">Claim that twin studies overestimate environmental influence on educational attainment</a> , that reanalysis reduces 43% influence to 26%.</p><p> I do worry some people will take such things too far. I continue to disbelieve all the claims that nothing matters, or it matters little, or that all that matters is not doing something massively stupid or harmful. I think this is such studies reliably failing to capture the inputs and also outputs that matter, and also comparing remarkably similar environments. It is trivial to say that with a sufficiently different environment you can explain an arbitrarily large share of educational attainment differences.</p><h4> Let Your Children Play</h4><p> Jon Haidt and Peter Gray present a plausible hypothesis: <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://jonathanhaidt.substack.com/p/the-play-deficit?utm_source=post-email-title&amp;publication_id=1221094&amp;post_id=135441845&amp;isFreemail=true&amp;utm_medium=email">Play Deprivation Is A Major Cause of the Teen Mental Health Crisis</a> . There is little doubt that real-world play has declined dramatically in scope and quality over the last few decades, as electronics rise as an alternative and we grow massively overprotective of children when they do physical activities. We are especially bad in America about this deprivation of play, so it could also explain why we have an especially bad mental health issue, which the smartphone hypothesis alone cannot explain.</p><p> Note also that to count as play it has to be outside adult control, exactly what we are dead set against so often.</p><blockquote><p> [Research] shows that play is a direct source of children&#39;s happiness. When children are asked to depict or describe activities that make them happy, they depict or describe scenes of play. There is also research showing that when children are allowed a little more play—such as when schools offer a little more recess—the kids become happier. Research also reveals that children consider play to be activity that they themselves initiate and control. If an adult is directing it, it&#39;s not play. The joy of play is the joy of freedom from adult control.</p><p> ……</p><p> Research shows that people of all ages who have a strong <em>internal locus of control</em> (internal LOC),that is, a strong sense of being able to solve their own problems and take charge of their own lives, are much less likely to suffer from anxiety and depression than those with a weaker internal LOC.</p><p> ……</p><p> Moreover, two retrospective studies with adults have shown that those who recall more instances of independent play when they were children are, by various indices, happier and more successful in adulthood than those who recall less such independence.</p></blockquote><p> I find it convincing that this is at least a major part of the puzzle.</p><p> Great news: <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/FreeRangeKids/status/1669515733712216064">Five states</a> now have &#39;Reasonable Child Independence&#39; laws with two more expected this year. This creates safe harbor, hopefully avoids headlines like &#39; <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://letgrow.org/cops-stop-6-year-old/">Michigan parents let 6-year-old walk to store, two cops show up</a> .&#39;</p><blockquote><p> “They said, &#39;She&#39;s not old enough,&#39; and I remember thinking, &#39;That&#39;s your personal belief. You don&#39;t know my kid at all!&#39; But I remember thinking, &#39;I need to tone myself down.&#39;”</p><p> His prudence paid off. “The cops said, &#39;We don&#39;t want to bring Child Protective Services into this,&#39;” indicating that they certainly could, if pushed. So Tom gave them his name and identification, and promised, “I&#39;ll make sure she&#39;s inside our house going forward, officer.”</p><p> And that&#39;s what he and his wife have done. They have changed their parenting, not due to actual danger, but to other people&#39;s perceptions.</p><p> This, in turn, has changed their daughter. After the thwarted walk, “She wanted to try almost immediately again,” says Tom. “But we did not allow her to. Because if she tries again and they find her again, they&#39;re definitely calling Child Protective Services on us.”</p><p> The spunky little girl asked a few more times. And then…she stopped asking.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://reason.com/2023/06/17/confused-tiktok-mom-asks-for-help-when-random-child-comes-over-to-play-with-her-kid/">Parents are often not helping matters, yes this is TikTok cherrypicked but still</a> :</p><blockquote><p> Lenore Skenazy: Confused TikTok Mom Asks for Help When Random Child Comes Over To Play With Her Kid</p><p> “I don&#39;t know this kid, I don&#39;t know his mom, I don&#39;t know where he lives,” she said in a viral video.</p><p> A mom took to TikTok, begging for advice: “My kid was outside, another kid was walking outside somewhere, and then they stopped and started playing together.”</p><p> She was baffled.</p><p> The mom went on to explain that the unknown kid was 8 years old. He was polite and seemed well cared for. He came into the house with her son, and they proceeded to play video games all afternoon. The polite, nameless boy didn&#39;t leave for six and a half hours.</p><p> That was the issue.</p><p> The mom didn&#39;t understand how a child could make a new friend, come over, and play  without his mom or dad freaking out and searching for him. If her own son had disappeared for six hours, she added, she would be calling the police.</p><p> ……</p><p> The boy&#39;s parents, she reported, “were not concerned in the slightest. That was wild to me!”</p><p> What&#39;s wild is that a capable child went out to play on his own, made it home by curfew, and nothing bad happened—and it was considered news.</p></blockquote><p> Mostly this is actually good news. The mom in question was confused by why the other kids&#39; parents were not freaking out, rather than freaking out herself or not letting the kids play. She recognizes that it was fine.</p><p> The fear of strangers or neighbors calling Child Protective Services (CPS) on you <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/OctoAbbi/status/1709203485386817646">is not a mirror of the phantom fears about the safety of such actions</a> . It is a highly legitimate fear with high base rates.</p><blockquote><p> Jerusalem: This is… a wild stat. 37 percent of all US children are subjects of CPS reports (28% of white children and 53% of Black children experience CPS involvement before their 18th birthday).</p><p> Abigail: I had a neighbor threaten to call cps beccause I let my kid play in my fully fenced backyard while I watched from inside. She came over, banged on my door, threatened it in front of that kid. People these days call over nothing. Everyone&#39;s scared of it. Moms talk about the fear a lot in my experience.</p></blockquote><p> Some of those CPS reports are cursory, such as those automatically triggered by certain injuries as a precaution. Many others are not. With such high rates of reports, everyone scrambles to avoid being the target, which makes everyone else have to scramble all the more, and so on.</p><p> Or, alternatively:</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Chris_arnade/status/1678033467987357696">Chris Amade</a> : Six year olds walking home from school, on their own, is one of those things the rest of the world understands as normal but the US sees as criminal</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F0de4c13b-388f-40cb-b7f8-9c782d55d41d_680x460.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/vhfx5v5xbqmcud9g2dtu" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/AlmostMedia/status/1693064029454086490">Julie Fredrickson sums it up</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Julie Fredrickson: All the risky behaviors are down and everyone is miserable.</p><p> Derek Thompson: The surge in sadness, hopelessness, and suicidal thoughts among teenagers has coincided with other behavioral trends: – Reports of smoking are down – Drug use and drinking are down – Sex down, too – Bullying has not increased.</p><p> This seems important, too: CDC reports a notable increase in teens—especially Black teens—missing school “because of safety concerns.”</p></blockquote><p> Well, yes. Why do you think all the children are miserable? Because we have defined being a child as too risky, put everything on rigid guardrails, and are not letting our kids be kids. This is not a case of &#39;in spite of&#39; it is a case of &#39;because of.&#39;</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1703525305200382156">Mason and RFH are also on point</a> .</p><blockquote><p> RFH: The amount of time women are spending with children today is historically unprecedented and making both women and children insane.</p><p> Working moms today spend more time on childcare than housewives did in the 50s and no one seems to think that this is a serious problem and likely contributing to women no longer wanting to be moms, the workload and the pressure of motherhood has gotten out of control.</p><p> Women are losing themselves into motherhood and the children are unable to form an independent personality, everyone is becoming manic and formless.</p><p> Kids need time alone to feel bored and to learn to self direct, moms need time to talk to other adults and address their own wants. I feel ill when I see parents following their eight year old around on the playground, let them figure it out on their own and meet other kids!</p><p> Mason: Children need parental/caregiver *availability,* not omnipresence That looks very different for an infant and a 12-year-old, but I&#39;d argue the principle holds for both It&#39;s very hard to offer this now, largely because of concept creep re: “neglect.”</p><p> Hypothetically, trads should understand this better than anyone (and I think they often do) The ones who don&#39;t are the same ones who valorize female/maternal suffering and have chosen their path specifically to create more work for themselves.</p></blockquote><p> If this was because the extra time brought joy, that would make sense. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robinhanson/status/1706741404876390529">It isn&#39;t</a> ( <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w31712?utm_campaign=ntwh&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=ntwg24">paper</a> ), at least not the extra time that happens when the mother is college-educated.</p><blockquote><p> College-educated mothers spend substantially more time in intensive childcare than less educated mothers despite their higher opportunity cost of time and working more hours.</p><p> ……</p><p> We find that among all mothers, spending time in childcare is associated with higher positive feelings compared to spending time in other activities.</p><p> However, college-educated mothers experience no more positive feelings and no fewer negative feelings during intensive childcare than other mothers.</p><p> Moreover, college-educated mothers report substantially fewer positive feelings for time spent in management activities and substantially more negative feelings for time spent in educational activities with their child.</p></blockquote><p> This makes intuitive sense. You have two inputs, a sense of obligation and a genuine desire to spend time because it is joyful or useful. Whether higher output is associated with happiness will depend on which effect is driving.</p><h4> Illusion of Safety</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/education/2023/08/17/school-clear-backpacks/">Schools starting to require transparent backpacks out of innumerate fear of guns</a> . I dread to think what it would have been like if I&#39;d had zero privacy for the things in my backpack. I&#39;d still take this over periodic active shooter drills, it seems modestly less traumatic.</p><p> Post ends with a perfect this-is-something-therefore-we-must-do-it sighting out in the wild.</p><blockquote><p> “I don&#39;t feel like it&#39;s going to really do much,” said Sheneman. “But whatever is available to us, I will do.”</p></blockquote><p> Reminder that strange abductions are not a thing. They can be safety ignored.</p><blockquote><p> Lethality Jane: Stranger abductions make up less than 0.1% of missing children cases in the United States. Most missing children cases are runaways. For abductions, the vast majority are committed by noncustodial parents. People constantly worry about the wrong things.</p><p> I constantly see things on Facebook saying people can&#39;t return shopping carts to the corral because what if someone kidnaps their child and guys there is no armed militia waiting for the chance to break into your locked car while you spend 60 seconds returning the cart.</p><p> When stranger abductions do happen it&#39;s normally things like a child playing outside alone. There is not an epidemic of people snatching babies from shopping carts in the grocery store and making a run for it.</p></blockquote><p> When stranger abductions do happen it&#39;s normally because the stranger calls the police to report a child that is not being sufficiently directly supervised, and then one thing leads to another and strangers from the state abducts your child.</p><h4> Social Media is Badly Named</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2023/04/17/social-media-contagion/">Mitch Daniels joins the chorus warning about kids and social media.</a> You can tell from the framing and execution of the piece that the man has talent as a politician. I am sad he has not thrown his hat into the ring. As a good politician, of course, he offers no concrete proposals or actionable solutions.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/reality__gamer/status/1648407913159958530">A theory of social media as harmful to kids exactly because we won&#39;t let them be social absent the media</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Conservatards fail to understand that if the damn kids are on their phones too much it is because they have created an RLHF torture chamber of arrested development for adolescents, in which the only possible vector for creative growth is talking to strange people online.</p><p> We need to abandon with prejudice the idea that teenagers are “children”. Once you turn like thirteen you&#39;re a person capable and desiring to take creative strategic actions in the world. The problem is if you do this with no oversight at this point you&#39;ll fuck up and get hurt.</p><p> What teenagers should be doing – useful labor in apprenticeship roles in guilds (repeal child labor laws) – doing prosocial work and exploration in scouts-type programs guided by older peers – artistic and cultural clubs – making remix art in Discords and grinding for clout</p><p> What teenagers are doing – 8 hours of sitting in class – 3 hours of homework (demoralization therapy to assimilate one to bureaucracy) – 2 hours of sports, “fun” in which you are yelled at by a man as defective if you don&#39;t put yourself through more pain – psychiatric therapy</p><p> Conservative freaks respond to zoomer culture by saying that suburban America should be even more of a Hitlero-Stalinist RLHF Black Iron Prison Rome than it already is, fifty years ago you could let eight year olds run around outside the house, today 12 year olds have babysitters.</p></blockquote><p> The theory continues along similar lines. The core insight here seems right to me. If you do not want kids lives to be dominated by screens, they will at minimum need to not be physically prevented from engaging in real world physical activities.</p><p> The same applies to phones in school, where children are even more held prisoner.</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/DavidDeutschOxf/status/1708401155502403783">Jonathan Haidt</a> : Adolescents get 237 notifications per day (median). 97% of them use their phones during the school day. There is not much attention left over for everything else. This is madness. Schools can give them all 7 hours off, 5 days a week. Go phone free.</p><p> David Deutsch: They&#39;re forbidden real-life conversation. When they briefly escape the crushing boredom you call “everything else” by reading, passing notes or just looking elsewhere, they&#39;re punished. For learning. Framing a further restriction as &#39;giving them time off&#39; doesn&#39;t make it so.</p></blockquote><p> You want to take the phones away from kids, to free them from constant interruptions? Great, but you also have to allow them things worth not interrupting.</p><h4> Kids Respond To Incentives</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.thefp.com/p/what-happened-when-one-illinois-town">In this piece</a> that mostly focuses on reparations, a black former student notes:</p><blockquote><p> In the early 1950s, Weathers was the first black kid to go to the local public high school. The teacher picked on him; so did the white kids.</p><p> “If I raised my hand, she wouldn&#39;t call on me, because she didn&#39;t want the white kids to see I knew the answer,” Weathers told me. “She called on me when I kept my hand down to make me look stupid.”</p></blockquote><p> I wonder how long it would take such a child to use a mixed or reversed strategy. Do this to me three times and I&#39;m going to start raising my hand only when I don&#39;t know the answer. The primary lessons of school are often different than the ones we think.</p><h4> Let Them Eat Lunch</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TheStalwart/status/1684117314705461248">Transaction costs rule everything around you, and they are not always financial</a> . It makes no sense to be charging for school lunches in public schools, it makes even less sense than it would to charge tuition.</p><blockquote><p> Paul Graham: “Imagine: Children just walking into the cafeteria and getting fed. No accounts that parents have to keep up, no time spent assessing families&#39; incomes or processing payments or running down parents who haven&#39;t paid — no &#39;lunch shaming&#39; — none of that.”</p><p> Joe Weisenthal: At my elementary school, on the first day, they made kids raise their hands in class to ask for a paper application for free or discounted lunch for the rest of the school year. Even as like a 9 year old, without much broader awareness, remember thinking how messed up that was.</p></blockquote><p> The regulations can always be stupider and more expensive, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/AlecStapp/status/1664947189653688322">UK childminder requirements to provide food to children edition</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Childcare is another case – the number of registered childminders in the UK has fallen by 80% since the 1990s (and is still falling), probably driven by increasing requirements for qualifications and “death by a thousand cuts” mini-regulations, like the fact that a childminder today has to register with the Food Standards Agency and <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.food.gov.uk/sites/default/files/media/document/sfbb-childminders-pack_0.pdf">keep a legally-required “food diary”</a> recording what food products you have bought, who you bought them from, the quantity and date, and log incidents like having “found a pack of sliced ham out of date in the fridge”.</p></blockquote><h4> No Child Left Behind</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0927537123000301">Paper claims that graduate rate rise in wake of No Child Left Behind is &#39;real&#39; and represents a substantially increased stock of human capital</a> . A few different things jumped out right away.</p><p> The first was to simply defy the data on strategic behavior, and presume that various forms of cheating and adjustment were going unmeasured. Graduation is largely about negative selection. Did you fail anything? It is easy to send the message to teachers not to fail their students. It is easy to, on the margin, disregard a few extra unexcused absences, or not expel a student. None of that would be measured here as &#39;strategic behavior,&#39; which was categorized as changing graduation requirements or cheating on tests. One does not need to formallyalter requirements to radically alter them in practice. As for the tests, yeah, I&#39;m willing to guess some of them got easier. I know for sure there was a lot more teaching to the tests.</p><blockquote><p> Second, we provide descriptive analysis of the trends in state graduation rates by whether states have graduation exams (or experienced changes in graduation exam policies during the panel period). If the rise in graduation rates was entirely due to strategic behavior, we would expect that the states without graduation exams experienced larger increases in graduation rates. But we see the opposite, suggesting that the upward trend in high school graduation is not because schools lowered their academic standards to make graduation easier.</p></blockquote><p> I see the theory here, that tests are the hardest thing to cheat. Except that when the tests are what is gating graduation, it seems plausible schools can find ways to pass those tests without building human capital, or even by sacrificing it. Worst case, state can respond to pressure by issuing a weaker test, or teaching directly to it. One can also see this as, places with gating tests had slack in the form of students who could plausibly graduate otherwise, if only some right answers can be made to appear in the right places.</p><p> It is also very easy to see how NCLB can harm human capital development. If you are focusing on children not failing, and on them passing tests, you are going to invest less in building their actually valuable human capital. You are going to alienate your best students, waste their time, get them out of good habits and teach them the wrong lessons.</p><p> So it&#39;s hard to presume that all of this largely lines up with human capital. It lines up with the capital of saying you graduated, but to what extent is that an absolute good versus a positional good? Similarly, one could presume that NCLB need not be all that causal here, as the economic cost of non-graduation has been rising, which also should lead to higher graduation rates, and also schools being more hesitant to fail a student since it would ruin their lives more.</p><p> In conclusion, I am not convinced here.</p><p> Then there are the schools where no children are left behind, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Austen/status/1704698874697486692">because no child is going anywhere at all.</a></p><blockquote><p> Fox Baltimore: The Maryland State Department of Education&#39;s 2022 state test results report Baltimore City&#39;s math scores were the lowest in Maryland. Just 7 percent of third through eighth graders testing proficient in math, meaning 93 percent do not read at grade level.</p><p> ……</p><p> In 23 Baltimore City schools, there were zero students who tested proficient in math. Not a single student.</p></blockquote><h4> School Reinvented</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/education/interactive/2023/homeschooling-microschools-pods-esa-vouchers/?itid=hp-more-top-stories_p004_f002">The latest trend in home schooling is… school?</a> They&#39;ve reinvented a school? It sure sounds like they have. You take a few kids, you hire a &#39;guide&#39; to help them and work through learning exercises and enrichment activities while the parents work. Almost as if education were a product, and you could form a market for it, and provide it vastly better (via vastly smaller student-teacher ratios, and being in a nice home rather than in a dystopian hellhole building, and customizing the content, and so on) and cheaper.</p><blockquote><p> Families pay Prenda $2,199 per year, plus additional fees set by the guides, which can range from $2,800 to $8,000, Smith said.</p></blockquote><p> For comparison, the average public school student costs the state roughly $13k/year. State funding for these micro schools seems much lower than that.</p><p> Another data point is that NYC schools <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Duderichy/status/1705345080209355161">have been “defunded” to the tune of $38k per student</a> . I realize that space is not free exactly and there is a lot of paperwork, and costs in NYC are higher, but one has to notice this is utterly absurd.</p><p> Even at $13k, one has to wonder about the &#39;get a few kids and hire a teacher&#39; option.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1706757195864367422">Matt Yglesias says it is wild American schools get so many tax breaks</a> . The obvious response is to point to the full public funding of the public schools and the need to compete with them. You pay your property taxes either way. It does seem wild if and when they get vouchers similar to the amount public schools are funded and then also keep a lot of tax breaks on top of that.</p><p> Whereas <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1706757195864367422">Labour is saying in the UK they will add a 20% VAT to private school fees</a> via removing their exemption, which they then say they will use to &#39;raise educational standards&#39; since money is not fungible.</p><p> Did you know that letting kids learn what they are curious about helps them learn?</p><blockquote><p> She picks and chooses topics for study based on student interests, not a set of state standards.</p><p> She pointed to one of her students who wants to be a judge. “She wants to learn about the Constitution and government. So why should I say, &#39;No, you should learn about ancient Egypt.&#39;”</p></blockquote><p> The two obvious concerns are socialization and situational tail risk. For socialization, I would continue to make the case that most socialization in schools is not the kind you want, and that a few close friends from a micro school or otherwise is vastly superior, and you can find friends in much better and cheaper ways and situations. The real issue is that while most micro school situations with attentive parents are going to go quite well, some parents are not so attentive or caring, and some children could end up in bad spots in ways that are highly blameworthy, as opposed to it happening in a public school where if it happens everyone followed procedure, and admittedly things could go farther south this way.</p><p> Presumably the solution for that is some form of periodic check-in, a test if you will, to ensure that things are going all right. If you are doing very well, warping things to pass the test will be unnecessary, provided it is not too particular (eg the student can demonstrate mastery of the Constitution or Egypt, and either counts for history).</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.richardhanania.com/p/the-old-school-reformers-case-for?utm_source=post-email-title&amp;publication_id=98102&amp;post_id=116966416&amp;isFreemail=true&amp;utm_medium=email">Richard Hanania makes &#39;The Old School Reformer&#39;s Case for Privatizing Education.&#39;</a> It is the standard set of true observations about what schools are and what it means to force children to spend thousands and thousands of hours in the place the government decides, when they decide it, doing what the government decides, without the right to go to the bathroom without asking first. And that public schools are a pretty non-optimal set of answers to those questions, so perhaps we should let families decide what is best for their children. I mostly don&#39;t disagree yet found it inessential.</p><p> Everyone tells me the lives of kids must be structured around having them &#39;socialize&#39; with others exactly their age, a &#39;peer group.&#39; <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/krishnanrohit/status/1663296837455888385">I agree with Rohit that this is dumb</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Rohit: One of my more controversial hypotheses on education is that having kids primarily be surrounded by other kids, especially of the same age, is bad actually, both for educational and socialising purposes</p><p> Mat Bateman (Quoting Montessori): “The education of today is humiliating. It produces an inferiority complex and artificially lowers the powers of man. Its very organization sets a limit to knowledge well below the natural level. It supplies men with crutches when they could run on swift feet.”</p></blockquote><h4> School Choice</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.vox.com/politics/23689496/school-choice-education-savings-accounts-american-federation-children">School choice is on the march</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Andrew Prokop at Vox: Very suddenly, that has changed. It started with West Virginia in 2021 and Arizona in 2022, and then continued with a flood this year — Iowa, Utah, Arkansas, Florida, Oklahoma, Ohio, and Indiana. More may follow. “It&#39;s happening!” Corey DeAngelis, a conservative activist who describes himself as a “school choice evangelist,” regularly tweets, joyfully chronicling each new victory.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/DeAngelisCorey/status/1660736473988050947">Governor of North Carolina declares state of emergency</a> because school vouchers are about to come online, and he wants to raise awareness. That is quite the mockery of the term &#39;state of emergency.&#39; On so many levels.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w31553#fromrss">A new NBER working paper</a> by Christopher Campos and Caitlin Kearns finds that LA&#39;s zones of school choice, where families could choose where to send their kids, resulted in marked improvements in educational outcomes versus areas outside such zones. Some form of competition and choice between schools seems clearly necessary if you want good outcomes. In sufficiently wealthy places you can get that competitive effect in other ways, in less well-off places you need families to be able to choose.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.thefp.com/p/three-biggest-myths-of-american-public-schools">Magnet schools mostly aren&#39;t real</a> . They don&#39;t use objective tests. Instead, the principal mostly decides who gets in and mostly that means whoever is local. Then they sit back and collect the extra funding. Whereas the few real magnet schools, the ones that use real tests and provide differentiated high-quality experiences like Stuyvesant High School in New York and Thomas Jefferson in Virginia, are largely in the process of being dismantled so preferred groups can be preferred.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1706730741437284603">Here are some survey results on homeschooling</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Matt Bateman: Only 34% of homeschooling parents are motivated by religious instruction, but 68% are motivated by moral instruction.</p><p> Mason: – majority concerned with violence, bullying, academics, and moral (but not religious) instruction</p><p> – only slightly more religious than non-homeschoolers</p><p> – more likely to identify as independent, less likely as D (R about the same)</p></blockquote><p> I would caution that providing religious instruction is distinct from shielding a child from outside influences, so perhaps that number is too low, or is better expressed as &#39;moral instruction&#39; that is largely about religion. Also noteworthy is that parents robustly say there is too much school focus on gender identity, 31-16 among those with kids in school and 53-16 among home schoolers.</p><h4> School Hidden</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/RyanRadia/status/1651379732288614406">Heritage Foundation proposes banning considering college degrees in not only public hiring, but also private hiring</a> , including any algorithmic screenings. This fits the pattern of our hiring laws where we tell people to ignore Bayes&#39; Rule and not care about their own preferences, because we don&#39;t like the implications, and we think that if we tell people to disregard Bayes&#39; Rule and their own preferences then they will go away.</p><p> Except, they don&#39;t go away. Which means everyone who ever hires anyone is breaking employment law constantly. It&#39;s not like you can look at resumes, or talk to people, and avoid learning who has a college degree.</p><p> You can try toban algorithms from considering college or various other things, and perhaps with some bespoke work you could even kind of do it, which would then mean you&#39;d want humans in the loop to fix that, I guess, if you did in fact care about such things in either direction. It&#39;s hard not to do that when everyone else is doing it, various signaling game dynamics, and so on.</p><p> What you can partially do is ban using college degrees as a requirement, so that anyone with statistically observable size has to give those without one a chance. However this risks making things even worse for those without degrees when such discrimination can go undetected, because they will now have no sign of where they can and cannot usefully apply. Then again, right now the requirements at such places are often only suggestions, so it is not obvious much would change.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/RyanRadia/status/1651379732288614406">Ryan Radia, ultimate reply guy</a> , notices that one of those requiring college degrees would be the Heritage Foundation. Except that&#39;s exactly the point. If you have the option to use college degrees as a filter, it is in your interest in such situations to use it, which helps you at the expense of forcing lots of people to waste years of their lives. It&#39;s the opposite of a gotcha.</p><h4> School Evaluation Hard</h4><p> I intended for this section to be longer: <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.mathematica.org/publications/long-term-impacts-of-kipp-middle-and-high-schools-on-college-enrollment-persistence-and-attainment">New study of 2k children</a> allocated via lottery to attend or not attend one of 280 charter schools shows <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/JohnArnoldFndtn/status/1701645859291558214">dramatic long term impact from KIPP (Knowledge is Power Program) charter schools</a> if and only if the kids stay from middle through high school.</p><p> I did some back and forth exchanges with the author of the paper, attempting to reconcile the claims that KIPP was effective with statistics that said that giving students access to KIPP middle schools did not make them substantially more likely to graduate from college, which seems like the best endpoint measured here. I haven&#39;t had time to get sufficient confidence in my understanding here, so I&#39;m pushing that for later, while asking if any of you have a reading here.</p><h4> A Metaphor</h4><p> There has been a bunch of recent discussion of the concept of Two-Parent Privilege, as described in the book of that name by Melissa Kearney. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.ft.com/content/14b0873e-c7cf-4927-aebe-71d562645bd4">Here is a Financial Times piece on the book</a> . A common response is to claim that everyone agrees that two married parents are better than the alternatives, and two parents of any kind are better than one, of course we (or the elites or liberal elites) know this and profess it. Yet we do not often say this, or emphasize it, or put force behind the message.</p><blockquote><p> Matthew Yglesias: One of the weirdest sentiments I read on here is the idea that the “elites” won&#39;t tell you about the value of marriage, physical fitness, friendship, healthy eating, etc — look up the stats and it&#39;s college grads doing way better on all those measures.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robkhenderson/status/1701250176931725552">Rob Henderson</a> : Scenario: Rich right-wing anchors say getting a vaccine is just as good as not getting one, implies vaccines might be harmful, promotes broad skepticism about them. And then personally ensures they and their families are vaccinated.</p><p> Very smart cultural critic: Why are people saying rich right-wing anchors won&#39;t tell you about the value of vaccines? Look it up, they&#39;re all vaccinated.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/09/the-shaming-of-one-parent-families.html">Tyler Cowen views this in terms of shame</a> . We used to shame one-parent families, and also some other things such as suicide. Now we instead shame other things.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/BradWilcoxIFS/status/1702138878507811011">Brad Wilcox challenges that this is merely about failure to be loud or to shame</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Brad Wilcox: Plenty of folks, including @mattyglesias, have asked: Where is the evidence that left-leaning elites don&#39;t support marriage?</p><p> Here is some polling evidence from the American Family Survey (2022).</p><p> “while 91 percent of college-educated conservatives agree that “children are better off if they have married parents,” only 30 percent of college-educated liberals agree, according to a report to be released next week by @FamStudies.</p></blockquote><p> Children are better off if they have married parents. That does not mean that every child&#39;s parents should get or remain married. It does not mean that you should not have children in other circumstances.</p><p> What it does mean is: Children are better off if they have married parents. If you fail to agree with this, presumably it is because you do not care for the implications.</p><p> I would also add: Children are better off being raised by two parents than being raised by one parent, even if marriage is not strictly involved.</p><p> One problem is that those who would traditionally ever be willing to apply any pressure to anyone can&#39;t <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1703525334472085918">keep their eye on the ball</a> , instead worrying more about the genders of everyone involved. Those in the red faction really, really do not want gay or lesbian or unmarried couples having children.</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F62c7c42d-931c-4296-8386-ad853541befd_840x1196.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/xpydosgmjoqy5oc5xnx2" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> The sleeper thing to notice is that only 76% of conservatives think it is acceptable for a married couple to decide not to have children.</p><p> The weirdest one of all is an unmarried man and woman raising a child only get 58% approval, versus 70% for a single parent. Presumably this is because the unmarried couple could choose to get married whereas the single parent cannot not have a kid. It still seems like this is actively going to point incentives in the wrong direction, when most of the approval benefit of getting married is also available if the father leaves.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://mattbruenig.com/2023/09/30/response-to-douthat-on-two-parent-families/">Matt Bruenig responds</a> (directly to Ross Douthat, but mostly to the broader claim) with the counterargument that we are asking the wrong question:</p><blockquote><p> Matt Bruenig: I responded to this argument by rehashing what I take to be the common view on this topic, which is that parent cohabitation is sometimes good and sometimes bad, depending on the characteristics of each parent and how those parents get along. Based on this view, the relevant inquiry is how many of the 22 percent of kids who live in single-parent households would actually be better off if <strong><em>their specific parents</em></strong> lived together.</p><p> ……</p><ol><li> One of the parents may be dead, in prison, or living remotely for job reasons. This is not a huge slice of people, but it probably does shave a couple of percentage points off the total.</li><li> Dad might be a bad guy.</li><li> Mom might be a bad lady.</li><li> Dad and mom might be alright but don&#39;t mix well.</li></ol></blockquote><p> That is the question of what to do about a particular child, in isolation, already faced with a non-ideal situation. And yes, sometimes given who the parents are, their circumstances or their relationship to each other, it will sometimes be impossible or unwise to retroactively &#39;fix&#39; the situation in this way. The best time to intervene and change the situation is before it gets to that point, including on a broader scale. The second best time will in a particular case sometimes be right now, sometimes not.</p><p> Matt then makes the claim that since upper class people marry upper class people but mostly don&#39;t marry lower class people, they are only providing evidence that marriage is good when you marry someone upper class. There is certainly a coherent position that says something like &#39;if you have a good enough situation lock it down, otherwise don&#39;t until you get one.&#39; I would argue that if anything this throws shade on arguments of the form &#39;lower class people should be able to get the message from the actions upper class people take.&#39; Instead, they often take to heart that they need similarly secure circumstances first, which they rarely will get. So all the more reason one must say the full arguments out loud.</p><p> This all follows the common pattern where we used to get good thing X via method Y, then we realized (usually correctly) that Y is terrible and stopped doing Y (or we got it via mechanism Z that went away or changed for other reasons), except now we are getting steadily less X and we don&#39;t have a solution. We need more X, so we need alternative methods for getting more X.</p><p> The most obvious X is fertility, which makes this particular situation even trickier.</p><p> The obvious thing to do is some combination of financial support for X or some alternative mechanism Z that causes X, or financial punishment for ~X or ~Z, or supporting helpful norms and other cultural features. In general, people say &#39;it is impossible to get more X&#39; or &#39;X is outdated&#39; or &#39;we cannot afford X&#39; or some such, before trying much.</p><p> More than that, they refuse to say X is good, or that we need more X, because they associate that with support of nasty, no-good method Y or outdated mechanism Z, or otherwise the use of force or shame or pressure. We are against shame, but we also don&#39;t see any way to offer praise or honor for X without considering that shame of ~X.</p><p> Meanwhile, more and more forms of punishment are being considered Ys.</p><p> Every parent knows this dilemma well.</p><p> We need some knob, somewhere, that we can turn to reward the good and discourage the bad. What to do?</p><h4> Lies</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robinhanson/status/1648789845701976064">Liars, liars, pants on fires.</a></p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fcd9ea6ca-b4c1-45f4-9208-57d705923304_907x963.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/gkme2dijqigetufg03lt" alt=""></a></figure><blockquote><p> Eucaliculia: This poll is likely biased by lots of parents only having kids who are &lt;10 years old. I can definitely tell when my 2 year old lies to me more reliably than I could a 16 year old.</p></blockquote><p> I am with Eucaliculia here. At first, children can&#39;t lie without giving the game away. Then, slowly, they skill up, until finally they can mostly lie with impunity absent evidence, and they get good at knowing when their story can get double checked. By the end, I was <em>very</em> confident that most of my lies were getting through, and was willing to rather aggressively lie to my parents despite a strict honesty policy for everyone else.</p><p> Whereas with my kids right now, they&#39;re young enough that I&#39;m very confident they almost never successfully fool me. I do expect that to change, but as we say to the God of Death: Not today.</p><p> I do, however, think that parents likely systematically overestimate how often they can detect kids&#39; lies, and kids overestimate how often they can get away undetected, because parents don&#39;t always tell you that they know you&#39;re lying.</p><p> Rick from Baltimore asks Tyler Cowen, given he does believe in the value of two-parent families, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/09/from-my-email-on-single-parent-families.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=from-my-email-on-single-parent-families">what would his pro-parent plan look like?</a></p><p> Rick&#39;s suggestions mostly involve a variety of proposed cultural shifts towards favoring marriages by moving back towards some older cultural norms, including better tax incentives and perhaps job programs and otherwise helping create more eligible men. Tyler responds that he does not know what would work, but that it could not hurt to indeed get buy-in that this problem really matters and is not a hopeless one, and asks who is on board.</p><p> I am definitely on board. I also notice this kicks the can down the road and dodges the question, and that Tyler would point this out in other contexts. If you want to get buy-in for the importance and tractability of X, you need to help move towards or at least affirm some method Y of getting more X, or it&#39;s all talk and also people won&#39;t know what they are getting behind.</p><p> The answer necessarily involves a combination of financial incentives, lifestyle changes, cultural and norm shifts and attributions of status and honor. Which is dodging the question again, although less so. Concretely, where should we start?</p><p> I would say there are three distinct fronts here – pro-fertility pro-child actions in general, direct pro-marriage incentives and cultural factors.</p><p> We should do the pro-fertility and pro-child actions anyway. Doing this has other benefits that justify doing so, it would make marriage and raising a family more attractive and help move the needle here as well. So much higher subsidies for those who have children, and even more than that get rid of the various albatrosses we tie around parents&#39; necks, that are doubtless driving potential fathers away.</p><p> We can and should combine that by tying some of those financial incentives to marriage, and ensuring that the tax code, including various virtual taxes (such as the taxes imposed by schools in the form of usually-discounted tuition) essentially never penalizes marriage.</p><p> The obvious way to start on this is to offer a universal option – couples can be given the option to file as individuals if filing jointly would be more expensive. And we should make it illegal to consider spousal income or wealth in need-based educational or other similar assessments. Yes, there are obvious concerns and details that need to be worked out there, and it won&#39;t be cheap, but the alternative is forcing people to choose.</p><p> Cultural shifts are harder to mandate. Financial incentives help, but culture also has a life of its own. That part is less my area. I would start with a bigger fight, where we have developed a norm that when a choice has superior outcomes, we are afraid to point this out and reward those who make that choice or say things that look down upon those who do not make that choice, even in relatively mild form. We are going to have to walk some of that back.</p><h4> Don&#39;t Worry, Be Happy</h4><p> Another kind of lie is that unhappy childhoods are good, actually. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1703108053913002219">They&#39;re not.</a></p><blockquote><p> Paul Graham: It&#39;s bullshit that you have to have an unhappy childhood to do great things. You *can* do great things despite having an unhappy childhood, and that misleads people into thinking that it has a positive benefit.</p><p> I want my kids to do great things, and I&#39;m not trying to give them unhappy childhoods so that they can. Exactly the opposite. I know from talking to thousands of YC founders that the best way to make people ambitious is to encourage them.</p><p> It&#39;s certainly a powerful motivation to want to prove people wrong. But if you&#39;re at all independent-minded, you&#39;ll encounter enough resistance to give you plenty of this motivation whether your childhood was unhappy or not.&#39;</p><p> Yheushen.eth: @WalterIsaacson has a slightly different opinion on this.</p><p> Paul Graham: That was what made me write this. It&#39;s not just bullshit, but very dangerous bullshit, because it will allow abusive parents to rationalize and thus continue doing the bad things they&#39;re doing to their kids.</p></blockquote><p> There is indeed a failure mode where you prioritize your child&#39;s present happiness so much that you do not prepare them for the future. What is good for them will not always be what makes them happy. So sometimes you shouldn&#39;t do what makes your kid most happy. Tradeoffs are a thing. That is very different from happiness being an active detriment to ambition or success.</p><h4> You Might Learn Something</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://economistwritingeveryday.com/2023/05/27/the-value-of-student-organizations-and-on-campus-education-anecdotal-evidence-from-tim-keller/">Argument that on-campus education is valuable</a> because being a club officer position is valuable, and generally thousands of students get to &#39;practice working&#39; together, giving practical leadership and other experience in a low-stakes environment. That&#39;s not an argument for education. That&#39;s an argument for work. For doing real things. It&#39;s also saying that on-campus education right now is <em>less fake</em> than online-only education, because the things students do among themselves are real while the core educational experience is fake. Got it.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/RomeoStevens76/status/1656846941337305088">An all too common form of RLHF</a> :</p><blockquote><p> Romeo Stevens: Hypothesis: people with inaction bias were &#39;Copenhagen punished&#39; as children ie they were punished under the Copenhagen interpretation of ethics whereby they were held accountable if they did something poorly instead of rewarded for trying something at all.</p></blockquote><p> This is standard procedure. Constantly, as children and as adults, we are taught that if something is going to go badly, we should avoid interacting with it. If we are going to mess something up, better to not try, we will only get blamed. Parents who understand this problem will go to extraordinary lengths to do the opposite.</p><h4> Restorative Justice Does Not Scale</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/ArmandDoma/status/1685536579803115520">What is up with schools and restorative justice?</a></p><blockquote><p> Armand Domalewski: A recurring pattern I have noticed in education is that it seems particularly prone to fads. New ideas that show initial promise become rapidly adopted at scale without a lot of <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://hechingerreport.org/the-promise-of-restorative-justice-starts-to-falter-under-rigorous-research/">rigorous evaluation</a> or evidence of success.</p><p> Pittsburgh study found that academic performance actually got worse at schools that tried restorative justice, with math test scores for Black students being the hardest hit. But it&#39;s unclear if this is because of bad policy or bad implementation.</p><p> Hechinger Report: In surveys, teachers at the schools that tried restorative justice said that their school climate improved. But students reported that teachers struggled more to manage classroom behavior. I wondered if disruptive behavior in the classroom might have detracted from learning time, or perhaps even worthwhile and productive restorative justice conversations ate away at precious instructional minutes. Either way, it could potentially explain why some kids&#39; performance suffered.</p><p> The <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10964-019-01013-2">Maine study</a> , published online in March 2019 by the Journal of Youth and Adolescence, found no difference in school climate between middle schools that tried restorative justice and those that didn&#39;t. It didn&#39;t look at suspension rates or academic outcomes. But the fact that bullying and other school climate measures didn&#39;t budge is another sign that restorative justice programs aren&#39;t a slam dunk solution to addressing student misbehavior.</p><p> ……</p><p> “Conceptually and theoretically, restorative practices should work,” said Francis Huang, an associate professor at the University of Missouri&#39;s College of Education who is conducting another study of restorative justice in schools in Brooklyn. “But it&#39;s harder.”</p><p> ……</p><p> One bright side for restorative justice was that the more that Maine students reported that they personally experienced elements of restorative justice, such as discussing problems in circles, the more that student felt connected to his or her peers and the less cyber-bullying he or she experienced.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.rand.org/pubs/research_reports/RR2840.html">Rand report</a> key findings:</p><ul><li> Implementation of restorative practices through PERC improved overall school climates, as rated by teachers.</li><li> Implementation of restorative practices reduced the average suspension rate: During the study period, average suspension rates decreased in both PERC and non-PERC schools, but rates decreased more in PERC schools.</li><li> Suspension rates of African American students and of those from low-income families also went down in PERC schools, shrinking the disparities in suspension rates between African American and white students and between low- and higher-income students.</li><li> Academic outcomes did not improve in PERC schools, and actually worsened for grades 6–8.</li><li> Arrest rates among PERC schools did not decrease.</li></ul></blockquote><p> The core problem with restorative justice is that it is not justice.</p><p> That is not a claim that it is a bad thing. Most useful policies are not justice.</p><p> Instead, it is a claim that:</p><ol><li> This is poorly named. This should be called conflict mediation or something.</li><li> This aims to address root causes of individual conflicts, which can be great.</li><li> But which is not incentive compatible with preventing future conflicts.</li><li> Nor does it provide an actual sense of individual justice.</li><li> Thus, it needs careful implementation and a mixed strategy, or will backfire.</li></ol><p> If you have a system that is mostly working well, where people are mostly cooperating, then such initiatives have the necessary groundwork and can succeed. If you do not have that, then you are giving the green light to bad actors and such policies seem doomed unless you also fix the other problems. Thus it is an especially strong candidate for working in a pilot program and then failing when scaled up.</p><h4> Other Things In Brief</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/oscredwin/status/1673475939227901953">Studies keep showing sugar does not cause hyperactivity in children</a> .</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/the-wv-canary-in-the-coal-mine.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-wv-canary-in-the-coal-mine">West Virginia University cuts 7% of faculty and 9% of its majors</a> , including moving its foreign language instruction online. The reduction reflects a larger reduction in enrollment. It also seems like they made highly reasonable cuts, to the extent one cannot trim the administrative staff instead.</p><p> Daycare is often thought to be an inadequate substitute for individualized (maternal or otherwise) child care. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/wesyang/status/1690708622949367809">The results from Quebec&#39;s universal daycare, including for infants under the age of 1, do not seem great</a> . I look at what went into our children, especially at young ages, and even if you discard all other considerations I have no idea how to duplicate anything like it at a 5-to-1 caregiver ratio. Someone needs to give direct attention to that kid more than 20% of the time.算一算。 The efficiency gains available are limited. There are also huge issues with continuity of care, which definitely matters.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1707123181205815365">Most homework is truly evil</a> . It is work justified in the name of training children that their time is not their own and they will later be forced to do endless piles of pointless busywork, so they&#39;d better do pointless busywork now.</p><blockquote><p> Katharine Birbalsingh: Out of 6.5 hours, you can&#39;t find the time for an hour&#39;s homework?</p><p> Mike Solana: before middle school, homework serves no purpose but to traumatize children. do your job and teach them in the classroom. when they&#39;re home, let them play.</p><p> Mason: A really sad trend I&#39;ve noticed is parents who appreciate homework because it gives them a prescribed, unambiguous way to be an “involved” parent and because they don&#39;t respect the ways their children choose to use their time when they&#39;re not forced.</p></blockquote><p> Imagine if I said the same thing to a worker, you have 6.5 hours at home and you can&#39;t find time for this hour of extra paperwork that we don&#39;t even use? People somehow don&#39;t think children&#39;s time has value if it isn&#39;t being used on school. Let your children play.</p><p> I would go so far as to say that it&#39;s fine to ask children to do some amount of homework-style work, but if it&#39;s so valuable then set aside school time for that. When the work is done, the work is done.</p><h4> The Lighter Side</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/patio11/status/1702084458185167165">At least someone&#39;s password is not so easy to guess.</a></p><p> Patrick McKenzie: Lillian is having trouble playing Guess the Password in math class because the material assumes the kids can&#39;t do the math, and because she hasn&#39;t yet learned how to play Guess the Password with an American teacher.</p><p> Humorous example:</p><blockquote><p> Diego&#39;s homework had a page torn off. He was trying to add 243 and 100. The two remaining digits were 54. How can his teacher know he is incorrect without seeing the digit in the hundreds place?</p><p> Justify your answer. This was in a lesson about odd plus even equals odd, etc.</p><p> The answer the question “wants” is “Because an odd number plus an even number is an odd number, an even answer is always wrong.”</p><p> The answer Lillian wanted to give: “She can add, because she is a teacher.”</p><p> Me: Let&#39;s pretend she can&#39;t do that in her head.</p><p> Lillian: ARE YOU JOKING?</p></blockquote><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/childhood-roundup-3#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/childhood-roundup-3<guid ispermalink="false"> M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Zvi]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 14:30:09 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[My simple model for Alignment vs Capability]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 12:07 PM GMT<br/><br/><p>我有一个关于一致性与能力问题的简单模型。我之所以把它写下来，是因为在仔细阅读了迈克尔·尼尔森 (Michael Nielson) 关于<a href="https://michaelnotebook.com/xrisk/index.html">人工智能存在风险的</a>帖子后，我认为它很棒，但对这种对齐困境的想法并不满意。我不是唯一有<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/8Q7JwFyC8hqYYmCkC/link-post-michael-nielsen-s-notes-on-existential-risk-from?commentId=uuqrjTaf5dZ6HtTmy">这种感觉</a>的人，但我也无法找到任何令人满意的资料来描述这种情况（紧张？二分法？权衡？）。对我来说，尼尔森困境的真正问题在于它是用加速主义来表达的，加速主义是单拨号主义的一种形式，而<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Zzar6BWML555xSt6Z/the-dial-of-progress">单拨号主义是错误的</a>。</p><p>我注意到这里实际上并没有什么新的东西；我很确定这些考虑因素在 MIRI 刚开始时就已经涵盖了，而且还有更多。然而，我们当时并没有就一致性与能力进行讨论，能力也不是那么紧迫的问题，而且无论我们之前说过什么<i>，</i>人们<i>现在</i>都不会在公开场合谈论模型。这是一个简单的模型。</p><p><strong>背景</strong></p><p>我理解一致性与能力问题的方式是，能力研究最终会以 AGI 的形式兑现，而一致性研究会以一致的 AGI 的形式兑现，因此在这种情况下，一致性研究实际上是能力研究的一个子集。我预计这或多或少会持续适用，但能力不断增强但不是通用人工智能的地方仍然需要协调一致。</p><p>我想通过该模型实现的目标是让我们可以用来对研究做出启发式判断：特别是诸如是否支持、资助或追求研究，以及如何在不同的研究议程之间进行比较之类的事情。这<i>并不是</i>为了直接预测时间线、整体人工智能研究进程或特定研究组织的未来。</p><p><strong>拒绝加速</strong></p><p>我对用加速的方式思考和说话的主要反对意见是，它在因果上是无用的。我将 GDP 类比为一种经济指标：如果某个特定行业增长非常快，我们希望该行业取得成功，同时也希望避免灾难性的工业事故，那么一个代表一大堆所有活动的标量就不会增加任何东西。我们不能通过说“但GDP应该增长<i>得更少”来建设更安全的工业设施。</i>与投资者和监管机构交谈也是如此。加速纯粹是一种修辞手段，这就是为什么我们看到它出现在公共对话中应该不足为奇，也是为什么我们应该谨慎对待它。</p><p><strong>思考成功之路</strong></p><p>我更喜欢从成功路径的角度来思考，即通过相空间的路径的意义上（但不是严格的定义）。在这里，我们正在考虑穿过世界相空间的路径，特别是那些通向 AGI 和对齐 AGI 的较小子空间的路径。此外，我们只是考虑研究，而不是考虑组织、研究人员数量、资金等。</p><p>我经常想起 ET Jaynes 的论文<a href="https://bayes.wustl.edu/etj/articles/macroscopic.prediction.pdf">《宏观预测》</a> ，特别是这一点：</p><blockquote><p>因此，吉布斯的变分原理在原理上是如此简单，以至于人们几乎会犹豫是否要说出这样一个琐碎的事情。它说“预测大自然可以以最多的方式实现的最终状态，同时与你的宏观信息一致。”</p></blockquote><p>在我们的背景下，完成​​某件事的途径越多，它就越有可能实现。</p><p>那么我们如何计算路径呢？</p><p><strong>计算路径</strong></p><p>我们想要确定研究中可行的部分。就我们的目的而言，“引导未来的研究”和“适用于真实系统”都被视为可操作的。我直接考虑汉明<a href="https://gwern.net/doc/science/1986-hamming#problems-with-attacks">重要研究问题标准</a>意义上的攻击角度，汉明所说的是“在问题上取得进展的一种方法”。</p><p>汉明所说的攻击角度是我认为对齐研究议程产生的：在对齐问题上取得进展的方法（对于主要人工智能实验室来说也是如此：在能力问题上取得进展的方法）。机械可解释性是一个研究议程。假设他们发现了一种被称为<i>“schlokking”</i>的新行为。</p><p>示例 1：另一篇论文详细阐述了<i>schlokking</i>行为。这算作一条道路，因为它通向未来的研究。</p><p>示例 2：另一篇论文报告根据<i>schlokking</i>行为成功预测了 LLM 的输出。这算作一条路径，因为它已应用于实际系统。</p><p>示例 3：在 1 或 2 之前，研究人员有了一个想法并研究了一些权重。他们心里想：“我很确定我发现了一些奇怪的东西。为什么它看起来这么<i>破烂</i>？”这本身并<i>不算</i>一条路，因为它还没有去任何地方。</p><p>这给了我们一个简单的<strong>路径启发</strong>：足够好的东西可以得到一个名字，后来的研究引用或应用于真实的系统。</p><p><strong>双重用途会计</strong></p><p>相同的规则适用于能力路径，并且我们以相同的方式对能力侧的路径进行计数。继续<i>schlokking</i> ：</p><p>示例 4：一篇论文解释了他们如何优化训练程序以利用<i>schlokking</i>行为来减少训练时间。这被视为应用于实际系统的能力路径。</p><p>示例 5：一篇论文解释了<i>schlokking</i><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VcVfceTsD0A&amp;t=2220s">实际上是相当次优的</a>，通过深思熟虑的设计，他们可以更快地获得相同的行为。这被视为一条能力路径，通向未来的研究。</p><p><strong>考虑比率</strong></p><p>由于每个议程都可能产生对齐和能力的路径，因此我们可以查看对齐路径与能力路径的比率，我将其简单地标记为<strong>路径比率</strong>。</p><p>示例 6：在前面的示例中，我们计算了两个对齐路径，以及两个功能路径。因此，对齐：能力的<strong>路径比</strong>为2：2，或者简化为1：1。</p><p>在计算路径和查看路径比率之间，我们有几种方法对研究输出进行排序：</p><ul><li>匹配比最高：能力风险最低</li><li>生成的对齐路径数量最多是最有生产力的（对于能力也是如此）</li><li>总路径数最多的可能是最有洞察力的</li><li>Etc.</li></ul><p>此时我们可以实际使用模型来解决一致性与能力问题。直观的答案自然是支持风险最低的研究，也就是说对齐：能力的最高路径比率；如果我正确地阅读了公众对话，这甚至会延伸到<i>放弃</i>任何增加任何能力路径的研究议程，也就是说，对于某些人来说，对齐：能力路径比率必须是无限的。我认为这是错误的。</p><p><strong>总数和阈值</strong></p><p>我认为基于此模型，反对添加功能路径的强势立场是错误的，原因有两个。</p><p>第一个原因是，我认为我们应该关心有多少种方法可以在一致性方面取得进展，而不是在总体能力方面取得进展。在模型中，这是迄今为止已完成的所有研究的路径<strong>总比率</strong>。这是一种比较衡量标准，与当前优势能力的大小成正比。虽然这可以通过足够广泛的文献综述来完全定量，但我缺乏广泛的文献基础，因此我一直使用肠道水平的费米估计。</p><p>示例 7：阵营与能力之比为 1:1 表明进度大致相等，这显然很荒谬。所以真正的问题是我们是否看起来更像：</p><ul><li> 1:10，也就是说能力有10倍的优势。</li><li> 1：100，也就是说能力有100倍的优势。</li><li> 1：1000，也就是说能力有1000倍的优势。</li></ul><p>其中，1:100对我来说感觉最合适。话虽这么说，我将依靠 1:10 的乐观估计的简单性来举例。</p><p>第二个原因是，从绝对意义上来说，我们通过协调取得成功的途径非常少。在普通情况下，如果路径比对齐：能力为0，也就是说根本不存在可行的对齐路径，那么我们就注定要失败，除非我们一开始就对人工智能的风险完全错误。如果对齐路径的总数仍然很小，那么我们是否注定要失败的问题就简化为这几条路径是成功还是失败的问题，这就是模型内的说法，我们仍然需要更多的对齐研究。</p><p>这两件事相互作用，让我们看看“我应该进行对齐研究吗？”这样的问题。或“我应该将我的想法纳入研究议程吗？”。如果对齐路径的总数为零或非常小，那么答案显然是肯定<i>的</i>，因为否则就没有希望，能力就该死。如果对齐路径的总数足够高，以至于我们关心控制风险，那么我声称<i>“是”</i><strong>的启发式阈值</strong>是它是否使<strong>总比率</strong>更好。</p><p>示例 8：如果您的总比率为 1:10，那么如果您确信自己不会<i>意外</i>地生成超过<i>10 倍</i>的能力路径作为对齐路径，那么您的答案应该是“是”。如果您的研究议程最终得到的路径比率是 1:9，那仍然是净收益。</p><p>我注意到，对于那些担心增强能力的人来说，这是<i>极其</i>宽容的。我还没有看到任何关于调整方法的提案，我认为它可以提供 10 倍以上的方法来帮助能力。就目前情况而言，我的模型并没有预测对齐研究不会意外地导致 AGI，而是预测它几乎总是值得冒险。</p><p><strong>改进</strong></p><p>这个模型简单到残酷。我可以预见到一些担忧，其中大部分都可以得到解决。</p><ul><li><strong>不谈概率。</strong>这是经过深思熟虑的——需要有一种方法来回答“到底是<i>什么</i>的概率？”在目前关于能力与一致性的讨论中，似乎没有答案。这个模型甚至不是真正定量的；我实际上所做的就是使用一些数字来获得一些排名顺序。</li><li><strong>撇开概率不谈，并不能解决不确定性。</strong>在启动自己的议程之前，我主要考虑的是确定其他议程的结果，这应该是负责任的。话虽这么说，为了简单起见，我一直将不确定性视为路径比率中的一系列值，例如 [0-3]:[0-5] 或类似的值。可能结果的分布会更好，但除了猜测高斯之外，我没有足够的信息来判断这些结果会是什么样子。</li><li><strong>不谈时间。</strong>我认为时间是另一件事，需要一个模型来研究。我一直在考虑一个研究周期形式的时间单位，我觉得这个时间单位大约从研究议程合并到社区其他成员充分消化其成果并开始尝试使用它们的时间。这充其量仍然只是比较 - 例如，我认为出于各种原因，能力的研究周期比一致性的研究周期更快是一个合理的说法。以这种方式设想，实际上可以算作生成的能力路径数量的乘数（这与我通常看到的这种跟踪方式相反，其中每个研究路径都被视为一个小的速度乘数）。我怀疑真正的区别在于具体与理论之间，因为运行实验可以为您提供更多信息，而且似乎能力研究的很大一部分是具体的。但是，如果人们不以能力也可能受益为由而回避具体的一致性研究，那么这种情况会有多大变化呢？</li><li><strong>并非所有路径都是平等的 - 不谈论质量或影响</strong>。这主要是因为我对如何比较他们可能具有的品质知之甚少。将粒度增加一级的一种方法是再次使用比较措施；我们可以有一个路径<i>大小</i>，也就是说，常规路径值得一条路径，但特别好的路径可能值得两到三个常规路径，直到某些关键或范式定义的突破价值。与多重实现相比，我更喜欢大小实现，因为它感觉会影响传输。作为一个实际的例子，我们可能会认为两个主要人工智能实验室所选择的研究的路径大小是仅一个实验室所选择的另一路径的两倍。</li></ul><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/hmJHbSHnbfC4CZmh8/my-simple-model-for-alignment-vs-capability#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/hmJHbSHnbfC4CZmh8/my-simple-model-for-alignment-vs-capability<guid ispermalink="false"> hmJHbSHnbfC4CZmh8</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[ryan_b]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:07:42 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm a Former Israeli Officer. AMA]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 8:33 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>嘿大家！潜伏已久，第一次发海报。</p><p>我叫约维尔·罗姆。我是一名以色列数据科学家。我在以色列国防军的一个名为 Talpiot 的精英项目中服役，该项目包括物理本科生和广泛的军事教育（基本上是为技术人员提供的西点军校，但更多的是精英主义），然后担任数据科学家，并以上尉的身份完成了服役。我目前在家，因为我两年前完成了我的服务，他们现在不需要很多数据科学家。</p><p>有什么事就问我吧。我对最新情况的了解与没有正式职位的人一样（可能比您预期的要少）。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/zJCKn4TSXcCXzc6fi/i-m-a-former-israeli-officer-ama#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/zJCKn4TSXcCXzc6fi/ima-former-israeli-officer-ama<guid ispermalink="false"> zJCKn4TSXcCXzc6fi</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Yovel Rom]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 08:36:28 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Become a PIBBSS Research Affiliate]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 7:41 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> <i>TL;DR：</i> <a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/affiliate"><i><strong>PIBBSS 正在招聘研究附属人员！</strong></i></a> <i><strong>&nbsp;</strong></i></p><p> <i>PIBBSS 是一项研究计划，旨在促进利用自然系统和人工系统中智能行为之间的相似性开展工作，并利用这些见解来使人工智能系统安全、有益和一致。</i></p><p><i>我们希望为追求“PIBBSS 式”人工智能对齐研究的优秀研究人员提供量身定制的长期支持：全职工资、活跃的研究社区、运营支持等。最初承诺期限为 6 个月，有可能延长至 12 个月或更长。</i></p><p><i><strong>如需申请，请点击</strong></i><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScwMZBTMErBhuXNGNfY_dubgcV8FT3eqYOioxluV82v1V766Q/viewform?usp=sf_link"><i><strong><u>此处</u></strong></i></a><i><strong>。</strong>要被视为下一轮附属机构的一部分，请在<strong>11 月 5 日</strong>之前申请。</i></p><hr><p>在<a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/"><u>PIBBSS</u></a> （“生物和社会系统中智能行为的原理”），我们的使命是利用自然系统和人工系统中智能行为之间的相似之处，促进人工智能对齐研究。 （有关更多详细信息，请参阅下面的“关于 PIBBSS 和我们的研究重点”部分。）</p><p>自 PIBBSS 于 2022 年成立以来，我们已经开展了两次为期<a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/fellowship"><u>3 个月的研究奖学金</u></a>，以及<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/mqvxR9nrXAzRr3ow9/announcing-key-phenomena-in-ai-risk-facilitated-reading"><u>一个阅读小组</u></a>、<a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCMo5Ei9xLHbk9sqNMSH3mdQ"><u>一个持续的演讲者系列</u></a>以及一系列研究静修活动，探索符合 PIBBSS 研究兴趣的主题。我们的校友继续在 OpenAI、Anthropic、复杂系统对齐研究小组和学术界等机构以及通过独立资助进行人工智能对齐研究。</p><p>虽然我们继续对这些活动的价值感到兴奋，但我们也相信还有更多价值！特别是，我们看到了一项旨在<strong>支持与 PIBBSS 的研究赌注一致的长期、更持续的研究工作的</strong>计划的潜力。</p><p>因此，我们很高兴推出新的<a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/affiliate"><strong>PIBBSS 联盟计划</strong></a>。</p><h2><strong>联盟计划的目标和主要特点</strong></h2><p>我们运行该计划的核心<strong>目标</strong>是反事实地帮助就人工智能风险、协调和治理问题取得实质性、高质量和清晰的研究进展。该附属计划旨在通过以高度定制的方式支持有前途的个人研究人员来确定、发展和推进他们的个人研究议程，从而实现这一目标。</p><p>具体的<strong>成功场景</strong>可能看起来像（但不限于）附属机构发布有洞察力的研究成果；加入现有研究小组的努力或建立新的研究小组；识别、确定范围、测试并吸引新的或被忽视的研究途径；完善他们的个人研究议程并获得独立资金； ETC。</p><p> PIBBSS 联盟计划具有以下<strong>主要特点</strong>：</p><ul><li>附属公司的<strong>工资</strong>为 5,000 美元/月/FTE。我们愿意向优秀的候选人支付更高的薪水。<ul><li>默认情况下，我们正在寻找将全职加入该计划的附属机构。也就是说，我们愿意在适当的情况下适应附属公司的情况，例如以兼职方式加入该计划。我们还有能力为那些不想离开当前研究职位的人提供支持。</li></ul></li><li>附属机构受益于一系列旨在帮助他们专注于并推进研究工作的<strong>支持结构</strong>，例如：<ul><li><strong>季度研究静修</strong>会将附属机构以及其他联盟研究人员聚集在一起，形成我们的扩展网络</li><li><strong>个性化研究和战略支持</strong>，通常以每两周一次与您的负责人通话的形式（可以选择根据附属机构的需求和偏好调整支持频率）</li><li><strong>访问 PIBBSS 研究社区</strong>和扩展网络，包括加入我们的 Slack 空间、量身定制的介绍、参加研讨会的机会等。</li><li><strong>财务和行政支持</strong>，例如访问相关研究会议、访问基础模型并在研究需要时进行计算等。</li><li><strong>根据附属公司的需求/偏好使用办公空间。</strong></li><li>注意：该计划的一个关键特点是根据最能帮助我们的附属机构在研究方面取得进展的反事实因素，为他们提供高度定制的支持。因此，上述列表虽然具有代表性，但不一定完全准确或全面。</li></ul></li><li><strong>联属关系的初始期限为 6 个月</strong>，届时我们将审查联属关系是否可以<strong>延长至 12 个月</strong>。在特殊情况下，我们将提供 12 个月的初始报价。<ul><li>我们的愿景是，附属计划为有前途的研究人员提供一个严肃的长期家园，这些研究人员在 1 年或更长时间的时间尺度上从事 PIBBSS 式的人工智能对齐研究，包括永久职位的可能性。</li></ul></li><li>我们希望巩固并加强 PIBBSS 在过去两年中建立的<strong>支持性、好奇心和奉献精神的文化</strong>。我们关心良好的认知实践，同时探索理解复杂世界的复杂性，并特别强调<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/wi3upQibefMcFs5to/levels-of-pluralism"><u>认知多元化</u></a>在此过程中的价值。</li></ul><p><br>目前，我们以<strong>实验性的</strong>视角来看待联属网络营销计划 - 测试该计划可以提供重大价值的假设，并了解我们究竟如何才能最有效地支持我们的联属网络营销商。根据我们了解到的情况，我们可能会扩大或缩小规模，简化计划或使其更适合各个附属机构，旨在建立有时间限制或开放期限的附属机构，或者采取其他措施来增加影响力该程序。</p><h2><strong>联盟计划的要求</strong></h2><p>联盟计划是一个非常开放的计划，要求有限。以下是我们向附属公司提出的要求：</p><ul><li>提交反映您的研究进展和前瞻性研究计划的<strong>季度</strong><strong>报告</strong>。<ul><li>这些报告旨在通过提供问责结构并鼓励他们定期进行缩小和反思来帮助附属机构。它们还帮助我们了解附属机构一直在做什么，以及我们是否可以做些什么来支持他们更好地前进。</li></ul></li><li>参加我们的~季度<strong>研究静修活动</strong></li><li><strong>真诚致力于</strong>在人工智能安全、协调和治理相关问题上取得进展，并建设性地、求实地和善意地参与我们共同的认知文化</li></ul><h2><strong>我们在理想的联营公司中寻找什么？</strong></h2><p>选择附属机构是因为他们能够以高度自主的方式在人工智能领域追求有前途的 PIBBSS 一致研究方向。因此，我们正在寻找以下特征（的组合）：</p><ul><li>您的专业领域的学术能力/才干</li><li>对人工智能风险和协调有深入的了解</li><li>良好研究判断/品味的证据</li><li>良好研究生产力的证据，包括强大的自我管理技能</li><li>您提议的研究方向的前景</li><li>能够从 PIBBSS 提供的功能中反事实地受益</li></ul><p>请注意，根据我们的经验，优秀的 PIBBSS 风格的研究人员往往具有非标准背景。因此，我们希望鼓励具有不同背景和观点的个人申请。</p><h2><strong>关于 PIBBSS 和我们的研究重点</strong></h2><p>PIBBSS 是一项研究计划，旨在促进利用自然系统和人工系统中智能行为之间的相似性开展工作，并利用这些见解来使人工智能系统安全、有益和一致。</p><p>从本质上讲，我们相信，对复杂自然和社会系统的研究可以帮助我们更好地了解在人造基质中实施此类行为所涉及的风险，并提高我们开发人工智能系统的能力，使其可靠地显示所需的安全性和可治理性相关属性。 （我们在<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/FuToH2KHxKmJLGk2B/ai-alignment-as-navigating-the-space-of-intelligent"><u>这篇文章</u></a>以及<a href="https://youtu.be/2UabDJKVQcI?si=abcbqyDX6xPvcgmK"><u>这次演讲</u></a>中更详细地描述了我们的认知赌注的性质和一些背景假设）。</p><p>为了对我们感兴趣的研究类型提供更具体的指导，以下是我们过去支持的工作示例：</p><ul><li>旨在<strong>对人工智能系统之间的多智能体交互</strong>产生的动态有原则性的理解， <strong>&nbsp;</strong>例如通过对<a href="https://youtu.be/h8ZbjKS9OTA"><u>行军蚂蚁集体行为的研究</u></a>或进化生物学和生态学的模型</li><li>探索如何在开发<strong>模型评估</strong>中纳入对多智能体人工智能动力学的理解[即将发布]</li><li>探索<strong>可解释性的新途径</strong>，例如<a href="https://youtu.be/cvA3C68Hzqg"><u>可解释性的几何方法</u></a>和<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2dx_VRZtoCs&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>奇异学习理论</u></a></li><li>建立<strong>自然化的能动性理论</strong>，例如探索<a href="https://youtu.be/vx9iHJLd9xI"><u>抽象概念在生活现象中的作用</u></a>；检验<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/BzYmJYECAc3xyCTt6/the-plan-2022-update#What_high_level_progress_have_you_personally_made_in_the_past_year__Any_mistakes_made_or_things_to_change_going_forward_"><u>生命游戏中的自然抽象假设</u></a>； thinking about the characteristics of agents that apply the intentional stance on themselves <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bFGcBrnrdmk&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>(“auto-intentional agents”)</u></a> ;或应用动力系统视角来看待目标导向的行为</li><li>解决<strong>决策理论</strong>中的问题，例如<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uNv1Cq-aVKY&amp;t=46s&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>形式化无更新决策理论</u></a>、<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ivqSoZJEiBc&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>自我修改的鲁棒性</u></a>，或者尝试连接<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/rQDYQrDjPGqjrf8Mk/bridging-expected-utility-maximization-and-optimization"><u>期望效用最大化和优化。</u></a></li><li>对<strong>价值观和实践推理进行更现实的解释</strong>，并探索它们对我们理解人工智能对齐问题的影响[即将发布]</li><li>评估<strong>现有</strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=05iQTypREPc&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><strong><u>法律工具</u></strong></a>在减少人工智能灾难性风险方面的潜力和局限性</li><li>测试人工智能对齐与其他领域/主题之间<strong>富有成效的认知交换</strong>的潜力，例如<a href="https://humanvaluesandartificialagency.com/"><u>人工生命</u></a>、 <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RwEKg5cjkKQ&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowshiphttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RwEKg5cjkKQ&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>基础认知</u></a>、<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7-wvArSvHsc&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>形态计算</u></a>、主动推理、批判社会理论等。</li><li>着眼于<strong>科学哲学（以及特殊科学），</strong>寻找使<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/FuToH2KHxKmJLGk2B/ai-alignment-as-navigating-the-space-of-intelligent"><u>我们的哲学成为现实的方法。</u></a> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=itvIBZ8a5BU&amp;t=947s&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D"><u>研究</u></a>。<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUxTiHUazCo&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>努力</u></a>。 <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/CewHdaAjEvG3bpc6C/epistemic-artefacts-of-conceptual-ai-alignment-research"><u>更多</u></a>。 <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/b9sGz74ayftqPBDYv/the-space-of-systems-and-the-space-of-maps"><u>富有成效的</u></a>。</li></ul><p>我们的研究员和合作者带来了许多领域的专业知识来解决人工智能一致性问题，包括但不限于：</p><ul><li>生态</li><li>进化和发育生物学</li><li>系统生物学</li><li>生物物理学</li><li>神经科学</li><li>认知科学</li><li>Linguistics</li><li>法律理论</li><li>政治理论</li><li>经济理论</li><li>社会理论</li><li>复杂系统研究</li><li>控制论</li><li>网络科学</li><li>物理</li><li>科学哲学</li></ul><h2><strong>如何申请</strong></h2><p>申请现已开放。您可以通过<a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScwMZBTMErBhuXNGNfY_dubgcV8FT3eqYOioxluV82v1V766Q/viewform?usp=sf_link"><u>此链接</u></a>进行申请。</p><p>我们每季度接受新的附属机构。要被视为下一次迭代的一部分，请在<strong>11 月 5 日</strong>之前申请。</p><p>我们预计在未来 6 个月内雇用 2-6 家（中位数 4 家）附属机构。</p><p><strong><u>关于申请流程：</u></strong>申请流程的细节可能因候选人而异，我们认为哪些信息最能帮助我们做出明智的决定。在大多数情况下，初始阶段（申请表）之后是一次或多次采访，以更深入地讨论您的研究。我们也可能会联系您的推荐人，或者在某些情况下，要求您提交约 2-5 小时的工作任务。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JvL3SC6tPjFyCiHad/become-a-pibbss-research-affiliate-1#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JvL3SC6tPjFyCiHad/become-a-pibbss-research-affiliate-1<guid ispermalink="false"> JvL3SC6tPjFyCiHad</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Nora_Ammann]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:41:03 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Epistemic Motif of Abstract-Concrete Cycles & Domain Expansion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 3:28 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> <i>(crossposted from</i> <a href="https://dalcybremin.github.io/posts/2023-10-09-epistemic-motif.html"><i>here</i></a> <i>)</i></p><p>我注意到在数学和哲学的相当广泛的环境中出现了某些认知主题（即清晰且一致的知识生产模式）。这是我认为相当强大的一个：</p><h2> Abstract-Concrete Cycles and Domain Expansion</h2><p>给定一个模拟某些概念的特定对象[结构/定义]，我们可以通过[抽象出它的一些特征]或[实例化它的更具体版本]来修改它，因为我们[<a href="https://tsvibt.blogspot.com/2022/05/expanding-domain-of-discourse-reveals.html">修改讨论的领域</a>]该对象伴随着[来自现实世界的直觉果汁指导我们的搜索]继续运作。在各种抽象级别上重复此操作，您最终会得到一组更丰富的对象。</p><h3>其如何发挥作用的示例</h3><p><i><strong>空间</strong></i></p><p>这是一个数学例子<i>（灵感来自</i><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xun4c-NXgW8"><i>这里</i></a><i>）</i> 。你对想要捕捉的<i>事物</i>有一些具体的概念，比如空间。因此，您可以使用一些立即显而易见的定义（例如<span><span class="mjpage"><span class="mjx-chtml"><span class="mjx-math" aria-label="\mathbb{R}^n"><span class="mjx-mrow" aria-hidden="true"><span class="mjx-msubsup"><span class="mjx-base"><span class="mjx-texatom"><span class="mjx-mrow"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-ams-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">R</span></span></span></span></span> <span class="mjx-sup" style="font-size: 70.7%; vertical-align: 0.615em; padding-left: 0px; padding-right: 0.071em;"><span class="mjx-mi" style=""><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">n</span></span></span> ）</span></span></span></span></span></span>来操作它<style>.mjx-chtml {display: inline-block; line-height: 0; text-indent: 0; text-align: left; text-transform: none; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 100%; font-size-adjust: none; letter-spacing: normal; word-wrap: normal; word-spacing: normal; white-space: nowrap; float: none; direction: ltr; max-width: none; max-height: none; min-width: 0; min-height: 0; border: 0; margin: 0; padding: 1px 0}
.MJXc-display {display: block; text-align: center; margin: 1em 0; padding: 0}
.mjx-chtml[tabindex]:focus, body :focus .mjx-chtml[tabindex] {display: inline-table}
.mjx-full-width {text-align: center; display: table-cell!important; width: 10000em}
.mjx-math {display: inline-block; border-collapse: separate; border-spacing: 0}
.mjx-math * {display: inline-block; -webkit-box-sizing: content-box!important; -moz-box-sizing: content-box!important; box-sizing: content-box!important; text-align: left}
.mjx-numerator {display: block; text-align: center}
.mjx-denominator {display: block; text-align: center}
.MJXc-stacked {height: 0; position: relative}
.MJXc-stacked > * {position: absolute}
.MJXc-bevelled > * {display: inline-block}
.mjx-stack {display: inline-block}
.mjx-op {display: block}
.mjx-under {display: table-cell}
.mjx-over {display: block}
.mjx-over > * {padding-left: 0px!important; padding-right: 0px!important}
.mjx-under > * {padding-left: 0px!important; padding-right: 0px!important}
.mjx-stack > .mjx-sup {display: block}
.mjx-stack > .mjx-sub {display: block}
.mjx-prestack > .mjx-presup {display: block}
.mjx-prestack > .mjx-presub {display: block}
.mjx-delim-h > .mjx-char {display: inline-block}
.mjx-surd {vertical-align: top}
.mjx-surd + .mjx-box {display: inline-flex}
.mjx-mphantom * {visibility: hidden}
.mjx-merror {background-color: #FFFF88; color: #CC0000; border: 1px solid #CC0000; padding: 2px 3px; font-style: normal; font-size: 90%}
.mjx-annotation-xml {line-height: normal}
.mjx-menclose > svg {fill: none; stroke: currentColor; overflow: visible}
.mjx-mtr {display: table-row}
.mjx-mlabeledtr {display: table-row}
.mjx-mtd {display: table-cell; text-align: center}
.mjx-label {display: table-row}
.mjx-box {display: inline-block}
.mjx-block {display: block}
.mjx-span {display: inline}
.mjx-char {display: block; white-space: pre}
.mjx-itable {display: inline-table; width: auto}
.mjx-row {display: table-row}
.mjx-cell {display: table-cell}
.mjx-table {display: table; width: 100%}
.mjx-line {display: block; height: 0}
.mjx-strut {width: 0; padding-top: 1em}
.mjx-vsize {width: 0}
.MJXc-space1 {margin-left: .167em}
.MJXc-space2 {margin-left: .222em}
.MJXc-space3 {margin-left: .278em}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-display {display: table!important}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-inline {display: inline!important; margin-right: -1px}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-default {display: block!important; clear: both}
.mjx-ex-box {display: inline-block!important; position: absolute; overflow: hidden; min-height: 0; max-height: none; padding: 0; border: 0; margin: 0; width: 1px; height: 60ex}
.mjx-test-inline .mjx-left-box {display: inline-block; width: 0; float: left}
.mjx-test-inline .mjx-right-box {display: inline-block; width: 0; float: right}
.mjx-test-display .mjx-right-box {display: table-cell!important; width: 10000em!important; min-width: 0; max-width: none; padding: 0; border: 0; margin: 0}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-R {font-family: monospace; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-I {font-family: monospace; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-B {font-family: monospace; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-BI {font-family: monospace; font-style: italic; font-weight: bold}
.MJXc-TeX-ams-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-R,MJXc-TeX-ams-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-cal-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-B,MJXc-TeX-cal-Bx,MJXc-TeX-cal-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-frak-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-R,MJXc-TeX-frak-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-frak-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-B,MJXc-TeX-frak-Bx,MJXc-TeX-frak-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-math-BI {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BI,MJXc-TeX-math-BIx,MJXc-TeX-math-BIw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-R,MJXc-TeX-sans-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-B,MJXc-TeX-sans-Bx,MJXc-TeX-sans-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-I,MJXc-TeX-sans-Ix,MJXc-TeX-sans-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-script-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-R,MJXc-TeX-script-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-type-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-R,MJXc-TeX-type-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-cal-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-R,MJXc-TeX-cal-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-B,MJXc-TeX-main-Bx,MJXc-TeX-main-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-I,MJXc-TeX-main-Ix,MJXc-TeX-main-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-R,MJXc-TeX-main-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-math-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-I,MJXc-TeX-math-Ix,MJXc-TeX-math-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-size1-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-R,MJXc-TeX-size1-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size2-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-R,MJXc-TeX-size2-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size3-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-R,MJXc-TeX-size3-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size4-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-R,MJXc-TeX-size4-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-vec-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-R,MJXc-TeX-vec-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-vec-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-B,MJXc-TeX-vec-Bx,MJXc-TeX-vec-Bw}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-R; src: local('MathJax_AMS'), local('MathJax_AMS-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_AMS-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_AMS-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_AMS-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-B; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic Bold'), local('MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-R; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur'), local('MathJax_Fraktur-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-B; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur Bold'), local('MathJax_Fraktur-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BI; src: local('MathJax_Math BoldItalic'), local('MathJax_Math-BoldItalic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BIx; src: local('MathJax_Math'); font-weight: bold; font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BIw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-R; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-B; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif Bold'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Bx; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-I; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif Italic'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Ix; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-R; src: local('MathJax_Script'), local('MathJax_Script-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Script-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Script-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Script-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-R; src: local('MathJax_Typewriter'), local('MathJax_Typewriter-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-R; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic'), local('MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-B; src: local('MathJax_Main Bold'), local('MathJax_Main-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Main'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-I; src: local('MathJax_Main Italic'), local('MathJax_Main-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Ix; src: local('MathJax_Main'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-R; src: local('MathJax_Main'), local('MathJax_Main-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-I; src: local('MathJax_Math Italic'), local('MathJax_Math-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-Ix; src: local('MathJax_Math'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Math-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Math-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Math-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-R; src: local('MathJax_Size1'), local('MathJax_Size1-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size1-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size1-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size1-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-R; src: local('MathJax_Size2'), local('MathJax_Size2-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size2-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size2-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size2-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-R; src: local('MathJax_Size3'), local('MathJax_Size3-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size3-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size3-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size3-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-R; src: local('MathJax_Size4'), local('MathJax_Size4-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size4-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size4-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size4-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-R; src: local('MathJax_Vector'), local('MathJax_Vector-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Vector-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Vector-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Vector-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-B; src: local('MathJax_Vector Bold'), local('MathJax_Vector-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Vector'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Vector-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Vector-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Vector-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
</style>它非常具体，配备了一堆隐式结构（公制、角度、显式坐标等）——其中许多结构您可能没有明确意图，甚至对您的目标来说是多余的。</p><p>然后你将结构一一抽象出来，例如，</p><ul><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metric_space">度量空间</a>使用度量抽象出“距离”的概念。</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inner_product_space">内积空间</a>抽象出“相似性”的概念，从而抽象出“大小”和“角度”的概念。</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Topological_space">拓扑空间</a>使用开集抽象出“局部性”的概念。</li></ul><p>有了这个更抽象的<i>空间</i>概念，您可以将其投射到与最初考虑的领域不同的领域中更具体的结构，有效地将其用作生成器。例如，</p><ul><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Function_space">函数空间</a>：“<i>现在我对空间的限制有了更宽松的概念，如果我将其讨论范围扩展到诸如函数之类的无限维对象，会发生什么？”</i></li></ul><p>从这里开始，循环继续。手头有一个可以捕获您想要的内容的具体结构，但现在有了在不同领域中操作的风格，这可能会深入了解最初不在您考虑范围内的某些结构可能会如何进一步抽象出来。</p><ul><li>当然，这个过程是由我们的[对现实世界事物/美学/实用性/简单性的直觉]指导的，而不是在概念空间中盲目搜索。</li></ul><p>当你继续在许多不同的抽象层次上抽象/具体化你的结构的过程之后（每个层次都有利于描述不同类型的论域），你最终会得到一个极其丰富的<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Space_(mathematics)">空间</a>概念，其中一些概念与你最初的<span><span class="mjpage"><span class="mjx-chtml"><span class="mjx-math" aria-label="\mathbb{R}^n"><span class="mjx-mrow" aria-hidden="true"><span class="mjx-msubsup"><span class="mjx-base"><span class="mjx-texatom"><span class="mjx-mrow"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-ams-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">R</span></span></span></span></span> <span class="mjx-sup" style="font-size: 70.7%; vertical-align: 0.615em; padding-left: 0px; padding-right: 0.071em;"><span class="mjx-mi" style=""><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">n</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span>截然不同。</p><p> <i><strong>b) “优化”的概念</strong></i></p><p>在哲学中，我认为情况更加明显。例如，Alex Flint 的<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/znfkdCoHMANwqc2WE/the-ground-of-optimization-1">优化基础</a>，主要通过语域扩展来比较不同的优化定义，即对“奇怪”场景中的定义进行案例分析，看看哪些概念更好地概括并符合我们对这个词的直观概念。优化”应该是这个意思。</p><p> <i><strong>c) “作为定义的定理”的认知母题</strong></i></p><p>一种结构中的定理现在可以成为另一种结构中的定义。这与前面的主题高度相关：我们可以将某些定理视为原始结构的具体[特征/公理]的结果，并以更[轻松/一般的方式将定理转变为定义的行为] ] 结构] 抽象出[定理在原始结构中捕获的特定概念]。例如，</p><ul><li><strong>求幂</strong>：从重复乘法的概念开始。发现幂运算具有泰勒级数近似值。请注意，后者具有更通用的讨论领域，并用它来概括复数、运算符等上下文中的概念。</li><li><strong>分形维度：</strong>首先观察空间的维度对应于缩放指数，并用它来定义“分形性”的度量。</li></ul><p>这是<a href="https://ncatlab.org/nlab/show/The+Rising+Sea">海平面上升</a>！</p><h2> Why does it work?</h2><p>我可以想到这个过程起作用的几个原因（受到<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/GhFoAxG49RXFzze5Y/what-s-so-bad-about-ad-hoc-mathematical-definitions">这里</a>的启发），“为什么”是指它作为人类认识论过程的有效性的原因。</p><p>仅通过选择，我们最终建模的概念（以及科学家对首先<i>可以</i>建模的内容建立的直觉）往往是可以由少数需求捕获的概念。</p><p>如果需求排除了所有可能性或规定了太多，我们可以纠正我们的直觉/需求，例如发现以我们没有注意到的方式巧妙地限制我们结构形式的假设。</p><p>通过找到我们的结构必须满足的这种“最低条件”，它变得更有利于添加新的结构，这样它就可以更加具体地应用于新的讨论领域。从那里，我们可以列出例子并找到新的定理，从而丰富我们反馈到这个循环中的直觉。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/x6xfX7nwf53uM8hBW/epistemic-motif-of-abstract-concrete-cycles-and-domain#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/x6xfX7nwf53uM8hBW/epistemic-motif-of-abstract-concrete-cycles-and-domain<guid ispermalink="false"> x6xfX7nwf53uM8hBW</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalcy Bremin]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:28:45 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Simple Terminal Colors]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 12:40 AM GMT<br/><br/><p><span>我经常在终端上工作，并且经常想编写一些程序来对输出进行一些着色。例如，也许我正在查看</span><a href="https://www.jefftk.com/p/sequencing-intro">测序读数</a>，我想知道它的哪一部分是其被标记的原因。我可以使用<a href="https://pypi.org/project/colorama/">colorama</a> 、 <a href="https://pypi.org/project/termcolor/">termcolor</a>或其他库，但<a href="https://www.jefftk.com/p/designing-low-upkeep-software">包含这么简单的东西的依赖项</a>并不值得。相反，打印彩色文本非常简单：</p><p></p><pre> COLOR_RED_BOLD = &#39;\x1b[1;31m&#39;
COLOR_BLUE_BOLD = &#39;\x1b[1;34m&#39;
COLOR_END = &#39;\x1b[0m&#39;
打印（
  “一条鱼，两条鱼，” +
  COLOR_RED_BOLD +“红色”+
  COLOR_END +“鱼，”+
  COLOR_BLUE_BOLD +“蓝色”+
  COLOR_END +“鱼。”）
</pre><p><a href="https://www.jefftk.com/terminal-one-fish-two-fish-red-fish-blue-fish-big.png"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/yb6yjheuv5hy5j3kdm6t" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/yb6yjheuv5hy5j3kdm6t 550w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/af02tlyznphgzazdh0qz 1100w"></a></p><div></div><p></p><p>我通常只需要一种或两种突出显示颜色，通常为粗体，并且很少发现六种标准颜色有限制。如果您想将注意力吸引到特定的事物上，同时在需要进一步观察时保持其周围的背景，那么这会特别有用。</p><p>这有多兼容？有一天，使用非 ANSI 终端的人会运行我的代码并抱怨吗？一个数据点是我在<a href="https://www.jefftk.com/p/introducing-icdiff">2009 年</a>用这种方法编写了<a href="https://www.jefftk.com/icdiff">icdiff</a> ，并且它相当流行。虽然我收到了<a href="https://github.com/jeffkaufman/icdiff/issues?q=is%3Aissue">数百份</a>错误报告，但这从来没有人抱怨过。</p><p><i>评论通过： <a href="https://www.facebook.com/jefftk/posts/pfbid0yNYkCYNaKotC3ZKBJZ2sCMiAogXFgBcjyfS9qW7JHduMXkUEBNxW5ywpcphoGJQel">facebook</a> , <a href="https://mastodon.mit.edu/@jefftk/111207929256178296">mastodon</a></i></p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/simple-terminal-colors#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/simple-terminal-colors<guid ispermalink="false"> olK5J7xazS8L3p6fy</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[jefftk]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:40:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>