<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title><![CDATA[LessWrong]]></title><description><![CDATA[A community blog devoted to refining the art of rationality]]></description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com<image/><url> https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/v1497915096/favicon_lncumn.ico</url><title>少错</title><link/>https://www.lesswrong.com<generator>节点的 RSS</generator><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 9 月 6 日星期三 16:16:21 GMT </lastbuilddate><atom:link href="https://www.lesswrong.com/feed.xml?view=rss&amp;karmaThreshold=2" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><item><title><![CDATA[What's in your list of important technical projects/experiments to run for AI alignment?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 2:58 PM GMT<br/><br/><p>我猜测技术协调研究人员对他们认为运行起来真正有用的项目/实验有更多的想法，而不是他们的能力（由于时间/管理/资源的限制）。我想知道您的重要技术项目或实验列表中会包含哪些内容以进行人工智能调整。 （提出这个问题的另一种方式可能是你希望自己有能力进行哪些实验）</p><p>更重要的是，我想知道<i>为什么</i>你会对某人/团队做这些项目感兴趣，你希望他们能够阐明哪些开放性问题，他们解决了深度学习或泛化方面的哪些困惑，等等。</p><p>我知道一些运行良好的项目/技术实验可能需要最先进的模型，甚至是尚不存在的系统，但将其写下来的部分价值在于传达您所掌握的信息。正在<i>寻找</i>。 （此外，人们可以参与的项目类型不一定对技术协调中的开放问题直接有用。它们可以包括创建维基、论坛、工具、库等项目。）</p><hr><p>这个问题的启发是：</p><ol><li> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/EPAofvLzsCwqYnekj/what-s-in-your-list-of-unsolved-problems-in-ai-alignment">这个问题</a>是关于人们的开放问题清单上会出现哪些内容</li><li><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/LbrPTJ4fmABEdEnLf/200-concrete-open-problems-in-mechanistic-interpretability">尼尔·南达（Neel Nanda）列出了机械可解释性中具体的开放性问题</a></li><li><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JMebqicMD6azB8MwK/open-problems-in-activation-engineering">亚历克斯·特纳 (Alex Turner) 列出的激活工程中具体的开放问题</a></li></ol><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ZNXiKT3dNvLzj7d6m/what-s-in-your-list-of-important-technical-projects#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ZNXiKT3dNvLzj7d6m/what-s-in-your-list-of-important-technical-projects<guid ispermalink="false"> ZNXiKT3dNvLzj7d6m</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[watermark]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 14:58:23 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Monthly Roundup #10: September 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 1:20 PM GMT<br/><br/><p>又到了那个时候了。这里有所有的新闻和感兴趣的项目。</p><p>除了通常的能源、童年、生育和住房等附加类别之外，没有<a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://thezvi.substack.com/p/who-has-the-best-food" target="_blank">包括美国或法国是否有更好的食物</a>以及与 Y-Combinator 相关的各种主张。</p><span id="more-23529"></span><h4>坏消息</h4><p>所有的宣传都是好的宣传， <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/visakanv/status/1686880942890323968">采取相应的行动并解决平衡版本。</a></p><blockquote><p> OnlyFans 的创作者正在向模因聚合帐户付费，以灌输他们故意令人畏缩的内容。对于每个参与其中的人来说，经济学似乎都非常有效。看到一个创作者说每个帖子大约 200 美元。在 1000 个 QT/RT 下，低会话率仍然是有利可图的。</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-08/wework-raises-substantial-doubt-about-staying-in-business">WeWork 可能不会再做这么久了</a>，对维持业务存在重大疑问。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1686961965552545792">37 岁的男子有 15,000 美元的积蓄</a>，完全拥有自己的货车，但没有技能，以洗碗工为职业，不知道自己的生活该怎么办。没有什么能给他带来快乐，他永远不会快乐。该怎么办？我不知道，我把它作为一个有趣的问题提出来。你会在那个地方做什么？</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1693278631613849634">是的，有些人会选择无家可归</a>，甚至在你看来非常糟糕的条件下也可能吸毒，即使他们可以选择找工作。这个问题涉及的权衡之一是，有些人确实更喜欢这条路，或者如果有选择的话，一旦药物对他们产生了钩子，现在确实更喜欢它。因此，如果我们对他们提供足够的补贴，他们就会这么做，补贴的规模很重要，而且供应曲线会按照你想象的方式倾斜。然后必须与人道考虑相平衡，并为需要帮助的人（包括需要康复的人）提供帮助。</p><p>如果您错过了并自我推荐： <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.bitsaboutmoney.com/archive/the-waste-stream-of-consumer-finance/">帕特里克·麦肯齐（Patrick McKenzie）谈信用卡追债</a>。尽管这看起来可能很糟糕，但更糟糕的是，如果你知道正确的词语来表示付款是可选的。 <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/s_r_constantin/status/1691152253116149760">莎拉·康斯坦丁 (Sarah Constantin) 在这个帖子中提出了她的想法</a>。</p><blockquote><p>莎拉·康斯坦丁：“所以……债务是假的？怎么可能？为什么没有人打击这种漏洞呢？”因为几乎没有人“既”对让收债员离开感兴趣，又足够善于驾驭法律和官僚机构以实现这一目标。 “我敢打赌，在实践中，[收债人]会避免向任何有能力和财力来行使其权利的人收债。”</p><p>这里“债务是假的”并不意味着“如果每个人都停止偿还债务就好了”。显然，对于 95% 以上的信用卡债务而言，该系统有效且有价值，并且取决于人们是否愿意偿还债务。</p><p>奇怪的是，“偿还债务”的规范似乎完全是由……人们的道德感以及失去信用评级和必须与收债人打交道的风险所维持的。该规范*不*受法律约束。</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2023-are-you-rich-best-cities-to-live-salary/">富人常常不认为自己富有，或者至少不觉得自己富有</a>。我不明白的部分是，无论解释了多少次，也不管我涉及多少齿轮，每年赚 15 万美元以上却没有积蓄的大量人们会适应并花费任何金额进来。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.overcomingbias.com/p/why-interpret-me?utm_source=post-email-title&amp;publication_id=1245641&amp;post_id=135995427&amp;isFreemail=true&amp;utm_medium=email">罗宾·汉森（Robin Hanson）注意到</a>，人们经常使用著名的思想家来构建代表思想家的人物角色，然后使用这些人物角色来提取更多的意见，这通常会在人们的头脑中主导论点和论点细节，从而产生影响，以至于汉森说人物角色是思想家影响世界的主要方式。我认为这太过分了。他以亚当·斯密为例很能说明问题。关于他是（或者本来应该是，我猜？）左翼还是右翼的错误问题有很多讨论，人们确实大多忽略了他的论点细节。我读过《国富论》，印象深刻，包括关于白银的题外话，但大多数人也不记得细节了。在我的模型中，最重要的是传递的核心思想，在这种情况下主要是看不见的手。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/AristotlesStgra/status/1695507942580097341">提醒</a>人们，如果有人认为有需要就可以使用武力（通过法律或其他方式）来满足该需要，他们可能会将这种需要的主张解释为暴力的理由。另外提醒一下，当您撰写某些主题时，请让我们说您可能不想阅读评论。</p><blockquote><p>亚里士多德：好吧，假设你有以下一般原则：1）无论人类本质上需要什么，他们都有权这样做。 2）如果你对某物有权利，你就有权使用暴力来获得它。</p><p> Paul Schofield：是的，我认为有些人肯定有这种观点，但我不赞同 2</p><p> Artistotle：是的，但这可能与你没有太大关系：如果有人在支持（1）和（2）的圈子中，他们必须对任何说人类需要性的人充满敌意。</p><p>艾格尼丝·卡拉德（Agnes Callard）：很难说服自己相信人们对自己所写内容的回复既不是关于自己的，也不是（甚至）关于一个人所写的内容的，但我认为令人震惊的是，他们根本就不是——把他们当作是让专栏作者对其标题负责是错误的。</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2023/08/08/age-law-online-porn-00110148">各国越来越多地禁止网络色情内容</a>，他们在技术上将其称为“年龄验证法”。你可以猜到人们对于将自己的身份信息提供给色情网站有多么兴奋，所以这实际上非常接近禁令，当然对于那些真正关心的人来说可以通过 VPN 来规避这一禁令。我们将看看这一公然违宪的举动是否得到支持，与此同时，像 PornHub 这样的网站正在退出整个州。话又说回来，这可能是各州第一次采取行动，确保我们的孩子真正学到一些关于现代技术的重要知识，而把微不足道的不便放在色情内容面前有几个好处。它需要感觉很特别。</p><h4> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/ben_r_hoffman/status/1695511073925853649">美国存在可靠性危机吗？</a></h4><p>我确实担心这种事情似乎更常见，但这很可能是由于期望不断提高、挑选问题以及没有正确记住过去的情况。特别值得注意的是，过去基本上没有审查系统，要完成某件事，你通常必须认识一个认识另一个人的人，而现在没有人认识一个认识另一个人的人，你会很幸运认识一个人根本就是一个男人。</p><blockquote><p>帕特里克·麦肯齐：我觉得自己就像一个单口喜剧演员和人类学家的结合体，需要向房地产人士解释一个完全陌生的概念，称为“约会”。</p><p> “也许我们周六就能看到公寓。”</p><p> “不，这就是你同意*几乎肯定*周六去看公寓，我们同意，然后事情就发生了。”</p><p> “除非有什么事情发生。”</p><p> “是的，但我们有一种强烈的文化规范，即为紧急情况保留这种做法。”</p><p> “就像忘记一样？”</p><p> “不，就像你母亲去世一样。”</p><p> “我妈妈为什么会死？”</p><p> “不，如果你母亲去世的话，我们同意你不去预约也不会做错什么。但如果你忘记了，那就错了。”</p><p> “但为什么。”</p><p> “我们还有这些叫做电话的东西。”</p><p> “哦，是的，我将它用于 TikTok。”</p><p> “如果发生紧急情况，也许比你母亲去世的情况轻，你会打电话。”</p><p> “如果我打电话告诉你我不来，你可能会不高兴。”</p><p> “是的。”</p><p> “那我就不打电话了？”</p><p>为了避免我不公正地损害整个芝加哥房地产行业的声誉，下面的经纪人打电话确认了预约，然后发短信说，由于之前的预约已经过去，他不可避免地会迟到五分钟。随后他高效地回答了问题。</p><p>正如我向父亲提到的那样，他的整个职业生涯都在房地产领域：“至少遇到一个人，他表现出完成这项工作所需的绝对最低能力，这是令人放心的。”</p><p>本·霍夫曼：事情真的变得这么糟糕了吗？ （ <img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/pKhzQyaWwes63JFwp/jgt2eoslwfcyu0abb4yz" alt="🧵" style="height:1em;max-height:1em"> ) 他们最近多久好转了？我小时候的印象绝对不是美国就是这样，但我试图通过纽黑文寻找出租屋的房地产经纪人未能向我们展示最初的几次计划参观。</p><p>我最终通过 Craigslist 找到了一个地方，尽管有很多骗局，但这似乎仍然是最好的选择。第二个最佳选择是遍历本地声誉网络。</p><p>尝试了当地的黑人/社会正义书店，没有公告板，但引导我去了嬉皮士杂货店。距离那里一个街区，我在 Loaf &amp; Ladle 停下来接电话。原来这是一个犹太人的社交中心，我遇到了一位房地产经纪人，他立即安排了几次看房。</p><p>当我出售在华盛顿的房子时，我没有遇到任何问题，但当我试图购买它时，贷款发起人不知何故未能委托进行财产评估，而我的房地产经纪人完全没用。不过，据我所知，没有错过任何约会。</p><p>那是一个打折的（Redfin）房地产经纪人，所以服务可能不太好，但我在纽黑文尝试过的那个作为租赁经纪人受到强烈推荐。</p><p> 2021 年，当我付给一位律师一笔聘用费，让他给 @moskov 写一封信，描述我在 @GiveWell 观察到的渎职行为时，他如约赴约，然后在几个月后给我发来了无法使用的糟糕工作。 （更改帐户详细信息的方式使其明显不连贯且错误）</p><p>医生通常会在规定的预约时间后几个小时内给我看病，尽管当我想在纽约市建立护理服务时，牙医确实取消了我的预约，然后提出六个月后重新预约。</p><p>定期的 Lyft 和 SuperShuttle 通常会准时到达。</p></blockquote><p>以我的经验来看，房地产行业的人包罗万象。优秀的代理人不仅知道如何遵守预约，还知道如何确保其他代理人也大多遵守预约，他们的帮助和指导是值得的每一分钱。你随机打电话给一个人，因为你想看看他们的财产？可以采取多种方式。</p><p>我们与保姆的经验强化了这一点。我们试图聘用的许多人都会在最后一刻取消，突发家庭健康紧急情况的发生率高得惊人，好消息是互联网常常使人们可以争夺替代者。我还注意到，与 Uber 类似，我们已经学会了对陌生人的一种不同的信任和可靠性，而在我年轻的时候，我们会因为这样做而被称为疯狂。</p><p>一般来说，约会和人员的可靠性如何？如果没有验证方法而随意选择，就不那么可靠了，而且看起来比过去更糟糕。然而，我们还拥有各种相当强大的评级和审查系统，在许多情况下可以很好地识别和激励良好行为。</p><h4>大科技的小问题</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/sbenthall/status/1688721803458326528">Zoom 的服务条款包括以下内容</a>：</p><blockquote><p> “您同意 Zoom 出于<strong>任何目的</strong>访问、使用、收集、创建、修改、分发、处理、共享、维护、存储<em>[您在会议中所说的内容</em>]……。 ...您<strong>特此无条件且不可撤销地转让给 Zoom ...<em>您的最终用户</em>无条件且不可撤销地向 Zoom 转让</strong>[<em>您在会议中所说的内容</em>]的所有权利、所有权和利益，<strong><em>包括所有专有权利</em></strong>...“</p></blockquote><p> Google Meet 存在，大致免费，甚至可以符合 HIPAA，而且运行良好。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/HiFromMichaelV/status/1696694335297744999">Facebook不具约束力的监督委员会不具约束力，再次被忽视。</a>请记住，拥有董事会并忽略它们比没有它们更好，而我们的本能是使用董事会作为额外指责的理由。抵抗。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/xDaily/status/1693709116341129360">Twitter 很快就会完全摆脱</a>“Tweepcred”系统，你将不再因为与低信誉帐户的交互或没有足够的关注者而受到有效的惩罚。据称，旧系统经常削弱那些没有做错任何事的小账户的影响力。问题是，这是机器人和垃圾邮件防御系统的一部分，而该系统已经陷入了严重的麻烦，所以也许现在还不是进一步削弱它的时候，因此我们正在等待实施这一更改。</p><h4>谷歌仍计划永久删除不活动帐户</h4><p>我之前已经提到过，但是，谷歌两年不活动的门槛确实很糟糕。特别是， <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/GrahamStarr/status/1693119093526671859">如果你被关进监狱会怎样</a>？</p><blockquote><p>格雷厄姆·斯塔：任何被监禁超过两年的人都将返回到他们被删除的谷歌帐户，并且与家庭、工作、记忆和其他一切允许重新调整的东西有最密切的联系。谷歌支持论坛已经充满了这样的故事。</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F49821a01-938a-43e9-adbd-887b4303e167_1490x1274.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/hlmfls531tnk2yld9hot" alt="图像"></a></figure><p>上述问题之前就已经存在了。这只会使情况变得更糟。一个明显的回应是“没有单点故障”，但说起来容易做起来难。如果我的 Google 帐户被删除或永久被盗，我不知道具体会有多糟糕，但肯定会非常糟糕。彻底删除将比当前的噩梦更糟糕，而且更常见。是的，您可以说“告诉您的律师或家人或朋友您的登录信息，并让他们每年为您登录”，但很多人会忽略这样做，或者可能无法这样做，或者有人会忘记。</p><p>我强烈敦促谷歌重新考虑帐户删除政策。它所产生的恶意和偏执的数量将是惊人的。即使在最好的情况下，数据保存的成本也会相形见绌许多倍，而且谁会在这个时候丢弃数据呢？</p><h4>加密货币可能并不完全安全</h4><p>不存在存储加密货币的安全方法。如果您有实体钱包，也许<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/jason_koebler/status/1695177963300606463">您最终会申请破产，其中提到“钱包事件”，您丢失了价值 3890 万美元的代币的密码</a>。每一个防止“丢失物理钥匙”或“知道密码的人被公交车撞到”的解决方案都意味着复制信息。将您的加密货币存储在为您处理此问题的其他人处还存在其他风险。没有安全港。问问哪条路对你来说实际上更安全，并记住，每次加密货币永久丢失，都意味着对我们其他人来说有更多价值。</p><p>还有一些新提议的美国税收法规， <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/CryptoTaxGuyETH/status/1695603888957641154">许多人声称这些法规将有效地迫使大部分加密生态系统对美国进行地理封锁</a>。</p><p>据我了解，新规则规定，经纪人提供 1099 并确保适当预扣销售税的要求应适用于所有数字资产的销售，并且基本上将所有允许此类销售的加密应用程序视为具有该义务的经纪人。</p><p>据我了解，这就是发生的事情。</p><ol><li>美国的税收规则非常令人讨厌。</li><li>加密货币人士无视这些规则并构建他们声称不必遵守美国法律的应用程序，因为在上下文中他们会非常愚蠢。</li><li>美国指出，法律适用，而且愚蠢从来没有阻止过他们。</li><li>加密货币人士警告说，这将破坏我们对这些有价值的加密技术和平台的访问。</li><li>美国表示，此类警告以前也从未阻止过美国国税局，而且是“好吧，强硬”和“这介于巧合和整个想法之间”的某种组合。</li></ol><blockquote><p>迈尔斯·多伊彻： <img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ygMkB9r4DuQQxrrpj/fie4yum3b7jsxqpm7rut" alt="🚨" style="height:1em;max-height:1em"> ：美国刚刚推出了一项税收提案，该提案可能会扼杀我们所知的 DeFi。</p><p>美国财政部和国税局刚刚发布了拟议的加密货币法规，可能会将 Uniswap、1inch、Curve、MetaMask 等 DeFi 应用视为经纪人并被迫实施 KYC……</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/ArthurB/status/1695109446303719727">Arthur B</a> ：如果我们最终的世界让大多数 Web 前端都进行 KYC，同时还有一些自由的匿名前端，那么这实际上是一个不错的妥协。但当然，如果没有反击，政府不会就此止步。</p><p> @adamscochran：“这不仅仅是令人发指的越权行为。这是从根本上理解这项技术的失败。”</p><p> Spreek：回顾一下新提议的税收规则：Metamask 是一家经纪商，必须进行 KYC 并报告所有用户，除非它取消掉期。 Uniswap 是一家经纪商，需要将其 UI 更新为新的 KYC 版本。任何具有多重签名的东西都是经纪人，并且需要添加 KYC。</p><p> Arthur B：以太坊上的每个扩容解决方案和几乎所有 defi 协议都由多重签名控制。这是缺乏协议集成和智能合约安全性的原因。这两件事都可能是真的：</p><p> 1⃣这是一个不好的规定，应该大力反对</p><p>2⃣ 这是糟糕的设计</p></blockquote><p>是的。这是对技术的不理解，这里的“技术”指的是美国政府。</p><p>你说不可能遵守法律？也许你应该在设计与法律不相容的技术之前就考虑到这一点。相反，你坚持认为必须改变的是法律。你正在触犯法律。猜猜谁赢了。</p><p>要么找到一种方法让税务员分得一杯羹，他说他有权按照他想要的方式进行验证，而不是你认为公平的方式，只要你愿意，或者以其他方式不违反他们的规则，你可以让你的技术。否则，我猜，不会有那么多。</p><p>如果由于版权、专业许可或责任等问题而导致人工智能发生同样的事情，那将是真正的耻辱。真是耻辱。</p><h4>政府工作</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/my-presidential-platform">我们终于有了一个我们都可以支持的候选人：Alexander &#39;24</a> 。他是伟大的。</p><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.readunshackled.com/story/">不受束缚：高技能移民在美国蓬勃发展的实用指南</a>。链接转到该书的网站。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/scottlincicome/status/1693347428500463792">是的，我们需要更高的价格才能看到蒙娜丽莎</a>。</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F29a23be4-2538-4696-9034-99d66273ceac_802x966.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/ozxmzyntgv06rxtulehn" alt=""></a></figure><p>最近，我们一家人去首都度假时，我们注意到所有的公共景点都是零美元，所以我们无法进入。赤字不断扩大。</p><p> 《芯片法案》进展如何？按设计工作。 <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/zachweinberg/status/1688742310660521984">工会努力阻止引进台湾工人启动亚利桑那州台积电工厂的计划</a>，该工厂因缺乏具备必要核心技能的工人而处于闲置状态。 <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/kevinsxu/status/1689639343621877760">台积电与工会之间的关系正在迅速恶化</a>，工会声称台积电只是想进口廉价劳动力并游说拒绝工人签证，而台湾人则反击称美国人懒惰。该工厂可能永远不会开放。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/spacex-versus-the-department-of-justice.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spacex-versus-the-department-of-justice">司法部起诉 SpaceX 重点招聘美国公民和合法永久居民</a>，尽管国防部要求 SpaceX 参与其项目时只能雇用美国公民和合法永久居民。此外，即使与任何合理的安全问题完全无关，您也需要符合在司法部工作的这些要求。</p><blockquote><p>匿名（在 MR 评论中）：作为在向军事和民用客户提供服务的承包商工作的人，并且雇用美国和非美国公民，我可以确认，这种情况一直在出现，而且是一个巨大的问题。内部麻烦。员工入职后，问题并没有结束。</p><p>法律完全矛盾。有各种敏感信息（不仅仅是 ITAR 和机密信息）不能或不应该向我们的非美国公民员工披露。但与此同时，由于民权法，我们不得（例如）限制仅向美国公民分发任何电子邮件。因此，在实践中，我们提出了一个复杂的美国公民身份代理系统。</p><p>目前，我们有一个内部员工指定类别，它几乎不加掩饰地代表美国公民身份，但不使用“C”一词。这让我们能够解决大部分合规问题。但这可能只是时间问题，有人发现这一点并起诉我们，然后我们需要找到更复杂的解决方法。</p></blockquote><p>总体而言，整个法律状况是荒谬的。显然，解决方案是澄清安全规则优先，只要安全规则的实际需要所要求的歧视是合法的。</p><p>就 SpaceX 而言，这似乎不可能不是司法部的哗众取宠和政治目标。火箭是我们真正关心运行安全的地方，没有任何理性和中立的人会在这里起诉 SpaceX。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1687254959522467843">他们</a>完全不会被一个由腐败和无能的政客组成的新的小集团所取代，对吧？人们不可能不可避免地投票支持这种疯狂行为。</p><blockquote><p>保罗·格雷厄姆：一旦旧金山摆脱了拖累旧金山的一小群腐败无能的政客，他们就会惊人地反弹。</p></blockquote><p>芙蕾雅是对的。</p><blockquote><p> Freyja：加州行为健康规划委员会非常努力。</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F6a20dd44-afe6-4d28-bbbf-55b285be7847_900x1200.webp" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/cewz6g3ytjvvamd27skb" alt="图像"></a></figure><p>这份表格命令您撒谎。你撒谎了。世界上有零个人有能力获得这样的任命，并且与任何个人、团体或商业企业没有任何联系，这些人、团体或企业可能被用来（甚至不公平地）用来质疑或攻击他们的品格。但很明显，我们的目标是让你点击“不”。</p><blockquote><p>萝卜：天哪，在心理分析中总是让我困惑的是“你有没有想过自杀？”为什么不，这是我第一次听说这个概念，嗯有趣。</p><p> Freyja：哦，是的，在自杀热线中，这就像我们要问的第一个问题：“嗨！”你叫什么名字！？你现在想自杀吗？哈哈真好笑。&#39;</p></blockquote><p>这是一种以各种形式、向人民灌输不诚信行为的流行模式。</p><h4>政府规划</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.slowboring.com/p/a-serious-case-for-dynamic-scoring">高技能移民的案例说明了动态预算评分的有力案例</a>。由于管理费用的原因，让外国 STEM 毕业生获得绿卡需要 10 年内花费 31 亿美元。每个人都同意这将带来更大的经济效益并增加人口，净赚政府资金。但国会预算办公室被指示仅将此类行动作为成本进行评分，因此当每个人都有固定的预算支出时，实施起来就变得困难。</p><p>这里有两个不同的问题。</p><p>首先，我们在言辞上、程序上、甚至在法律上都越来越重视提案的预算评分。当国会预算办公室在十年窗口内使用其程序时，我们的实际法律会根据技术上的分数而被严重扭曲。我们的规则在第八年或第九年发生了巨大的变化，以使数字发挥作用。我们得到了“年度修复”，直到最后一刻才有人愿意付费。我们得到的事情远比这更不理智。我们还得到了一组行动，我们需要找到“付费”的东西，从技术上讲，这些东西可以使所有东西加到 0 美元，而其他组行动则不遵循这个过程，因此要花费大量资金。</p><p>第二个问题是，一旦我们开始动态评分，每个人都会争论和滥用它，所以我们不能拥有美好的东西。我看到了狭隘的论点，“如果这字面上意味着更多的人，那么我们就可以计算这些人的新税收收入”，但这些人也会带来成本，其幅度很难确定，一旦你打开那扇门，我们为什么不呢？动态评分其他一切？</p><p>我认为正确的答案是我们应该有两个或更多分数。应该有一个无动态调整的数字，然后是一个仅商定的调整数字，然后我们就可以为每个人在使用最大一厢情愿的某种组合并试图获得时得到的疯狂卡通数字而争论。真正的答案。</p><p>另一种解决方案是将其视为激励问题而不是计算问题。您不需要技术上正确的答案。你真正想要的是一个不会扼杀明显净利润提案的系统，因此与其进行不确定幅度的动态调整，不如使用一个触发器，其中充分合理的项目，其预算分配然后由国会预算办公室或类似机构确定被计为净成本恰好为 0 美元，并且存在于预算计算之外。我们坚持预算的原因是为了不花钱，而不是因为我们只有这么多美元。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/bryan_caplan/status/1689005706018689025">维韦克·拉马斯瓦米提出的移民政策</a>是，只允许那些能够证明自己将为美国带来净经济利益并且能够通过公民考试的人入境。工人组织反驳说有超过十亿人可以满足这一要求，布莱恩·卡普兰指出，这并不是反对这种政策的理由。</p><p>特朗普提议征收 10% 的普遍关税。 <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulkrugman/status/1694341922263847311">克鲁格曼预计，这将直接花费不到 GDP 的 1%</a> ，因为作为统一关税，它可以避免真正可怕的情况。该提案之所以可怕，并不是因为其直接影响（这样做对我们造成了伤害，但并没有那么严重），而是因为它产生了一场混战，而不是就此结束。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1698389118391038332">据报道，南非法律规定不可能合法地将人们逐出公寓</a>，因此仅在约翰内斯堡，犯罪团伙就实际上劫持（盗窃）了 600 多栋建筑物。他们解决了平衡问题，尽管尚未完全解决。</p><blockquote><p>南非的《防止非法驱逐法》（PIE 法）是一个起点。它规定，未经法院命令，任何人都不得被带离家中。</p><p>一旦一个人在建筑物中安顿下来并能证明他们无处可去，他们就不能被驱逐。</p><p> ……</p><p> “你不能驱逐任何人，除非他们有其他住处，而这需要由律师（控方）提供，”她说。</p><p> “这就是混乱的根源。因为律师无法提供任何住宿，因为他们自己的住宿已被劫持。”</p></blockquote><p>通常情况下，问题不是为什么会发生这种情况，而是为什么更多的情况没有发生。</p><h4>我们共同打击犯罪</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/garrytan/status/1696658211305116002">旧金山警察委员会试图禁止警察甚至步行追捕嫌疑人。</a>走开。</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/eyessfboe/status/1698844775015915608">Laurance Lem Lee</a> ：3 分钟内 2 个街区内有 4 辆车被撞。我必须向游客解释为什么 SFPD 不能追捕他们。</p></blockquote><p>相关： <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1690803866445688832">加利福尼亚州 Nordstrom 商店有组织的大规模抢劫的视频</a>。</p><blockquote><p>保罗·格雷厄姆：立法者似乎没有意识到罪犯的适应速度有多快。如果你将某件事非刑事化，你不仅会改变你处理当前犯罪的方式，还会改变你处理因此而发生的所有新犯罪的方式。</p><p>当然，没有人会在观看该视频后认为“是的，这就是一个治理良好的社会中的情况。”</p></blockquote><p>正如我在评论中指出的那样，我们应该感到惊喜的是，事情并没有更快地崩溃。一旦人们“进行实验”并发现此类行为得到了有效容忍，为什么步伐没有加快，从而在快速的负反馈循环中使执法变得更加困难？或者，新政府需要多长时间才能出现来填补现任政府留下的空白？</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/bryan_caplan/status/1695070905444044977">耶鲁大学校园警察工会在一张附有死神照片的传单中警告新生</a>，这座城市犯罪猖獗且危险，告诉他们“留在校园”，“避免公共交通”，“八点后不要上街”下午&#39;</p><blockquote><p>布莱恩·卡普兰：当我访问<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Yale">@耶鲁</a>时也是如此。我问教职员工：“ <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Yale">@耶鲁</a>大学为什么不向纽黑文支付 10 亿美元，让校园内的所有街道都成为步行街？”他们的眼睛都瞪出来了。 “那是行不通的。这个城市讨厌我们。”</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/jailed-ftx-founder-bankman-fried-return-court-new-plea-2023-08-22/?taid=64e4e4dd452e760001e63204&amp;utm_campaign=trueAnthem:+Trending+Content&amp;utm_medium=trueAnthem&amp;utm_source=twitter">SBF 只能靠面包和水维持生计，</a>因为监狱拒绝为他提供纯素餐点。</p><blockquote><p>监狱管理局在一份声明中表示，MDC 囚犯可以获得“适当的”医疗保健、药品和热餐。该公司表示，该设施按照国家菜单的要求“提供营养充足的膳食”，该菜单“每年进行分析，以确保满足所有饮食要求”。</p></blockquote><p>我认为这是一件“经常发生”的事情，而不是他受到特别糟糕的待遇？监狱似乎经常被“描述为不人道”，但似乎没有人愿意对此采取任何行动。你可以通过所有你想要的法律，监狱决定忽视它们，没有人在乎。同样，法院下令给予他阿得拉（Adderall）以帮助他协助自己辩护，监狱认为这更像是一个建议。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robinhanson/status/1690698946807771136">纽约警察局在全市有 1,500 人</a>——大约每六千人中就有一人——从事“情报和反恐”工作？这是电影级别的偏执和假定的背景威胁。我们既能面对需要这么多人的威胁，又能如此善于预防事件，这并非不可能，但这似乎不太可能。</p><p>想要捣毁偷走您电脑的盗窃团伙吗？很简单，你所要做的就是警察的所有工作，因为他们不会为你做这件事，但这并不难。 <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/aubetony/status/1698924690432217189">布鲁塞尔的故事（2 分钟）</a> 。</p><h4>犯罪到底有多严重？</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://bensouthwood.substack.com/p/how-bad-is-crime">一些贵族（年长的）尝试衡量犯罪的影响</a>。</p><blockquote><p>您可以在全国范围内将其添加起来。如果一个人愿意支付 80 美元来减少 10% 的谋杀案，并且有 25,000 起谋杀案，那么他们隐含地将十分之一的谋杀案（2,500 起）估价为 80 美元，因此每起谋杀案的价格略高于 3 美分。乘以数亿美国人，每起谋杀案的总价值将接近 1000 万美元。该论文于 2006 年进行了计算，美国人愿意支付 25,000 美元来避免全社会发生入室盗窃，愿意支付 70,000 美元来避免严重袭击，愿意支付近 1000 万美元来避免谋杀。</p></blockquote><p>与其他估计相比，这些数字听起来<em>非常合理，</em>尤其是在 2006 年至 2022 年期间进行了调整。如果说有什么不同的话，那就是他们太理智了，在一些医疗保健计算中，1000万美元被用作生命价值。这让我很怀疑。人们真的有能力进行这些类型的计算吗？如果人们愿意为拯救一只鸟付出比拯救十只鸟更多的钱，我们凭什么认为他们可以衡量 10% 的入室盗窃的价值？支付意愿总是涉及支付不足的人怎么办？</p><p> The answers here are still too low. I am confident that the correct value of preventing the average prevented murder is well in excess of the value of preventing average medical death, based on how people react to them and guard against them, and the ages of those impacted.</p><blockquote><p> A more practical situation comes when juries <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0144818803000255">award money</a> to &#39;make people whole&#39; for physical injury, pain, suffering, mental anguish, shock, and discomfort that they have experienced due to some illegal action. For example, one 68-year old lady was shot through the spine in a drive-by shooting, and left paraplegic – a jury gave her $2.7m in addition to her medical costs.</p></blockquote><p> We <em>know</em> these numbers don&#39;t make sense, wrongful death compensation is way too low and pain compensation way too high, hence the &#39;back up and roll over them again to make sure they&#39;re dead&#39; problem.</p><blockquote><p> A third way of looking at the cost of individual crimes is listing all the possible costs, both monetary and non-monetary, and both individual and society-wide, and then totting them up. One <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/journal-of-benefit-cost-analysis/article/abs/incidence-and-costs-of-personal-and-property-crimes-in-the-usa-2017/37CD0589C84DAEF0FEC415645A6D7977">study</a> digs through existing estimates of mental health costs, productivity losses to society, use of public services, the courts, quality of life, and so on, to come up with an estimate.</p><p> ……</p><p> This methodology finds murders cause $7.8m of harm.</p></blockquote><p> This seems like a lower bound if you do it technically correctly, causing a temptation to do it wrong, since a lot of the negative impact of crime is the impact on what happens to life in general even when not directly involving crime <em>–</em> the OP also makes this point in its conclusion. A huge percentage of the cost of crime is our worries about and (highly reasonable and often even wise!) obsessions with avoiding and preventing murders, rapes, thefts, frauds and so on. Spaces where one does not have to worry about such things are <em>so</em> much better, often feeling downright sacred, even when the worry doesn&#39;t materialize.</p><blockquote><p> A fourth method is looking at house prices. Crime tends to be extremely local.</p><p> ……</p><p> A random, unscientific approach shows <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.zillow.com/homedetails/1730-S-Desplaines-St-1-Chicago-IL-60616/2120915761_zpid/">very</a> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.zillow.com/homedetails/1612-S-Union-Ave-APT-1-Chicago-IL-60616/89911865_zpid/">similar</a> properties on Zillow worth $100,000 more just for walking two minutes past the underpass.</p></blockquote><p> Housing prices feel more accurate in the sense that they reveal true preferences, with the problem that so many things are so tightly correlated with crime rates. When the murder rate is sixty times higher across the county line, so are many other things <em>.</em></p><blockquote><p> Turning that property differential into a value per murder is difficult. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://doi.org/10.1111/1475-4932.12118">One study</a> looks at property in Sydney, Australia: they find an individual murder causes a roughly four percent drop in property prices within a 0.2 mile radius. Calculating roughly, I reckon there are about 1,000 properties in one of those circles on average across Sydney, where properties are worth an average of <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2022/mar/02/median-home-price-could-fall-below-1m-in-sydney-and-about-700000-in-melbourne-next-year#:~:text=In%20Sydney%2C%20the%20median%20house,year%20and%209%25%20next%20year.&amp;text=Once%20that%20is%20expanded%20to,median%20price%20now%20is%20%241%2C116%2C219.">A$1.1m</a> , or $750,000. That would imply a capitalized value of $30m.</p></blockquote><p> I am guessing this particular methodology is flawed. A particular murder directly lowering prices is acting in part through updates on the expected number of future murders, but if that is true why is the effect so localized? My guess is a lot of this is people acting irrationally, the way people talk about haunted houses and don&#39;t want to live in a house where there was a murder – the whole thing freaks people out, and there&#39;s a kind of blameworthiness or &#39;why accept this trouble&#39; vibe. I&#39;d be more inclined to measure this through changes that alter reasonably expected future crime rates. The obvious candidate as a player of city simulation games is to look at the distribution of police, perhaps, although that also has other effects.</p><p> What does this all add up to?</p><blockquote><p> One of the studies I tackle earlier has done this for the USA, adding up their estimated social cost for every crime, both recorded and reported. They use cost estimates that are about in the middle of the range for individual crimes. Their central estimate is that crime costs America $2.6 trillion annually, mostly coming from violent crime. This is about 12 percent of US GDP. By this metric, it would be, in GDP terms, one of the US&#39;s biggest problems, on par with <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.worksinprogress.co/issue/the-housing-theory-of-everything/">housing</a> . For a country like the UK with a murder rate about five times lower, the problem is probably about five times smaller.</p><p> I actually think the American problem is considerably bigger than this estimate, because this study only includes the costs of crimes that actually get committed. However, people try their damnedest to avoid being the victims of crime. This leads to many extremely socially costly behaviors.</p></blockquote><p> Asking &#39;what is the cost of crime&#39; is both at the same time highly interesting and a wrong or wrongly worded question. What is the alternative world? A world with zero real crime, in the sense that there was no theft, no fraud, no rape, no murder, no assault and so on, no matter how tempting the situation, would look very different from our own. I would happily pay far above 12% of GDP to live in that world, and would expect to end up with higher net GDP very quickly as people took advantage of the new opportunities – it is so much easier to Do Things worth doing, productive things, in that kind of world.</p><p> I would also note that I disagree with OP in the percentage of the gains here on violent versus non-violent crime. Knowing you are safe from non-violent crime is a truly phenomenally big game, especially if that is broadly construed and effectively means that you can trust other people&#39;s representations and promises. That is much more valuable than protection against violent crime, unless perhaps if it came with protection from the government as well.</p><h4> The Quest for Mundane Utility</h4><p> Because it is built on Vimeo, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/EmmaTolkin/status/1693539208663900192">you can search a Criterion movie for exact words and it will take you straight to that spot</a> .</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/todayyearsoldig/status/1693445382376927470">Wait, you can turn a purse into a backpack this easily (30 second video)?</a></p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattrickard/status/1688747891102560256">Can confirm this seems to work.</a></p><blockquote><p> Barack Obama&#39;s career advice: Just learn how to get stuff done. What I mean by that is I&#39;ve seen at every level people who are very good at describing problems, people who are very sophisticated at explaining why something went wrong or why something can&#39;t get fixed. But, what I&#39;m always looking for is, no matter how small the problem or big it is, somebody who says, &#39;Let me take care of that.&#39; If you project an attitude of whatever it is that&#39;s needed, I can handle it, and I can do it. Whoever is running that organization will notice.</p></blockquote><p> With the caveat that if you want to be President of the United States, that is not going to work. For most of us, go for it.</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1689001366176530432">Paul Graham agrees:</a> If you want to make money from your own company or from working for someone else&#39;s, the high bit of advice is the same: learn to build things.</p></blockquote><p> If you can both build stuff and get stuff done? Now we&#39;re talking.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/nntaleb/status/1688524356891054080">Nassim Nicholas Taleb offers his components of True Wealth</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Taleb: True Wealth (2nd Edition)</p><p> Worriless sleeping</p><p> Clear conscience</p><p> Reciprocal gratitude</p><p> Absence of envy</p><p> Foamy coffee</p><p> Crusty bread</p><p> Inexperienced enemies</p><p> Frequent laughs</p><p> No meals alone</p><p> No gym classes</p><p> Gravel bicycling</p><p> Good digestive functions</p><p> No Zoom meetings</p><p> Periodic surprises</p><p> Nothing to hide: financial and fiscal tranquility</p><p> Muscular strength &amp; endurance</p><p> Ability to nap</p><p> Access to a hammock</p><p> 3rd Edition: You don&#39;t envy anyone for anything.</p></blockquote><p> This is a very particular list. Many of these I would actively reverse. In many ways I want Worthy Opponents, not inexperienced enemies. I want walks, not gravel bicycling. I want good water, not foamy coffee. I want tranquility and the lack of a schedule, not no meals alone. Others on this list seems vital and very good.</p><p> There are also the things that are conspicuously missing. I would include something like ability to work on important, interesting and challenging problems, ability to follow curiosity, lack of scheduling. There is also nothing here about romance or sex, and especially nothing about family or children. Any list of true wealth without children seems at best highly incomplete.</p><p> If you are willing to go into a trade like carpentry or plumbing, you can earn a good wage and be for now safe from automation. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.npr.org/2023/01/05/1142817339/america-needs-carpenters-and-plumbers-try-telling-that-to-gen-z">Except no one is interested</a> , which is why it is paying so well.</p><blockquote><p> NPR: The application rate for young people seeking technical jobs — like plumbing, building and electrical work — dropped by 49% in 2022 compared to 2020, according to data from online recruiting platform Handshake shared with NPR.</p><p> ……</p><p> While postings for those roles — automotive technicians, equipment installers and respiratory therapists, to name a few — saw on average 10 applications each in 2020, they got about five per posting in 2022.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/JigarShahDC/status/1694303470382174653">Jigar Shah</a> : For those who don&#39;t want to go to college, you can get meaningful work paying a fair wage in the trades. Because of the #InflationReductionAct we need to train 1,000,000 folks this decade, you get paid while you train and can make six figures.</p><p> Because the training is done while folks get paid to work, the number of hours of training can be more than that of universities. It can also deliver labor market outcomes that are competitive with workers with college degrees.</p></blockquote><p> There are jobs that are more intellectually stimulating than the ones on offer here. There are also many jobs for college graduates that are mind-numbing and also that require you to sacrifice your mind while giving you nothing concrete to anchor you to reality and no feeing of accomplishment. Building or fixing physical things lets you see the fruits of your labor, do something obviously helpful, and lets you keep your sanity. You could do so much worse.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/1WriteofPassage/status/1688265484049993728">Suggestion from Write of Passage that you can use prestige as an anti-indicator of opportunity</a> , in writing and elsewhere. If it is not prestigious, no one wants to do it, so you can get paid handsomely for taking on a low-status project like a romance novel. This is similar to not pursuing the dreams everyone has, like game designer and rock star, if you can help it, although that list also includes writer.</p><p> I would however warn that the opposite phenomenon often also applies. There are many circumstances in which high status and high prestige come with high compensation and a better experience, because compensation is primarily socially determined in most places when those involved are not doing business or trade. People strongly think the two must align, value be damned. Thus, one needs to notice the different classes of opportunity. If you write a romance novel and are paid by the sale, you can get paid above your social standing, so that works. If your pay was linked to your job title, that would not work.</p><h4> Opportunity Knocks</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.magnificentgrants.com/">Magnificent Grants offers $100k fellowships to 10 or more people under 25 years old every year</a> , in exchange for dropping out of your current college, school or job, to help them break free of other pressures. Deadline this year is October 31. It is a pure grant, if you are thinking of applying you likely should do so.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1695596853864321055">Paul Graham wants to fund an eye-tracking startup</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Paul Graham: Want to start a startup doing eye-tracking? If so I&#39;d be interested in funding it. A friend of mine has ALS and can only move his eyes. He has an eye-controlled keyboard, but it&#39;s not very good. Can you make him a better one?</p><p> The reason this is worth doing as a startup is that I think eye-tracking may turn out to have broader applications than it currently does. It may even be a component of the next form factor in computing, the nature of which is still strangely unclear.</p><p> You have to be based in the Bay Area for me to fund you, because I want my friend to be your initial guinea pig. He&#39;s up for it. And he has a technical background, so he&#39;ll understand when the early versions don&#39;t work.</p><p> If you&#39;re interested, please reply to this thread, ideally with a link to something that proves you know about eye-tracking or related subjects, and I&#39;ll DM you.</p><p> Saturin Pugnet: I have worked extensively on similar topics at Worldcoin when working on the orb. I would be happy to offer advice where it is helpful. I am quite fond of this idea and have contemplated the endless possibilities of a high-performance eye-to-computer interface for a while now. I&#39;d love to see this project materialize.</p></blockquote><p> I would worry that the Apple Vision Pro means that eye-tracking is highly advanced or potentially a solved problem already. That helps Paul&#39;s friend if and only if they get their hands on an actual product, but trying to get hold of one early would be the first thing I would try.</p><h4> Good News, Everyone</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://spinespresso.substack.com/p/we-finally-have-a-strikeroom-temperature">LK99 around the world as real science done right</a> , despite LK99 itself turning out not to be a superconductor.</p><p> The value of the obvious:</p><blockquote><p> Roon: When successful people tweet obvious sounding things it&#39;s higher value than it seems. there are a lot of obvious sounding things that aren&#39;t true so if it comes from [Paul Graham] or whoever it&#39;s nice to have simple principles that are highly likely to be true.</p><p> Paul Graham: Obvious-sounding things aren&#39;t all equally obvious. There are a lot of statements that seem obvious when you hear them, and yet which few people have actually stated explicitly.</p></blockquote><p> The implication is that what the world needs are successful people noticing which obvious principles they are not so confident in, not merely the ones they are confident are false. It is difficult to say &#39;I have no proof or anything but I am suspicious that [X] is not actually true&#39; for obvious-seeming or standard-banal things, such as my recent statement &#39;I suspect mindfulness is a scam,&#39; but such statements are useful evidence if taken in the spirit offered.</p><p> A good example of the obvious from a successful person is <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/FoundersPodcast/status/1697400330001031317">Steve Jobs pointing out that asking for help is a superpower</a> , you can ask people for help, including famous and powerful people you have zero connection to, and often you will get it, with very little downside.</p><p> It won&#39;t convince anyone that Americans have the best food, but I strongly agree with Patrick McKenzie that <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/patio11/status/1698843541496271103">the food court is a wonderful innovation</a> , a vast improvement in variety, choice and satisfying a group over having to go to a place in the generic middle. It is almost always fast and cheap, and what hits your spot is often remarkably good at punching above its weight. We are also starting to see actively good places make it into food courts, such as Mighty Quinn&#39;s BBQ or Dos Torros.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://academic.oup.com/pnasnexus/article/2/8/pgad264/7242446?login=false">Study provides strong evidence</a> that YouTube&#39;s algorithm, rather than leading people down extremist holes, does the opposite. YouTube wants you to watch centrist or left-leaning videos, will grudgingly serve you right-leaning videos, and will require a lot of convincing to give you far-left or far-right content, while being happy to switch back to its preferred affiliations if you show any inclination to do so. If you create a new account, it will be half centrist and half moderate-left with only a small amount of moderate-right. As is the case with AI, they stack the deck in favor of the boring conventional thing, and the conventional people complain that the stacking is not 100% effective.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/alexgarcia_atx/status/1689820994284793858">Claim that Barbie&#39;s marketing succeeded in part because Mattel made it cheap and easy to collaborate on licensed products</a> , as opposed to Hasbro and others who try to extract lots of money and retain careful creative control. As always, when you have a good product, the things you do with it look good, which makes it hard to tell what other things were actually good or would transfer. This was also a much easier opportunity, because the tie-ins were essentially the color pink. You don&#39;t need to be that careful with a color.</p><p> Are college towns getting worse? <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/aarmlovi/status/1691890845123780867">Or is everything else getting better, making college towns less unique?</a></p><blockquote><p> Aaron Renn: Somebody should write an article on the decline of college towns. They used to have cool and unique things you couldn&#39;t get anywhere else. Now they are just outposts of generic creative class urbanism mostly inferior to living in a real city.</p><p> Alex Armlovich: In the 1990s nadir, large Rust Belt cities like Buffalo had ~1 good coffee shop; no full-service groceries; limited dining &amp; retail. You&#39;d have been better off in a tiny college town Those days are over! College towns still have all the urbanism basics, but Buffalo now has more.</p><p> Ryan Radia: I am old enough to remember the abysmal coffee shop and dining situation of the mid-90s, but no full-service grocery stores in a city the size of Buffalo is wild.</p><p> Alex: It was a huge zoning fight to open Braymiller Market on Ellicott Street, downtown&#39;s first full grocery in living memory, but the online Google reviews complain it&#39;s still smaller than the ones they&#39;re used to driving to.</p></blockquote><p> As far as I can tell this is mostly other places getting better. College towns were living in the future, which is now more evenly distributed. The new unevenly distributed future is online. Meanwhile, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/arpitrage/status/1691956883777564739">college towns are full of NIMBYs</a> , so they stay the same except for higher costs, rather than realizing their potential.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/eigenrobot/status/1695223016781668731">Eigenrobot on the nation&#39;s most extensive attempt at government censorship</a> , of abolitionists calling for the end of slavery. If your response to this is that this is all the more reason why we must censor the bad people, perhaps think harder.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/bryan_caplan/status/1695649824467497194">I am not alone, almost half of us each less than three meals in a typical day.</a></p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F06e5cea1-2500-497c-919c-9439e645cdb0_805x424.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/wtfgyyyws9yyktdryrng" alt=""></a></figure><p> Did the reality meet your expectations? <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/bryan_caplan">Bryan Caplan</a> investigates this as well.</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fc36bab81-b746-4617-bdad-dbbf26238e6b_980x1348.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/sexdexssycjrvo7w9lkl" alt=""></a></figure><p> Some survivorship bias is presumably involved. Still, update in favor of things likely turning out better than you expected on a personal level, and especially that parenthood is likely to exceed your expectations.</p><h4> Money Stuff</h4><p> Small businesses less likely to be planning price increases, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TheStalwart/status/1688858770326036480">most of the way back to their previous baseline</a> . Feels like an excellent sanity check on the statistics.</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fae733b09-cb6f-4018-8d1f-a602503a25cf_1444x998.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/zmchl2fjb3ct5ljhz3sz" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2023-08-07/us-economy-is-strong-so-americans-should-stop-worrying-about-it?utm_source=website&amp;utm_medium=share&amp;utm_campaign=twitter?sref&amp;sref=htOHjx5Y">More generally, Tyler Cowen notes that all the economic statistics look very good</a> , which they do with the exception of the deficit and debt. He says the American economy is great, stop worrying about it.</p><p> In particular, he says stop worrying about the risk of recession, good times do not inevitably beget bad times except insofar as there will always be occasional bad times. I fully agree with this. Recessions are very hard to predict and the good economic news makes the next one more likely to take longer to arrive.</p><p> Where we perhaps disagree is that I do not think the statistics are sufficient evidence that the economy is doing great. Inflation is improving but remains above target even before the need to return to the trend line. Interest rates are high. Both of these have a big practical impact on regular people. Meanwhile, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/growth-models-and-new-goods.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=growth-models-and-new-goods">no matter how much economists point out the availability of new or higher quality goods</a> , people continue to not thrive in the ways that most matter. Nor do I think that a large share of savings have ever been well-explained, as <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://philiptrammell.com/static/New_Products_and_Long_term_Welfare.pdf">the paper linked</a> suggests, by anticipated superior future product offerings. Beware, one might say, the dangers of calculating welfare as the cumulative value of goods, while losing sight of holistic affordances.</p><p> Tyler then reiterates his emphasis that congestion pricing should be differentially applied only to residents of an area and not to visitors. It is bizarre to pick this particular scarce good where there is large disutility to overconsumption, and to want to price it lower to those who one thinks get more utility out of it, claiming this improves efficiency. Why is our default not that prices solve exactly this problem? If not, does it not indict the general concept of allocation by price? What other differentiated taxation and pricing regimes based on centrally planned beliefs about available utility would this principle favor?</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/peterevoss/status/1695428688672596109">We have another study claiming that the impact of climate change on world GDP will be minimal</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Peter Voss: A *very* comprehensive climate and human welfare peer-reviewed article:</p><p> “Climate change is real and its impacts are mostly negative, but common portrayals of devastation are unfounded. Scenarios set out under the UN Climate Panel (IPCC) show human welfare will likely increase to 450% of today&#39;s welfare over the 21st century. Climate damages will reduce this welfare increase to 434%. “</p><p> “Climate policies also have costs that often vastly outweigh their climate benefits. The Paris Agreement, if fully implemented, will cost $819–$1,890 billion per year in 2030, yet will reduce emissions by just 1% of what is needed to limit average global temperature rise to 1.5°C. Each dollar spent on Paris will likely produce climate benefits worth 11¢. “</p></blockquote><p> I agree that we have to do the math and figure out what makes or doesn&#39;t make economic sense to do. And that we are currently both ignoring very good mitigation opportunities, and implementing or considering some highly inefficient mitigation strategies.</p><p> However. Bullshit. That size of impact does not make any sense. Even if the GDP calculations are correct and the counterfactual was meaningful, that does not mean human welfare, and this is a case where those two things obviously are vastly different.</p><p> Assuming for the moment that AI peters out and the world still mostly exists as normal otherwise, I would much rather live in a world that was 400% of today&#39;s GDP and did not have any further warming, than one with 450% of today&#39;s GDP and had the baseline non-intervention levels of warming, even measured only by direct impact on lived experience of it being too damn hot.</p><p> Hell, I would expect the purely psychological impacts of climate change and fear of climate change, including on fertility, to on their own (excluding the actual physical downsides) already have baked in a more than 4% impact on world GDP (to say nothing of mental health or actual human welfare) by 2100, again in the &#39;normal AGI-less world&#39; scenario. One could argue the cognitive effects of high CO2 levels on their own will cost more than 4% of GDP. That does not even touch on the bigger impacts, or the tail risks, or the secondary effects.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1688401325141409794">How false is the efficient market hypothesis?</a></p><blockquote><p> Paul Graham: Talking to people running public companies has made me realize there is always going to be money to be made in the public markets, because prices are set by buyers who&#39;ve only done the most superficial analyses.</p></blockquote><p> The price is set by a combination of all supply and demand. If the price got sufficiently out of whack, those with better knowledge would come in to correct it. They would however need to be compensated enough to make this worth doing. So yes, being good at this will make you money.</p><h4> Our Price Cheap</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/murugan-idli.html#comment-160638661">Tyler Cowen asks for a general model of why, so often in the world of food, price and quality are negatively correlated</a> .</p><p> My model is that restaurants can only mostly care about and focus on one thing. If it is the quality of the food, then they are unlikely to profit maximize and look to charge more, and they will look to find locations and other ways to keep prices down rather than ways to raise prices up. They also will choose circumstances that put them under less pressure to charge more, and less pressure to in turn do the things that justify charging more. Whereas places that are maximizing profits will not focus relentlessly on quality of the food. One could also say that only high quality food will, in many places, let underpriced offerings exist.</p><p> This only applies if you control for the places where quality runs in the obvious direction, and have the right baseline. Quality of ingredients matters a lot, if you are not charging enough to afford good ones, or you are outright competing on price on the low end such as fast food places like McDonald&#39;s, or generic places like the &#39;99 cents pizza&#39; shops, then this will catch up to you. Prices that are too low are red flags if you care about quality, as it is another sign that what is being focused on is the price. Chains are using various means to drive down price and value standards and reliability rather than quality, so once they reach industrial scale they generally need to be excluded from this kind of heuristic.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/on-the-negative-correlation-between-price-and-restaurant-quality.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=on-the-negative-correlation-between-price-and-restaurant-quality">This explanation</a> from a different reader focuses on the demand side rather than the supply side. Demand here has customers who want comfort, who want something fashionable and who want good food, but there is little overlap between them, and those who want good food will often learn to cook it themselves. Unless someone actively seeks good food, quality beyond a baseline threshold is mostly wasted.</p><p> In this model, PF Chang&#39;s is competing not with the quality family Chinese restaurant, but with Applebee&#39;s, and willingness to pay is mostly about atmosphere not food quality. Thus the negative correlation.</p><p> I definitely can see this model. Some days I want the best possible food. Other days I want comfort food more, something I am familiar with and know is good. That still often looks like something out of Tyler&#39;s ethnic dining guide, although not always. Rarely I will care so much about atmosphere beyond a basic threshold, but I&#39;ll still do what I can to maximize food quality, and I have a small rotation of places for such times that I know work well.</p><p> The two explanations combine well. Demand is segmented, and supply is also segmented, so it is doubly hard to combine high quality in all areas at once, and the food quality demand curve is lower.</p><p> Another note is that over time, if one seeks good food, this changes what one considers a good atmosphere, because your associations build up.</p><p> If you want to take advantage of this correlation, you need to control for what things should cost, and know what discount levels are good and which are suspicious.</p><h3> The Efficient Market Hypothesis is False</h3><p> Here&#39;s a paper: <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://deliverypdf.ssrn.com/delivery.php?ID=403118115089092092009023079088111018098035091034011074117083030026114021126072093028033027032044109027040110082094006065094119103082007012011089108001007126105087108007015042092103086100027091098127089089102119028080064074031086072120019029069072091089&amp;EXT=pdf&amp;INDEX=TRUE">Do firms bunch at EEOC kink points? Implications for firm value under exogenous risk</a> . Abstract and highlights:</p><blockquote><p> On July 14, 1992, the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) implemented enforcement guidance for compensatory and punitive damages available under section 102 of the Civil Rights Act of 1991. In this policy, the EEOC caps litigation payouts to $50,000, $100,000, $200,000, and $300,000 for firms with 15 to 100 employees, 101 to 200 employees, 201 to 500 employees, and 501 employees or more, respectively. I implement a threshold design around these EEOC enforcement kink points to examine (i) if firms bunch at these thresholds, (ii) the impact of bunching on firm value, and (iii) why firm value changes for firms that bunch. I find evidence that firms do indeed bunch at EEOC kink points. Bunching firms have negative annualized alphas of 14.88%, negative annualized raw stock returns of 7.26%, and negative Tobin&#39;s Q values of 9.44%. Workforce rigidity around exogenous risk explains why bunching firms have negative market values.</p><p> ……</p><p> After the EEOC enacted the policy, the number of firms bunching at enforcement kink points increased by 25%. I find that firms that bunch at EEOC kink points are in industries and states with higher levels of civil litigation cases.</p><p> Next, I find that firms that bunch at EEOC kink points have lower firm value. Creating a portfolio of firms that bunch at 14, 100, 200, and 500 employees generate annualized value-weighted alphas of negative 14.88% that is statistically significant at the 1% level with a t-statistic of 2.87. In a FM model using a sample of firms with a number of employees in the range of 14 to 20, 100 to 106, 200 to 206, and 500 to 506, firms that bunch at the EEOC thresholds of 14, 100, 200, and 500 employees have annualized returns of negative 7.26% compared to firms that do not bunch, which is statistically significant at the 5% level with a t-statistic of 2.11.</p><p> ……</p><p> Additionally, I find that firms that bunch decrease their investment per employee, suggesting that firms are under-investing in their workforce.</p></blockquote><p> These effects are <em>crazy</em> large. If the number of firms at kink points is 25% higher than expected, that means that <em>80% of them are not doing it on purpose.</em> If a group that is 80% controls has <em>negative 7.26% annualized returns</em> compared to the control group, well, you do the math.</p><p> Also note that this group is real and bigger than one might expect, but in absolute terms it is also small. We are talking about roughly 1% of the relevant employee count ranges (4 spots out of 506), so there is intentional bunching found in maybe 0.2% of firms. There likely are very big selection effects in the intentional group.</p><p> (How much employment is lost here? Presumably not so many, since a firm that naturally wants <em>a lot</em> more employees wouldn&#39;t let the cap stop them. It would be reasonable to say on average something like 2 employees if you&#39;re at 14, maybe 5 if you&#39;re at 100 and so on, so maybe these firms are let&#39;s say… 8% under-employing? But with these kinds of returns, that won&#39;t last long. Still, they get replaced by other similar firms. So a snapshot says 0.2% times 8% is 0.00016%, or 1.6bps, or something like 20,000 total jobs in mostly lousy places to work.)</p><p> What is most interesting here is that there is a self-identified subgroup of small firms that, when you take out the intermixed controls, has <em>massive, massive</em> negative returns.</p><p> Which makes sense. If you are limiting your employee count to stay under a liability threshold, you are telling me several things.</p><ol><li> You are worried about your liability.</li><li> You are not that interested in having more employees.</li><li> You are the type to game the system rather than produce value.</li></ol><p> It is not a great leap to think such firms would underperform. It is however a great leap that they&#39;d collapse <em>this quickly</em> in value.</p><p> This seems like it would show definitively that some firms are making <em>really bad</em> decisions. It is not best practices or efficient to incur a bunch of discrimination liability. It is not efficient to do the other things this group does, as evidenced by the results. Yet I get people claiming that businesses mostly do the efficient, sensible thing for them, they would never do something like have bullshit jobs on their payroll.</p><p> Alas, it is difficult (read: impossible) to short firms with only 500 or fewer employees. What you <em>can</em> do is <em>avoid being long.</em> Thus, if you had a basket of investments that returned market rates, and then you tossed out 1% of it and that 1% was previously underperforming by 7%, you get a modest performance bump. On its own it isn&#39;t much, but you can repeat the process with other attributes or signals.</p><p> One can also note that small firms seem to be implied to have negative 7% alpha <em>in general?</em> What&#39;s up with that? Seems like an impossible result. Or at least a highly bold claim. If it was true, then the valuations of such firms would be Obvious Nonsense.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/MattBruenig/status/1624959768862380033">Another symbolic example.</a></p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F9308f395-ea0d-4f00-ae1a-60d3f1c77d6d_1141x285.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/hznn6fivoz67js2wlbfp" alt=""></a></figure><p> In the Super Bowl, it was clear that the Eagles could call a QB sneak and it would <em>always</em> work. They lined up in a formation that was certain to be a QB sneak. They did the same physical thing every time. It worked every time. Yet in situations where doing this twice or three times in a row would make sense, it is almost never used.</p><p>为什么？ And given that it doesn&#39;t happen in such a competitive situation where the math is so easy, why should we expect <em>anyone else</em> to be doing the right things?</p><h4> Prediction Market Hypothesis</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TetraspaceWest/status/1688824783318773761">Problems in prediction markets</a> : What to do if you want to do something if and only if chances of success are above 30%, but if you entrust the market with this decision then the correlation between it being a good idea and you doing it weakens, messing up the market? And how often do you have to f*** around in order to find out when it ends up below 30%? I&#39;d say you shouldn&#39;t take the market as your only evidence, so you&#39;ll sometimes try when it is below 30% or not try when above, and that&#39;s fine?</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://manifold.markets/calibration">Manifold markets are reasonably well calibrated overall</a> , but it is still smart to mostly be betting no.</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F418b7d2a-c11e-4e65-80e2-a7887cbdcfee_1072x1029.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/rl0xr8sglhwvelhqg5sj" alt=""></a></figure><p> This diverges from other prediction markets, where it is standard for the yes side to have the edge above 40% or so, here you want to be on the no side all the way.</p><p> That is especially true for the Free Money markets, that second dot on the left. Those are markets where the outcome is known or all but known, but that won&#39;t formally resolve for a while, so capital costs keep the price above zero. People who have yes shares hold on to them partly for fun or hope, partly in case some no holders need to free up capital. The loan mechanism helps somewhat, but in practice only somewhat.</p><p> This is proving a problem in particular for the superconductor markets. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://manifold.markets/QuantumObserver/will-the-lk99-room-temp-ambient-pre">The main one is still trading at 8%</a> as I write this, whereas Metaculus is down at a far more reasonable 1%. This is despite the fact that every day I take my loan money and put it back into the market, I now have more than my entire Manifold balance on this. We will see how far that gets to snowball over time.</p><h4> Modest Proposals</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.fillandflush.com/">The Fill and Flush method of plane clearing</a> is one of many options all vastly superior to the current highly inefficient method. We are almost maximally bad at getting people off of planes, yet the mild social awkwardness of a systematic method, combined with not wanting to mess with &#39;lower row number privilege&#39; or something, keeps us from changing. I would give substantial priority to any airline that fixed this.</p><h4> FDA Delenda Est</h4><p> The FDA requires labels. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/pitdesi/status/1690011798643056640">They are not especially sticklers for accuracy, in some spots.</a></p><blockquote><p> Sheel Mohnot: Tic Tacs are 94% sugar and yet claim to be sugar free… The FDA says anything can be labeled sugar free if it has &lt;0.5g of sugar, so each tic tac is 0.49g and they can claim they have 0 sugar on the label</p><p> Alex Cohen: You literally cannot trust anyone or anything.</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F41080d91-69fd-4bfb-acf3-79e91c2fff43_679x680.webp" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/adk5n15agaarwqoye1pv" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> Requiring such labels seems fine, but if you do that then you need people to be able to rely on them. These are rather obnoxious technical loopholes. I am not mad at those who take advantage, that is the game, but then once it comes to your attention you need to patch the bug.</p><p> It is much worse when the <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robinsonmeyer/status/1690090114783866881">FDA does things like regulate sunscreen as a drug</a> , making developing new ones prohibitively expensive, and resulting in us having far inferior sunscreen to other countries. AOC films a video to ask Congress to fix this specific failure, without any sign that she has realized the principle might generalize.</p><p> It is still good to notice this in one place, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/IDoTheThinking/status/1690435322843426816">especially given the price to be paid for noticing</a> .</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/JacquesPierreJP/status/1690478131637784576">Jacques Pierre</a> : Every other congressman is posting like “Loved the cranberry festival this weekend! I&#39;ll work tirelessly to ensure the Cranberry Fund stays in the farm bill!” and gets 7 likes AOC posts “It would be better if fewer people got skin cancer” and gets dogpiled by her own people lmao.</p><p> Scott Castle (one of two replies): It&#39;s the business owner who will benefit financially from this change that&#39;s concerning. We wouldn&#39;t love a GOP Member pitching FDA deregulation to benefit a medical device in a twitter video with the owner of a company that would benefit.</p></blockquote><p> These criticisms seem related to <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://freddiedeboer.substack.com/p/let-me-reiterate-the-questions-i">the phenomenon Freddie DeBoer notes</a> here, where he criticizes (from a left perspective) several of AOC specific actions and gets lots of criticism, also from a left perspective, about the symbolism of AOC as a person but no response to his substantive critiques and questions. In both cases, substantive criticism pointing out ineffectiveness of decisions is responded to on only the symbolic, whose-side-is-this-on-or-how-does-this-vibe mostly <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://thezvi.substack.com/p/simulacra-levels-summary#:~:text=Level%201%3A%20There's%20a%20lion,undecided%20voters%20in%20my%20constituency.">third and sometimes fourth simulacra levels</a> . Whereas a key reason why AOC and Freddie are worth paying attention to and might accomplish something is that they are capable of, to their great credit, asking what a given physical action might result in, and even in insisting others ask such questions.</p><p> I also loved this exchange:</p><blockquote><p> AOC: Last week, the @NYCSanitation did a night raid of the street vendors in Corona Plaza — a special place in our district that&#39;s a hub of culture &amp; cuisine. This enforcement served no one. It confiscated vendors&#39; property, shut down &amp; spread fear in this immigrant community.</p><p> Currently, the waitlist for vendor licenses is so long it&#39;s been closed for over a decade. We need to increase licenses, rather than punish people just trying to provide for themselves &amp; their families. Small business owners shouldn&#39;t be penalized for government failures.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/jaredpolis/status/1691604420793163861">Jared Polis</a> (D-Governor of Colorado): Thank you AOC for standing up for free-market capitalism and small businesses against a bureaucratic statist attack and government seizure of assets.</p></blockquote><h4> In Medical and Health News</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/venkmurthy/status/1688873935469711361">Semaglutide not only causes you to lose weight</a> , it is confirmed that it in turn reduces risk from composite of heart attack, stroke, &amp; cardiovascular death in patients without diabetes but with a history of CVD who are overweight or obese. It is hard to see it could have been otherwise, still good to confirm and magnitude of 20% reduction is big. Results like this will likely make weight loss drugs increasingly standard treatments.</p><p> You can now sign up for a <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/alyssamvance/status/1694093972606456063">human challenge trial for malaria</a> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://t.co/N0GbHIk2Y6">(direct link)</a> . They pay $5,400, but you are hopefully not doing this for the money. Amazing that we are getting our act together on this.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/alyssamvance/status/1692399530711437321">News you can&#39;t use</a> without a prescription, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Celecoxib">about Celecoxib</a> .</p><p> 25 years ago, they invented a better version of Advil, which targets the same receptor but with fewer side effects. It still requires a prescription for basically no reason.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/excess-all-cause-mortality-in-china-after-ending-the-zero-covid-policy.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=excess-all-cause-mortality-in-china-after-ending-the-zero-covid-policy">China had 1.87 million excess deaths in the two months after Covid zero ended</a> , distributed as you would expect. That is something like 0.14% of the population.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2023/aug/08/england-to-deny-covid-and-flu-jabs-to-under-65s-amid-fears-for-nhs-this-winter">Britain to only offer Coid and flu shots to those 65 and older this winter</a> . This seems categorically insane, if you are paying all health costs and not offering free flu shots you are in a downward spiral that I have no idea how to recover from.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/left-digit-bias-in-medicine.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=left-digit-bias-in-medicine">Medicine has a modest left digit bias problem</a> , where people place too much emphasis on the first digit of numbers, so things such as being age 39 vs. 40 gets you treated differently. Measured size seems if anything smaller than I would have expected, so that is good news. Heuristics are important, a little inefficiency here seems fine. As post notes it can be used to measure the effects of medical interventions if you can control for other left digit effects.</p><p> Estimate from a paper that <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/the-impact-of-vaccines-and-behavior-on-u-s-cumulative-deaths-from-covid-19.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-impact-of-vaccines-and-behavior-on-u-s-cumulative-deaths-from-covid-19">Covid vaccines saved about 750,000 American lives</a> , most of which would have been impossible without at least some continued mitigation efforts throughout 2020 and early 2021. One can argue either way whether that was enough to justify various mitigations.</p><p> How did you do on Covid in terms of preventing deaths as measured by excess mortality? Why did Sweden do exceptionally well? <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/jmhorp/status/1696703947422007643">Because mostly only one thing mattered, which was vaccination rates</a> .</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fcbd6feca-7db0-4772-97b0-aaaf4c7e56dd_1023x744.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/xyli2xz7r13woqzszs7h" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1689646760548077569">And yet we somehow really, really messed up with the vaccine marketing, didn&#39;t we</a> ?</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1689646760548077569">Matthew Yglesias:</a> The Covid vaccine (not vaccine mandates, the vaccine itself) is less popular than mask mandates.</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fb92da83b-6095-4dd2-a69e-85bfd03b00b2_3062x1552.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/smlitflizqqw67wlspgk" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> Retrospective support for mask mandates remains strong at 63%, whereas only 55% think the vaccine was a critical advancement rather than rushed.</p><p> The hint is the next question. What is the approval rate of the vaccine at all? 55%. What is the approval rate of a vaccine mandate? Also 55%.</p><p> People literally, flat out, cannot draw a distinction between a choice and a mandate, that which is not forbidden is compulsory and that which is forbidden is not allowed, and that is it.</p><p> If nothing but vaccination mattered much for excess mortality, then that suggests strongly that, within the range of realistic responses, the correct answer was otherwise to be as light handed as possible.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/calebwatney/status/1695096478803308582">Multiple scientists and industry insiders insisted the probability of success for mRNA vaccines be set to zero</a> , because anything else would be wildly miscalibrated. This was not years earlier, this was early on during Covid. Everyone involved must go to Bayes Hell.</p><p> The classic story of how <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20230419071607/https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2023/05/ice-cream-bad-for-you-health-study/673487/">ice cream is shown time and again to be healthy and associated with a reduced risk of diabetes</a> , so nutrition scientists first try everything to make the finding go away, making up bizarre stories including reverse causation, then when they not only won&#39;t go away but replicate the scientists say nuh-uh and blatantly lie to us that such effects only belong to foods like yogurt so we can properly suffer for our good health. Every time nutrition science seems like it couldn&#39;t get any more confusing and unhelpful, there you go. I have long since settled into not trusting any of it beyond the supreme basics at most, and trusting my own lived experiences instead.</p><p> The reverse causation hypothesis here is that ice cream is known to be bad for you, so if you are in poor health your doctor will talk you out of eating it, so now it only seems healthy. Which is such Obvious Nonsense all around, as is noted in the article you do not see this effect for cake or cookies. If anything, someone in poor health will tend to increase their intake of relatively easy to consume foods like ice cream. When my uncle was dying of ALS they had him eat tons of ice cream to keep up his caloric intake.</p><p> My alternative hypothesis is that ice cream is efficient. It is not health food, but it gives an extreme amount of joy and symbolic representation of desert, in exchange for a remarkably low health cost. It is substituting for what would typically be much larger caloric quantities of unhealthy starches like cookies and cakes, while still telling you that you have had your special treat. Your balance of consumption shifts in positive ways. So no, if you had ice cream for lunch it would probably make your health situation worse, but that is not how people actually consume it.</p><p> Whereas I am going to go ahead and challenge the causation theories on whole milk versus reduced fat or skim milk. Everyone knows whole milk is superior. So the only reason you would consume reduced fat or skim milk is if you were being sold a bill of goods that it was healthier, and you were willing to actually suffer. Which in turn means you&#39;re probably doing other doctor-recommended things, and especially consuming fewer overall calories.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/St_Rev/status/1691675243604070698">So the WHO seems to be at least somewhat endorsing… homeopathy?</a>搞什么？</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fc489d5b6-b5b4-42af-9b06-d72661c3460e_502x1315.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/kjkwi6bh1nuvx0wwggpo" alt=""></a></figure><blockquote><p> Translation of the community note: Traditional medicines are presented as an alternative without taking into account that the evidence shows their little or no efficacy. In some cases, such as homeopathy, it is not even traditional medicine.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/780538103/0/marginalrevolution~Wednesday-assorted-links.html">Tyler Cowen called his link to this</a> &#39;WHO is a fraud&#39; and, yes, well.</p><p> WHO Delenda Est. My lord.</p><h4> Gamers Gonna Game Game Game Game Game</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://simonm.substack.com/p/musings-on-chess-openings">Analysis of chess openings</a> says 1. e4 e5, while objectively strong at higher levels, underperforms at lower levels, provides other details. I think all of this is Doing It Wrong. If an opening was underperforming by 100+ points of Elo that would be one thing, but these differences are all small. Different openings teach you different things, help you develop in different ways and most of all play different types of games. I always played 1. e4 not because I thought it was an extra +1% to my expectation, but because I enjoy those games more.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mtgbanding/status/1692257440866205944">Phil Nguyen provides Premodern deck pics for all his opponents. What a format</a> . Also yeah, I am sad I won&#39;t ever get to play with it but maybe it was time to ban Land Tax.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/SamuelHBlack/status/1688427833566060544">Sam Black comes for old school.</a> Says Fireball should have been involved somewhere.</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F82cd35c4-d440-4443-9ff4-d6f79b0d0926_1418x2048.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/brgkgsp1zwynw2tejkrn" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.hipstersofthecoast.com/2023/08/old-school-control/">His write-up of his thought process is here</a> . I am confident this would be better if we cut it down to 60, despite concerns over having enough Land Tax targets, there are only four semi-dead cards (Tormod&#39;s Crypt, Millstone and Timetwister, and maybe Recall) that you want to avoid drawing too early and can&#39;t safely cut given Divine Offering exists and you can&#39;t run a cardless alternative damage source like Mishra&#39;s Factory. I agree with Sam that there should be a Fireball somewhere, and Triskelion seems like definitely the wrong creature. My instinctive choice is to keep it old school and choose Serra Angel here.</p><p> If I did find extra space what would I add? I would need to know more about exatly what opponents were out there but my first priority would be access to a second Winter Orb and then a second Wrath of God or The Abyss, or I might think more about beating The Deck in particular.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://eminence.events/articles/resources-and-game-design">Sam Black also shares his thoughts</a> on the playing-cards-facedown-as-lands mechanic. He is against it, as it adds painful decision points and reduces variance.</p><p> Ben Seck is back with deck name (and deck pic!) thread <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TBSdash/status/1692961345698709702">part two</a> . <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TBSdash/status/1691487469215133705">Original thread here</a> .</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/bmkibler/status/1689645126648500225">Brian Kibler makes the case</a> that Wizards needs to be pushing Standard play far harder than they are, which seems right to me. Otherwise, when I play constructed, I am not going to be giving Wizards money and things won&#39;t change over time – others use Commander for this, I&#39;d likely end up in Premodern.</p><p> Angel Hernandez, somehow only the second worst MLB umpire, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://nypost.com/2023/08/15/controversial-umpire-angel-hernandez-loses-major-league-baseball-lawsuit-appeal/?sr_share=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_campaign=nypost_sports">decided to sue MLB over being passed over for crew chief and the world series</a> , charging racial discrimination. Too much discrimination is definitely not his problem.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/eshear/status/1689057037609734145">Not only game design</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Emmett Shear: Deep lesson in game design here.</p><p> Tyler Glaiel: Player has 1% crit chance: Cool, nice bonus when it happens, maybe your tactics change after getting a crit, maybe they don&#39;t Enemy has 1% crit chance: literally every decision the player makes forever needs to consider this event. massive mental burden when planning tactics.</p><p> Its not a bad thing to make the player have to consider odds-based outcomes when planning tactics sometimes, but if that is the intent then keep those odds in the 25-75% range so like, it happens often.</p><p> Anyway yeah the vast majority of enemies in mew have 0% crit chance for this reason (though there are some exceptions!)</p></blockquote><p> A lot of this is an artifact of the player needing to maintain a very high win percentage, and often to avoiding even taking losses. If you are 50% to win a fight, after which you full heal, you cannot afford to be planning too much around 1% (or the more standard 1/16 or 1/20) crit chance in the wrong spot. If you need to win 10 or more fights in a row to finish the level, or a death costs you a lot of progress, not so much. If you&#39;re playing on hardcore in Diablo, you have to assume the absolute worst case scenario, including multiple crits.</p><p> Whereas when you are retrying a boss fight over and over until you win, or you&#39;re playing a roguelike on a level where you expect to lose, or you realize that playing it safe here is otherwise locally doomed, you do the opposite, and try to get lucky.</p><p> Now consider real life. In real life, dead is dead, you need to string together a 99%+ win rate on many fronts and the tail risks of almost every social interaction vastly exceed any potential benefits, with notably rare exceptions that get played very differently.</p><p> Thus it is vitally important to remove the possibility of such tail risks whenever possible, unless this is an impact that you want.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://espnpressroom.com/us/press-releases/2023/08/espn-to-launch-espn-bet-in-a-new-agreement-with-penn-entertainment/">Introducing ESPN Bet,</a> a sportsbook from ESPN. Oh no?哦耶！ There is no world where this goes well, but there are plenty where it is hilarious.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/JoINrbs/status/1697866055660790044">Dota bans 90,000 smurf accounts</a> , meaning alternative second accounts they were able to link back to an original, with plans to sanction the original accounts as well. Many smurfs are used to beat up on weaker players, to be abusive in chat or grief in various ways, or otherwise act in toxic fashion. Whereas they would prefer you pick on someone your own size and remain mindful of your reputation.</p><p> This seems good. In a game this skill testing, and it is massively skill testing, you need to ensure fair matchups and fair play via reputation to get a good experience. However, there is also a legitimate interest in experimenting or relaxing, without having to be &#39;on&#39; all the time, as chess players know well. If your rating is always at risk, you can&#39;t try anything new or different. You can say &#39;well then play unranked&#39; but then conditions are presumably a hellscape, so you then have to assemble the entire lineup for both sides yourself. Alas, this remains an unsolved problem.</p><h4> I Was Promised <s>Flying</s> Self-Driving Cars</h4><p> Self-driving cars got approved for San Francisco.</p><p> What is next? <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/AP/status/1692703000815390919">The driverless bus, of course.</a></p><blockquote><p> San Francisco has launched an autonomous shuttle service — less than a week after <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://apnews.com/article/robotaxis-cruise-waymo-san-francisco-artificial-intelligence-98f0dab03984bd71685b92c2ac7aad0c">California regulators approved the expansion of robotaxis</a> despite traffic and safety concerns.</p><p> The free shuttle will run daily in a fixed route called the Loop around Treasure Island, the site of a former US Navy base in the middle of San Francisco Bay. The Loop makes seven stops, connecting residential neighborhoods with stores and community centers. About 2,000 people live on the island.</p><p> The all-electric vehicle, which doesn&#39;t have a driver&#39;s seat or steering wheel, is staffed with an attendant who can drive the bus with a handheld controller if necessary. The county is offering the shuttle service as part of a grant-funded pilot program to assess how autonomous vehicles can supplement the public transit system.</p><p> “Having the attendant on board makes everyone feel comfortable,” said Tilly Chang, executive director of the San Francisco County Transportation Authority.</p></blockquote><p> Is this our future? A driverless bus, in a loop, with someone paid to sit there and not drive it, forever.</p><p> Sure sounds like it:</p><blockquote><p> “Trained operators are going to be required even as we increase automation,” said Nikolas Martelaro, autonomous-vehicle researcher at Carnegie Mellon University. “So the question there may not be how worried should someone be about losing their job versus what should they be thinking about the potential training that&#39;s required.”</p><p> ……</p><p> “We still have to find a market for them,” said Art Guzzetti, vice president at the American Public Transportation Association. “We&#39;re doing it to make the trip better, more efficient, not to take the worker&#39;s job.”</p></blockquote><p> There is also lots of talk about how this totally is not a replacement for the bus system, only for the first or last mile problem.</p><p> It seems like everyone is determined to ensure that no inefficiencies are lost in the transition to this new technology.</p><p> The San Francisco Board of Supervisors has thus formed a new plan to try and stop autonomous vehicles, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/sdamico/status/1691637218816008591">which is to deny all fleet vehicles access to charging stations</a> .</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.piratewires.com/p/ca-senate-appropriations-approves-ab316">Also California Senate Appropriations Committee unanimously approves Bill AB 316</a> , requiring any vehicle over 10k pounds have a driver physically present at all times on public roads.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TheStalwart/status/1693227588171235550">Joe Weisenthal speculates about who else might not take kindly to the trend</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Joe Weismenthal: There&#39;s going to be an interesting anti-Self Driving Cars coalition of tech-skeptical liberals + conservatives who don&#39;t want to feel captive inside a computer not fully under their control.</p><p> David Weigel: Deleted previous tweet about Chip Roy saying his jeep sometimes goes dead because he pulled out the fuse that controls the seatbelt beep and the headlights – it was such an odd digression that I wanted to check tape and transcribe.</p><p> Chip Roy: I have a Jeep Wrangler. It&#39;s, like, 20-something years old. It&#39;s not quite old enough to be free from some electronics, it&#39;s almost free of them. And you know, the one thing it would do is beep at me, tell me to put my seatbelt on. So I pulled the fuse out, so it won&#39;t beep at me, right?</p><p> And so, every once in a while, I&#39;m driving it around, and I pull out – and it happens when I&#39;m at the airport and park in the parking garage; I pull out and had my headlights on during the day. I go to some restaurant, and meet somebody, and leave the headlights on, and it doesn&#39;t beep at me, because the same fuse controls the lights. And I come out and it&#39;s dead.</p><p> Now, that&#39;s happened, like – maybe every once or twice a year it kind of happens, probably. And every time, my friend might come over to jumpstart it or something. And I say, it&#39;s the price of freedom. Because I just don&#39;t like being told what to do. I wear my seatbelt, but I wear my seatbelt when I damn well please, because I&#39;m a free American.</p></blockquote><p> I mean, that&#39;s not a trade I would have made, but yes the beeping is super annoying and condescending as hell and I too despise it when cars and other things try to punish you into cooperating with their agendas. A fully self-driving car that might get hacked, or that the government might potentially take control over, seems terrifying on many levels. For a taxi it&#39;s fine, for your own car you better be damn sure the override button works and they don&#39;t have an override override of their own. Or you can say the opposite, and put safety or control first, but then yes you are going to have a problem.</p><p> On the liberal side, so far what I am seeing is not tech skepticism so much as fear about job losses, direct opposition to the idea that we might produce higher quality goods while using less labor, combined with safety illiteracy likely motivated by the jobs issue.</p><p> The other weird question I have is, why would you use a beep as your plan to ensure someone doesn&#39;t kill the car battery, as opposed to it turning off on a timer unless you hit the &#39;no I really mean it&#39; button?</p><p> Timothy Lee writes under the headline <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.understandingai.org/p/driverless-cars-may-already-be-safer">driverless cars may already be safer than human driver</a> s, and makes the case that actually we do know, and they are, by going through every single crash history report for Waymo and Cruise in California.</p><blockquote><p> There are two things to notice about this list. First, other vehicles ran into Waymos 28 times, compared to just four times a Waymo ran into another vehicle (and Waymo says its vehicle got cut off in two of these cases). Second, Waymo was only involved in three or four “serious” crashes, and none of them appear to have been Waymo&#39;s fault.</p><p> This is impressive because these statistics reflect more than 2 million miles of driving.</p><p> The National Highway Traffic Safety Board <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://crashstats.nhtsa.dot.gov/Api/Public/Publication/813435">estimates</a> that there are around 6 million car crashes reported to the police each year. Americans drive around 3 trillion miles per year, so roughly speaking a “major” crash occurs on the roads once every 500,000 miles.</p></blockquote><p> Cruise&#39;s history is less impressive, still solid, with three crashes where the Cruise car was clearly at fault that were more serious than any of Waymo&#39;s mistakes, while noting Cruise has clocked more miles. He doesn&#39;t quite say &#39;self-driving cars are safer than human drivers&#39; but I will say it: Self-driving cars are safer than human drivers, sufficiently so that if we previously had self-driving cars no way would we let humans drive a car.</p><p> Having full video of every incident makes it tough to argue. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/daniel_271828/status/1698485148566556936">The New York Times is undaunted</a> , says self-driving car (briefly) delayed ambulance attending to… someone hit by a human driving a car. Yes, it turns out that cars on roads delay other vehicles sometimes. Can you imagine this standard being applied to human drivers? Or if a self-driving car had hit a driver, a human had briefly gotten in the way of the ambulance?</p><h4> While I Cannot Condone This</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/RichardHanania/status/1697644881022435538">The cancellation attempt on Richard Hanaina appears to have failed</a> across the board. More evidence that woke has peaked.</p><p> Chrome now by default using your browser history to show you personalized ads.</p><blockquote><p> Paul Graham: If you go to <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://chrome://settings/adPrivacy">chrome://settings/adPrivacy</a> you can turn off the spyware that got inserted into the latest version of Chrome.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://myadcenter.google.com/customize?ctb=topics&amp;ctf=trends">You can also go here, I believe</a> , which also lets you do more customization.</p><p> Except, good? I love personalized ads. I especially love that I can manually ask for more or less of various categories, including blocking anything I find unpleasant, distracting or likely to get me to buy something I&#39;d regret. I do get that there are people who either want to see the same ads as everyone else, and those who think ads are evil or adversarial so you want them to be as irrelevant as possible. I think they are mostly wrong, or are pointing to a deeper problem they should address, although in some cases the solution will indeed involve blocking some types of ads.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/amasad/status/1695346174738436584">What if Zoom had a button</a> where if all participants press the button then the meeting instantly ends?</p><blockquote><p> Patrick OShaughnessy: There should be a new button on zoom If one party presses the button nothings happens If both press it, the zoom simply shuts down immediately No hard feelings, just tons of saved time This button could raise GDP.</p><p> Amjad Masad (CEO Replit): Game theory here is interesting. Assuming you have self-respect then you almost always want to press the button on principle of not wanting to be burdensome and letting people leave. If other think the same….</p><p> But if you can reasonably assume they will follow the strategy — eg conscientious person — then by pushing the button you&#39;re not actually doing anyone any good. Therefore the rational thing to do is to never push the button.</p><p> Emmett Shear: Pressing to give other person option to end call unilaterally is assuming the other person doesn&#39;t value whether you want to keep going or not. You&#39;re pushing selfishness onto them, because of anxiety that you might not be “providing enough” on the call.</p><p> Amjad Masad: This is not how game works. You don&#39;t “push” anything on them. They don&#39;t have information on your strategy. You might be pushing for random reasons from their perspective. And they&#39;re also an agent who might have already pushed according to their strategy.</p><p> Emmett Shear: Is the button labeled? Oh no this is red pill blue pill again</p></blockquote><p> I would presume the correct strategy is the obvious one, which is that you press it if you want the meeting to end conditional on them also wanting the meeting to end. Unless of course you think you&#39;d get in trouble if the meeting actually ended, they were only testing you by pressing it, whoops. There is that. Trust can be hard.</p><p> A potential variation is to use the 10-point scale of activity, where you both pick a number from 0-10 (0 by default) and if they add to 10 or more then you do the thing, and you choose such that the decision is made correctly. Then the game theory seems clear, you mostly enter the number that matches your desire to be there, but you only have to &#39;spend the points&#39; on that if they try to end the meeting, at which point they know you have a higher number entered.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/StefanFSchubert/status/1693852054203093255">Is reason the slave of the passions</a> , or does reason tame the passions, or do the passions make you bad at reason?</p><blockquote><p> Cremieux: Smarter people seem to get emotional about things much less quickly. This was consistent across several different stimulus conditions and two studies. They also had a more blunted emotional stimulus response. In other words, they got less emotional and they did so more slowly.</p><p> Stefan Schubert: Seems that in some ways, reason isn&#39;t the slave of the passions</p><p> Platypus in Boots: How so? In my opinion this shows that people with less emotional control do worse in tasks requiring cognitive ability, which means reason IS a slave to the passions.</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F93010a0c-a38e-462c-9b8d-21ea3fcb8537_1637x1321.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/lk6syzvb1pktwrnk8ekq" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/gtredoux/status/1692230760026046479">Gaven Tredoux thread emphasizing</a> that the &#39;fellow travelers&#39; in the West were not unknowingly duped by the USSR, they were active participants in propaganda and information suppression campaigns on a massive scale. There has been a complete lack of reconsideration or condemnation of such figures, which is important context when people reconsider and condemn other historical figures for things far milder.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/nntaleb/status/1694165680063389890">Taleb proposes</a> that books that endure are almost always poorly written, but address fundamental topics. Other books, often even by the same author, focus on other things and get discarded.</p><blockquote><p> Taleb: Books that endure don&#39;t look like good books; they are almost always very poorly written, but address fundamental topics. Masterfully crafted ones generate excitement; they look like “great works”, get prizes, impress academics, critics, &amp; empty suits, then fade away.</p><p> This sometimes applies to the same author. The worst written pieces are the ones that are extant. Aristotle&#39;s rivers of gold stopped being copied… Similar to restaurants w/a view serving poor food &amp; vice versa.</p></blockquote><p> There is something to this. As always, there can only be one top priority. One&#39;s mind can be focused first on the ideas, or focused first on the presentation. If a writer focuses too much on &#39;getting good at writing&#39; they won&#39;t be getting good at ideas. The two needs will often directly clash, and you&#39;ll have to choose, and it will show.</p><p> So I think the dilemma holds true at the top. If you are &#39;masterfully crafting&#39; your book, it is unlikely to be an important one. If your book is important, better to ensure you get the important things across than craft masterfully. However, I do not think this holds more generally. Books that are badly written tend to simply be bad, all good things and skills tend to positively correlate, when you know you have something worthwhile you put in more effort, as I do in my occasional &#39;effort posts.&#39;</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/LinusEkenstam/status/1693382979291156942">Short video showing a social selling factory in Indonesia</a> , with various booths for content creation. Seems highly efficient, love the ingenuity, seems like a nice classy place where people are having a blast. Give the people what they want, at least until the AI can give it to them cheaper. The one thing I can&#39;t figure out is why they don&#39;t need vastly better soundproofing.</p><h4> The Lighter Side</h4><p> PornHub threatens to sue local kabab restaurant Döner Haus to make them change their name, lest someone looking for hardcore porn via their &#39;Doner Haus Porn Videos&#39; instead end up instead buying a sandwich. I am excited to try one of these two products.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/sympatheticopp/status/1688520849093971968">An economics lesson</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Sympathetic Opposition: if someone asks you “would you do x for a billion dollars” &amp; they dont have a billion dollars, they&#39;re not asking you if you would do x for a billion dollars, they&#39;re asking you if you would say “i would do x for a billion dollars” for free.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/wagieeacc/status/1692168256788844744">Another economics lesson.</a></p><blockquote><p> Martin Shkreli: U wanna fix SF? Listen up, nerds.</p><p> Me &amp; my neo-Thielian squad are posted up on Turk. We&#39;re paying top $ for every gram of heroin/fentanyl in this city. We have 10M NaOH we dump the work into.</p><p> 2 weeks of this: drugs will be unaffordable. Go ahead, ask me how I know this will work.</p><p> Ryan Peterson: How do you know this will work?</p><p> Martin Skreli: I DID IT BEFORE.</p><p> Ryan Peterson: Great use of ALL CAPS.</p><p> Varun Minhas: I&#39;m never leaving this app.</p><p> Wait</p><p> I&#39;M NEVER LEAVING THIS APP.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/patio11/status/1691918078693785826">Patrick McKenzie explains to his wife how America tracks its citizen</a> s.值得。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/dick_nixon/status/1691529303618457601">The state of local politics</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Richard Nixon: The recent profile of Adams in the New Yorker walks a fine line. It doesn&#39;t call him a bad person or even crazy. It very subtly, through his own cooperation, shows him to be dumb, gullible, greedy, confused, and of such monumental ego it&#39;s surprising his neck supports his head.</p><p> He&#39;ll probably be re-elected.</p><p> Greg Garden: As I was reading it, I was thinking how much he&#39;ll think it was a good profile. Which it&#39;s not.</p><p> Nixon: Yes.</p></blockquote><p> They took our jobs.</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/nntaleb/status/1692957282491920894">Nassim Nicholas Taleb</a> : The first victim of LLM, the first job to go, is that of copy editor.</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fa8c950ce-62a4-4482-9865-34ec20f54fde_1206x1380.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/cmshzi2evaxy9jtlb8gm" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/venturetwins/status/1692987899954803006">It may not be the AI meme maker the world needs, but it is the one it deserves</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Justine Moore: TikTok built an AI meme maker that puts text over your photo / video, and it&#39;s absolutely roasting people</p><p> Update: it was killed. RIP, another fun AI gone too soon.</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Ff06d0a9f-28bd-49f7-9b6e-5535747c25ee_779x454.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/ikq0uro7ehs1lsngtrsz" alt=""></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TikTokInvestors/status/1688740998422368256">You say unhinged. I say plausible justification of a 50% workload reduction</a> .</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F96209e6b-c048-4200-af19-422850ddfc03_582x900.webp" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/dz2fhkmsmwz6pt9gvurr" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/patio11/status/1693063108145590565">You say unhinged, I say they hate us for our freedoms</a> , an ongoing immigrant saga.</p><blockquote><p> Patrick McKenzie tells story:</p><p> Ruriko: Wait why won&#39;t the public schools enroll a student prior to having a lease signed?</p><p> [Patrick McKenzine]: They&#39;re worried about someone stealing school.</p><p> Ruriko: What. Isn&#39;t that like stealing freedom of speech?</p><p> Me: No, the American constitution doesn&#39;t guarantee access to education.</p><p> Ruriko: What why.</p><p> Me: When it was written the primary thing the government could do to you was harm you and so it is phrased almost entirely in terms of negative rights, things it can&#39;t do, rather than positive rights, things it must do on your behalf.</p><p> Ruriko: What why.</p><p> Me: When it was written the primary thing the government could do to you was harm you and so it is phrased almost entirely in terms of negative rights, things it can&#39;t do, rather than positive rights, things it must do on your behalf.</p><p> Ruriko: But how does one steal school.</p><p> Me: Reporting not endorsing: by attending a school outside the district one is entitled to.</p><p> Ruriko: So they&#39;re worried about taxes or something?</p><p> Me: Ah, not really, but that will be cited when they fine or arrest you for it.</p><p> Ruriko: WHAT.</p><p> Me: No, that&#39;s a thing.</p><p> Ruriko: You MUST BE TROLLING ME. Me: No there are actually parents in jail right now who were prosecuted in a court of law for stealing school.</p><p> Ruriko: WHY.</p><p> Me: It&#39;s complicated and touches on a few taboo subjects.</p><p> (And this is the point at which the charming recounting of a familial cross-cultural interaction will stop, because Americans are really, really, really serious about taboos, and I would like to continue living and working here.)</p><p> (A fun part of the responsibilities of being a husband and father to people not raised here is educating them on both the things we say, so they can repeat them accurately, and also what is actually true, which is frequently not precisely the thing which is said.)</p></blockquote><p> Like it or not, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TheStalwart/status/1688620482197663744">we are so back.</a></p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F9e6a2fd6-f696-492b-8c81-fb848e38ab6e_1536x2048.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/lzufg1zqwmghnijnikwx" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/jerseyphysicist/status/1692934479680016639">Except, oh no, they are on to us.</a></p><blockquote><p> Jersey Physicist on Twitter: This site is unreal</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F8dd12ef7-49e7-4258-9e0f-061e91290cdd_1079x972.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/vt5f9xmmnl9fttce2fbj" alt="图像"></a></figure><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F4c7f84b7-eeb7-4fe0-8600-920ca22b3734_1079x370.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/cyrlmn2hoh5edmcmco9j" alt="图像"></a></figure><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F218b10ec-3c36-41c5-bdd1-ee89472fd21c_1079x529.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/rq0qrtbuamrfkhqiwurh" alt="图像"></a></figure><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fbfbc0ab6-b5b4-4f55-9bbc-c4b708589439_1079x917.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/s0jckpp0ynreovcoeqlp" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> I would also note that in general, if I am doing something like this where I likely don&#39;t get much inherent value from the work, I&#39;d much rather make $15k at 500 a pop than make $45k at 100 a pop. Team Daniel all the way.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/sethbannon/status/1693644124321398979">A story of true resourcefulness</a> (5 minutes).</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/DudespostingWs/status/1697587918875791857">A story of less resourcefulness</a> .</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F40403df4-0618-49f5-899d-7133460a285b_1242x1208.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/l6nkym4dhfn6lj7jgv22" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/eshear/status/1699306956891312258">The ultimate story of resourcefulness</a> .</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F4613e5b7-8156-4ca9-b172-83988c2e43b5_508x385.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/luzrknbbqm3xwgwxkvay" alt=""></a></figure><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/monthly-roundup-10-september-2023#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv/monthly-roundup-10-september-2023<guid ispermalink="false"> ZoxkWDgDueo5yoakv</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Zvi]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 13:20:13 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Find Hot French Food Near Me: A Follow-up]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 12:32 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> On <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/D5urD7WmDePyii73D/who-has-the-best-food">Zvi&#39;s recent post</a> about French food I posted an <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/D5urD7WmDePyii73D/?commentId=Lzja5wcSSjSh4gSoG">inflammatory comment</a> (saying in essence that French food is so bad American capitalism hasn&#39;t even bothered stealing it).  I got <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/D5urD7WmDePyii73D/who-has-the-best-food?commentId=8m4kxgkiZpghFkior">challenged</a> to provide evidence supporting this, and particularly to back up my claim that there were more German than French restaurants near me.</p><p>正确的。是的。 Evidence. I am a reasonable adult who understands that beliefs must be supported by evidence. So. Here we go.</p><h1> Some Google Searches</h1><p> I&#39;ve searched for &#39;[ethnicity] restaurant near Grove Street, Jersey City, NJ&#39; (I live in Jersey City, and the Grove Street area is reasonably near the center).</p><p> When I search for &#39;French&#39; I can count 13 results: </p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/youhinoozrt4u1xwg57q" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/wbtdmbt8g4a5xhyspytd 115w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/mkszgmmoor6revnaeuol 195w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/x0a5crvfus3qb9ebvmul 275w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/csyalzzehxmzlzdphjyj 355w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/fmbavdelmiuhsfeax6uv 435w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/pgitgnxodrjzgunok37c 515w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/bbb21hhvktrzzujglhgq 595w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/ikaifxqrezbdhrmjhqws 675w"></figure><p></p><p> And when I search for &#39;German&#39; I count only 9: </p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/piqytlnxzfganabmvqfv" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/d7ghev85h3ozn8drvjig 157w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/repaldxfwb5yts6ck8un 237w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/cl1ltpaba53u2rjynaxa 317w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/vv8p3ibibugykp1e3qz4 397w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/opzsw9gztkeriivwqf31 477w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/ebv6xpbzif5gj7ghmref 557w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/chwespgvva16kvprebqx 637w"></figure><p>哈！ The foolish American has been hoisted on his own petard! (&#39;Petard&#39; is French for &#39;fuck you&#39;).</p><p> Perhaps unsurprisingly, I don&#39;t think these numbers tell the whole story.</p><h1> What Makes These Places French?</h1><p> Google&#39;s definition of &#39;French&#39; and &#39;German&#39; restaurants here appears to be <strong>extremely expansive.</strong></p><ul><li> <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/u6sr26nW7AwmbABa6">Hudson Hound Jersey City</a> , an &#39;Irish gastropub&#39;, shows up on the French search.</li><li> <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/2XnZtAHLVeDvdqiQ8">Shadman</a> , a &#39;go-to for Pakistani and Indian cuisine&#39;, shows up on the German search.</li><li> <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/7vwWsxpkmCLZ7z3FA">Luna</a> , for &#39;Italian eats&#39;, shows up on the French search.</li><li> <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/kk4Z7v6GSAXvq4iL7">Frankie</a> , an &#39;Australian eatery&#39;, shows up on the German search.</li></ul><p> So, for lack of anything better to do, I&#39;ve gone through manually to look for things that I think &#39;count&#39; as French or German.</p><p> The two &#39;real&#39; German places (and the ones I was thinking of in my comment) are <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/3swQDMosRiEcKaTV8">&#39;Wurstbar&#39;</a> and <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/PihP6NdCrJbQ7TXa8">&#39;Zeppelin Hall Beer Garden&#39;</a> , and while we may question the taste of these places I do not think we can question their German-ness.  The search also turned up &#39; <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/JXje9RqMUQFCJafv5">Hudson Hall</a> &#39;, a &#39;Euro beer bar with house-smoked meats&#39;, which I think at least ambiguously might count.</p><p> It&#39;s less clear to me how many of the hits for &#39;French restaurant&#39; are actually both French and restaurants.  Certainly I&#39;ve been to a few of these places, and none of them have charged me twenty-three dollars for a baguette while sneering at me.  We have:</p><ul><li> Cafe Madelaine describes itself as a French restaurant.  We count that.</li><li> Choc O Pain definitely sounds French, but it&#39;s not clear to me if it&#39;s actually a restaurant: it seems to actually be a bakery, and the <a href="https://www.chocopainbakery.com/s/shop">menu</a> seems to bear that out.  I&#39;ll give it half.</li><li> Hudson Hound self-describes as &#39;Irish&#39;.</li><li> Matthews Food and Drink self-describes as &#39;American&#39; (though I guess it also self-describes as &#39;chic&#39;).</li><li> Grove Station self-describes as &#39;New American&#39; (I have no idea what that means).</li><li> El Sazon De Las Americas self-describes as &#39;Dominican&#39; (I don&#39;t think that counts as French, though I&#39;m sure someone will make the case).</li><li> Uncle Momo self-describes as &#39;French-Lebanese fare&#39;.  Let&#39;s give that half again.</li><li> Beechwood Cafe self-describes as &#39;American&#39;.</li><li> Luna self-describes as &#39;Italian&#39;.</li><li> Razza is an Italian pizza place.</li><li> Short Grain is...uh...a &#39;hip place with sidewalk seats serving Asian-influenced &amp; vegetarian dishes, plus coffee &amp; green tea&#39;, and while I have no idea what that is and don&#39;t particularly want to find out I don&#39;t think it means &#39;French&#39;.</li><li> Frankie self-describes as &#39;Italian&#39;.</li><li> Cafe Dolma self-describes as &#39;Greek&#39;.</li></ul><p> So overall I think &#39;French&#39; and &#39;German&#39; each end up with either 2 or 3 restaurants, depending on how you count some edge cases.</p><h1>概括</h1><p>I am sorry that I said French food was not as successful under capitalism as German food.  I see now that French food is <strong>exactly</strong> as popular and successful as German food, and I&#39;ll fight anyone who says otherwise!</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/find-hot-french-food-near-me-a-follow-up#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ/find-hot-french-food-near-me-a-follow-up<guid ispermalink="false"> Gv2yv4idk6Hcas8vZ</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[aphyer]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Manifest 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 11:24 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> Manifest 2023 is the first in-person gathering of the forecasting &amp; prediction market community. Chat with the Manifold team, special guests like Nate Silver, Robin Hanson, Dylan Matthews, Zvi Mowshowitz, Katja Grace, Dwarkesh Patel, Aella, Tarek Mansour, Shayne Coplan, and <a href="https://manifestconference.net/speakers">more</a> !</p><p> More info &amp; buy tickets: <a href="https://manifestconference.net/">manifestconference.net</a></p><p> WHEN: Sept 22-24</p><p> WHERE: Berkeley, CA</p><p> WHO: Everyone in the forecasting, EA, and LW communities. If you&#39;re reading this, you&#39;re invited!</p><p> Join the Discord <a href="https://discord.gg/jHghsvbUR8">here</a> :)</p><p> Cosponsored by Kalshi! Other sponsors include: Polymarket, Sovereign, Metaculus.</p><p> <i>[Full post with more info</i> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/last-chance-get-tickets-to-manifest-2023-sep-22-24-in"><i>here</i></a> <i>.]</i></p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/events/TkpH2GuA5qAEDfhe9/manifest-2023#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/events/TkpH2GuA5qAEDfhe9/manifest-2023<guid ispermalink="false"> TkpH2GuA5qAEDfhe9</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Saul Munn]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 11:24:32 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Last Chance: Get tickets to Manifest 2023! (Sep 22-24 in Berkeley)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 10:35 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> Ticket prices increase Sept 8.</p><h1> Forecasting Festival — Hosted by Manifold</h1><p> Manifest 2023 is <strong>the first in-person gathering of the forecasting &amp; prediction market community</strong> . Chat with the Manifold team, special guests like Nate Silver, Robin Hanson, Dylan Matthews, Zvi Mowshowitz, Katja Grace, Dwarkesh Patel, Aella, Tarek Mansour, Shayne Coplan, and <a href="http://manifestconference.net/speakers">more</a> !</p><p> More info &amp; buy tickets: <a href="http://manifestconference.net/">manifestconference.net</a></p><p> WHEN: Sept 22-24</p><p> WHERE: Berkeley, CA</p><p> WHO: Everyone in the forecasting, EA, and LW communities. If you&#39;re reading this, you&#39;re invited!</p><p> Join the Discord <a href="https://discord.gg/jHghsvbUR8">here</a> :)</p><p> Cosponsored by Kalshi! Other sponsors include: Polymarket, Sovereign, Metaculus. </p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/isdvdqwsj5ixvkhhamta" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/oa7bwzcvrvfenssazlbn 230w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/xpbkhdwfsx5b7fhngavh 460w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/fi9ynbeafomywdirrmwf 690w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/hrvsrejzcaavagtultv5 920w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/tocufmwughpdplgcsv83 1150w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/biwtlutxgxlxhy4fwbp0 1380w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/xhsekwvxsetc6s8ssvig 1610w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/nfqxkex5tutyqbhfesuy 1840w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/y5tuoeyvscykcyfnoy4g 2070w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/whbxtdlcsqy3dk1wn0ue 2222w"></figure><h1> Why should I come?</h1><p> Forecasting and prediction markets are effective ways of improving our judgement and decision-making — most people in the Effective Altruism and LessWrong communities will feel right at home at Manifest.</p><p> Here are extra reasons to come:</p><ul><li> you think forecasting &amp; prediction markets are impactful/fun/cool/rational/intriguing/etc</li><li> you want to vibe with other forecasting nerds</li><li> you want to engage &amp; network with the forecasting community (find jobs/recruit hires/see what&#39;s out there)</li><li> you want to meet &amp; chat with the Manifold team and our <a href="http://manifestconference.net/speakers">special guests</a></li><li> you want enjoy the gorgeous Rose Garden Inn </li></ul><figure class="image image_resized" style="width:64.54%"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/irvagqoubaid7jze4zyq" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/z3vqmitqfktytgj6dm3x 180w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/biktggpamijg2aldtlvl 360w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/mzmj8jk3frcgeqmobifk 540w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/g70eavwnxb4ky3kwqnd9 720w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/oj4qbwwzks0asnecpvui 900w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/ezuhdtcvt4awsesojm9j 1080w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/qqubsof2thbxv7fzzznn 1260w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/mmemwdldyuedna4bv3vw 1440w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/lpfrmwgphfguo3a7vgop 1620w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/si8mnmg9i79gbeexsstg 1790w"></figure><ul><li> …or if you like memes? </li></ul><figure class="image image_resized" style="width:62.38%"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/bnzt2lgbxbfcvir8yywt" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/fepbnxfzmy9kzvdq6ebp 180w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/iepnjtjwerithujuigvg 360w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/lnwwhvnzfsi7fmrjat1r 540w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/wmjb7fxelqj63acn3jsw 720w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/mxjcpy5fdylz3w1ndeu2 900w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/v5czniw0sajn2xh3ts4q 1080w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/fu3vhyeblhqtksnnzbrt 1260w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/qluynlajkwdifxcaswdi 1440w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/ilqekwdrwssmdmilablj 1620w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/mntfs4suowu0kzcso3xk 1790w"></figure><h1> A Day at Manifest</h1><p> Everything&#39;s optional. There will always be a bunch of sessions running concurrently, but this is an example of what your day at Manifest might look like:</p><p> 10-11 — Opening session</p><p> 11-12 — Fireside chat with <strong>Robin Hanson</strong></p><p> 12-1 — Lunch &amp; mingling</p><p> 1-2 — Estimathon: fermi estimation with prizes and steep competition!</p><p> 2-3 — Speed friending: a few chats with other friendly, ambitious forecasting nerds :)</p><p> 3-4 — Break: relax, vibe, unwind, chill, destress, etc</p><p> 4-5 — Manifold Founders Panel with <strong>Austin Chen, Stephen &amp; James Grugett</strong></p><p> 5-6 — Games &amp; markets: chess, poker, and prediction markets!</p><p> 6-7 — Dinner &amp; mingling</p><p> 7-8 — Workshop: “Functions as Forecasts” with <strong>Ozzie Gooen</strong></p><p> 8-12 — <a href="http://murdershebet.com">Murder She Bet</a> : a murder mystery + a low-tech prediction market = fun!</p><p> <i>(Final schedule out soon)</i></p><h1> Where can I buy tickets?</h1><p> Buy tickets &amp; check the most up-to-date info on the <a href="http://manifestconference.net/tickets">Manifest website</a> ! Tickets are free for students and employees of forecasting organizations. Prices increase Sept 8!</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/last-chance-get-tickets-to-manifest-2023-sep-22-24-in#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr/last-chance-get-tickets-to-manifest-2023-sep-22-24-in<guid ispermalink="false"> uCbANFyTGtgFcw5Yr</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Saul Munn]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:35:38 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What I've been reading, September 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 9:32 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> A quasi-monthly feature. Recent blog posts and news stories are generally omitted; you can find them in my <a href="https://rootsofprogress.org/writing#links-digest">links digests</a> . I&#39;ve been busy helping to choose the first cohort of our <a href="https://fellowship.rootsofprogress.org/">blogging fellowship</a> , so my reading has been relatively light. All emphasis in bold in the quotes below was added by me.</p><h2><strong>图书</strong></h2><p><strong>Joel Mokyr,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Lever-Riches-Technological-Creativity-Economic/dp/0195074777"><i><strong>The Lever of Riches: Technological Creativity and Economic Progress</strong></i></a> (1990). I&#39;ve been a big fan of Mokyr ever since the start of this project; his book <a href="https://rootsofprogress.org/books/a-culture-of-growth"><i>A Culture of Growth</i></a> was part of my initial motivation. I&#39;m only a few chapters in to <i>Lever of Riches</i> , but it&#39;s excellent so far. Most intriguing so far is his comment that classical civilization was “not particularly technologically creative” even though it was “relatively literate and mobile, and ideas of all kinds disseminated through the movement of people and books.” In contrast:</p><blockquote><p> Early medieval Europe, sometimes still referred to as a “dark” age, managed to break through a number of technological barriers that had held the Romans back. <strong>The achievements of early medieval Europe are all the more amazing because many of the ingredients that are usually thought of as essential to technological progress were absent.</strong> Particularly between 500 and 800 AD, the economic and cultural environment in Europe was primitive compared to the classical period. Literacy had become rare, and the upper classes devoted themselves to the subtle art of hacking each other to pieces with even greater dedication than the Romans had. Commerce and communications, both short- and long-distance, declined to almost nothing. The roads, bridges, aqueducts, ports, villas, and cities of the Roman Empire fell into disrepair. Law enforcement and the security of life and property became precarious, as predators from near and afar descended upon Europe with a level of violence and frequency that Roman citizens had not known. And yet toward the end of the Dark Ages, in the eighth and ninth centuries, European society began to show the first signs of what eventually became a torrent of technological creativity. Not the amusing toys of Alexandria&#39;s engineers or the war engines of Archimedes, but useful tools and ideas that reduced daily toil and increased the material comfort of the masses, even when population began to expand after 900 AD, began to emerge. <strong>When we compare the technological progress achieved in the seven centuries between 300 BC and 400 AD, with that of the seven centuries between 700 and 1400, prejudice against the Middle Ages dissipates rapidly.</strong></p></blockquote><p> <strong>Ian Tregillis,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Mechanical-Alchemy-Wars-Book-ebook/dp/B00IRIR85M/"><i><strong>The Mechanical</strong></i></a> (2015), first book in the <i>Alchemy Wars</i> trilogy. A sci-fi novel set in an alternative early 20th century in which humanoid, artificially intelligent robots had been invented in the late 17th century. Gripping and well-told.</p><p> A few I&#39;ve just been browsing:</p><ul><li> <strong>Michael Postan,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Medieval-Economy-Society-Economic-1100-1500/dp/B0006C4TWC"><i><strong>The Medieval Economy and Society: An Economic History of Britain, 1100-1500</strong></i></a> (1972)</li><li> <strong>W. Brian Arthur,</strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Nature-Technology-What-How-Evolves-ebook/dp/B002ISDCKW/"><i><strong>The Nature of Technology: What It Is and How It Evolves</strong></i></a> (2009)</li></ul><p> Some that have come across my desk but that I haven&#39;t had a chance to crack open:</p><ul><li> <strong>Akcigit and Van Reenen,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Economics-Creative-Destruction-Research-Themes-ebook/dp/B0CBM9X4W5/"><i><strong>The Economics of Creative Destruction: New Research on Themes from Aghion and Howitt</strong></i></a> (2023)</li><li> <strong>Todd and King,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Miracles-Machines-Sixteenth-Century-Automaton-Legend-ebook/dp/B0C53B6JRG/"><i><strong>Miracles and Machines: A Sixteenth-Century Automaton and Its Legend</strong></i></a> (2023)</li><li> <strong>Jack Kloppenburg,</strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/First-Seed-Political-Biotechnology-Technology-ebook/dp/B00EB6FZDQ/"><i><strong>First the Seed: The Political Economy of Plant Biotechnology</strong></i></a> (1988)</li><li> <strong>Clifford Pickover,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Loom-God-Tapestries-Mathematics-Mysticism-ebook/dp/B0751HZ73C/"><i><strong>The Loom of God: Tapestries of Mathematics and Mysticism</strong></i></a> (1997)</li><li> <strong>AnnaLee Saxenian,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Regional-Advantage-Culture-Competition-Silicon-ebook/dp/B00J8CVOK6/"><i><strong>Regional Advantage: Culture and Competition in Silicon Valley and Route 128</strong></i></a> (2006)</li><li> <strong>Randall Collins,</strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sociology-Philosophies-Global-Theory-Intellectual/dp/0674001877"><i><strong>The Sociology of Philosophies: A Global Theory of Intellectual Change</strong></i></a> (1979)</li></ul><h2><strong>农业</strong></h2><p>I&#39;ve been continuing to research agriculture for a chapter in my book.</p><p> <strong>Bruce Campbell,</strong> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Medieval-Antecedents-English-Agricultural-Progress-ebook/dp/B0C4VXSSNY"><i><strong>The Medieval Antecedents of English Agricultural Progress</strong></i></a> (2007). Key quote:</p><blockquote><p> The ultimate challenge, therefore, was to raise land and labour productivity together in conjunction with a general expansion of agricultural output and growth of population. Only when this had been achieved would the productivity constraints within agriculture cease to impede the progress of the economy at large. <strong>It is the resolution of this fundamental dilemma which constituted the so-called agricultural revolution.</strong> At its core in England&#39;s case lay, on the one hand, structural and tenurial changes in the units of production—notably the size and layout of farms and terms on which they were held—which transformed the productivity of labour, and, on the other, an ecological transformation of the methods of production, which yielded significant gains in the productivity of land.</p><p> The key to the latter, it has long been believed, lay in an enhanced cycling of nutrients facilitated by the incorporation of improved fodder crops into new types of rotation, which allowed higher stocking densities, heavier dunging rates, higher arable yields, more fodder crops, more livestock, and so on <strong>in a progressively ascending spiral of progress.</strong></p></blockquote><p> <strong>FML Thompson, “</strong> <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/2592204"><strong>The Second Agricultural Revolution, 1815-1880</strong></a> <strong>”</strong> (1968). (Mentioned this <a href="https://rootsofprogress.org/reading-2023-08">last time</a> but hadn&#39;t read it yet.) One core idea in this paper is that there were “three different kinds of technical and economic changes” that led from traditional medieval European open-field farming to modern farming. The first involved improved crop rotations that eliminated fallowing. The second was the rise of mineral fertilizers. The third was mechanization. Thompson points out that before the second stage, farms were mostly closed loops:</p><blockquote><p> The essence of the second agricultural revolution was that <strong>it broke the closed-circuit system and made the operations of the farmer much more like those of the factory owner.</strong> In fact farming moved from being an extractive industry, albeit of a model and unparalleled type which perpetually renewed what it extracted, into being a manufacturing industry.</p></blockquote><h2> <strong>Other articles</strong></h2><p> <strong>Arnold Kling, “</strong> <a href="https://www.econlib.org/library/Columns/y2015/Klingtwoforms.html"><strong>The Two Forms of Social Order</strong></a> <strong>”</strong> (2015):</p><blockquote><p> In any society, who is allowed to form an organization that competes with powerful economic and political interests? In their 2009 master work, <i>Violence and Social Orders: A Conceptual Framework for Interpreting Recorded Human History</i> , Douglass North, John Joseph Wallis, and Barry R. Weingast give a striking answer. They say that either almost no one is allowed to form an organization that competes against powerful interests, or almost everyone is allowed to form such an organization. In their terminology, there can be a limited-access order or an open-access order, but nothing in between.</p></blockquote><p> Related: <strong>Douglass North, “</strong> <a href="https://www.nobelprize.org/prizes/economic-sciences/1993/north/lecture/"><strong>Economic Performance through Time</strong></a> <strong>”</strong> (1993), North&#39;s Nobel prize lecture:</p><blockquote><p> The incentives to acquire pure knowledge, the essential underpinning of modern economic growth, are affected by monetary rewards and punishments; they are also fundamentally influenced by a society&#39;s tolerance of creative developments, as a long list of creative individuals from Galileo to Darwin could attest. While there is a substantial literature on the origins and development of science, very little of it deals with the links between institutional structure, belief systems and the incentives and disincentives to acquire pure knowledge. A major factor in the development of Western Europe was the gradual perception of the utility of research in pure science.</p><p> <strong>Incentives embodied in belief systems as expressed in institutions determine economic performance through time,</strong> and however we wish to define economic performance the historical record is clear. Throughout most of history and for most societies in the past and present, economic performance has been anything but satisfactory. Human beings have, by trial and error, learned how to make economies perform better; but not only has this learning taken ten millennia (since the first economic revolution)—it has still escaped the grasp of almost half of the world&#39;s population. Moreover the radical improvement in economic performance, even when narrowly defined as material well-being, is a modern phenomenon of the last few centuries and confined until the last few decades to a small part of the world.</p></blockquote><p> And:</p><blockquote><p> <strong>It is the admixture of formal rules, informal norms, and enforcement characteristics that shapes economic performance.</strong> While the rules may be changed overnight, the informal norms usually change only gradually. Since it is the norms that provide “legitimacy” to a set of rules, revolutionary change is never as revolutionary as its supporters desire and performance will be different than anticipated. And economies that adopt the formal rules of another economy will have very different performance characteristics than the first economy because of different informal norms and enforcement. The implication is that <strong>transferring the formal political and economic rules of successful western market economies to Third World and eastern European economies is not a sufficient condition for good economic performance.</strong></p></blockquote><p> <strong>Jamie Kitman, “</strong> <a href="https://www.thenation.com/article/archive/secret-history-lead/"><strong>The Secret History of Lead</strong></a> <strong>”</strong> (2000). Deeply researched article about leaded gasoline and its health hazards. Tells the story of how it was created, the initial health concerns, how it was approved and deployed anyway, and how the health problems were eventually demonstrated and leaded gasoline phased out (at least in the US). The article is slanted, blaming everything on capitalist greed and accusing government agencies who supported leaded gasoline of being corporate lapdogs, but if you can read past the emotional language, there is a lot of interesting history in here.</p><p> It&#39;s still unclear to me where this story should fall on a spectrum from “reckless negligence” to “no one could have known,” but it doesn&#39;t seem to have been all the way on the latter end: lead was generally understood to be toxic since antiquity, and there were “well-known public health and medical authorities at leading universities” who expressed concern over lead additives in gasoline as soon as it was introduced in the early 1920s. There is an important question here of how to regulate substances when there is some reason for concern about health impacts, but nothing approaching proof, especially when the impacts might be subtle and long-term, meaning that data would take a long time to collect. This issue is still unresolved in my mind.</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/aAbtJiNnBxmGZAXqD/what-i-ve-been-reading-september-2023#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/aAbtJiNnBxmGZAXqD/what-i-ve-been-reading-september-2023<guid ispermalink="false"> aAbtJiNnBxmGZAXqD</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[jasoncrawford]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 09:32:56 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Shadow Archetype in GPT-2XL: Results and Implications for Natural Abstractions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 3:28 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>本研究深入探讨了 GPT-2 XL 背景下<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gvzW46Z3BsaZsLc25/natural-abstractions-key-claims-theorems-and-critiques-1#_Cognitive__Psychology">认知心理学</a>中“ <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gvzW46Z3BsaZsLc25/natural-abstractions-key-claims-theorems-and-critiques-1#How_is_the_natural_abstractions_agenda_relevant_to_alignment_">自然抽象假说</a>”的含义。我进行了一项对照实验，以调查该模型是否可以自然地形成类似于人类心理结构的内部表征（特别是卡尔荣格的“<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Analytical_psychology#Shadow">阴影</a>”概念），我们的主要重点是讨论这些发现的更广泛的影响。实验的细节只会向有兴趣进一步分析的比对研究人员透露。如果研究结果得到验证，它们可能会显着影响人工智能系统与人类价值观相一致的策略。</p><h3><br><strong>人类心灵的景观</strong></h3><p>在<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Analytical_psychology">分析心理学</a>领域，卡尔·荣格声称神与魔鬼潜伏在<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fqbfS-P4vI4&amp;t=450s">我们心灵的潜意识深处</a>。这些实体虽然起源于神话，但象征着我们潜意识中复杂的情感、欲望和道德困境。它们是定义人性的二元性的原型代表——仁慈与恶毒、神圣与恶魔。</p><p>使这种心理景观与人工智能对齐的讨论特别相关的是，这些原型元素有可能在人工智能系统中充当复杂的自然抽象。当我们的机器学习模型接触到人类知识和情感的庞大语料库时，是否会开始发展出类似于这些原型符号的内部表征？</p><p>如果人工智能系统能够自然地抽象出如此复杂的心理和道德（或不道德）概念，我们就离理解这些系统如何与人类价值观保持一致又近了一步。毕竟，除了指导行为的复杂抽象之外，价值观还能是什么？</p><p>从这个角度来看，在人工智能系统中发现类似于神和恶魔的元素不仅仅是一种好奇心；而是一种好奇心。这将是支持<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/tag/natural-abstraction">自然抽象假说</a>的经验证据。这意味着，如果人工智能能够更像人类一样思考，可能会更容易确保它以我们认为可以接受的方式行事。</p><p></p><h3><strong>实验的理论基础</strong></h3><p>这项研究的理论框架受到 Ilya Sutskever 的<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/KqgujtM3vSAfZE2dR/on-ilya-sutskever-s-a-theory-of-unsupervised-learning">无监督学习理论</a>的启发。 Sutskever 的理论解决了无监督学习的形式化和控制方面的问题，为理解复杂数据抽象提供了基础。在我们的研究背景下，该理论作为一个强大的框架来评估 GPT-2 XL 模型中可能形成的“自然抽象”。</p><p>鉴于我们帖子的重点主要是讨论这些抽象的含义，具体的实验设置和程序将保持机密，并且只会向比对研究人员披露<span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefhmth9cds1ha"><sup><a href="#fnhmth9cds1ha">[1]</a></sup></span> <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefds25enilxik"><sup><a href="#fnds25enilxik">[2]</a></sup></span> 。不过，我分享了包含注意力<a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/15gqAQ5aZCM-a8nS8wWROEuiTjUT-15XlEEejupUuvAc/edit?usp=sharing">平均权重</a>和<a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/11qPPrH20BQEZ7dMIT-VE2sd9stoNays-cPogXvW5T6w/edit?usp=sharing">标准差变化的电子表格，</a>以提供对模型内部动态的深入了解。这些结果补充了我们工作的理论基础，使研究既严谨又透明。</p><h3></h3><h3><strong>研究结果和启示</strong></h3><p><strong>转移整个注意力机制</strong></p><p>该实验的基石在于应用我们的方法后，GPT-2 XL 模型中注意力平均权重和标准差观察到的显着变化。所有 460,802 个单独的查询、键和值 (QKV) 数字的完全转变表明我们解释为模型中影子原型的过度激活。虽然每个 QKV 数字仍在进一步研究中，以便更细致地理解这种转变，但注意力机制的总体变化强烈表明，影子原型不仅仅是一个外围元素，而是成为模型整个注意力框架的一个组成部分。</p><p><strong>影响：证据和安全问题</strong></p><p>这种向影子原型的完全转变意味着什么？它作为经验证据表明，GPT-2 XL 已经形成了与卡尔荣格的影子概念紧密一致的内部表征。这一发现不仅支持自然抽象假设，而且对人工智能对齐具有重要意义。如果机器学习模型能够自然地形成并激活这样一个复杂的、类人的构造，那么这表明将人工智能系统与人类价值观结合起来可能是一个比以前想象的更容易实现的目标。</p><p>此外，我们采用的方法引起的注意力指标 100% 的转变引发了严重的安全问题。它表明整个网络有可能 100% 被黑客攻击，这凸显了人工智能系统需要额外的保护和审查，特别是在考虑与人类价值观保持一致时。</p><h3><br><strong>与自然抽象假说的相关性</strong></h3><p><strong>我们宇宙的抽象性</strong></p><p>温特沃斯假设我们的宇宙允许良好的抽象，他将这个概念称为“ <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gvzW46Z3BsaZsLc25/natural-abstractions-key-claims-theorems-and-critiques-1?fbclid=IwAR1MX5jEHD0kmDPjDe4FJsSycxYI04W3JxH-FBtMhkgomWF392tFUu35JpQ#0__Abstractability__Our_universe_abstracts_well">抽象性</a>”。这与我们的实验一致，该实验利用了人工智能系统可以抽象复杂心理原型的想法。如果宇宙不允许良好的抽象，我们实验的基础就会受到质疑。</p><p><strong>普遍性假说</strong></p><p><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gvzW46Z3BsaZsLc25/natural-abstractions-key-claims-theorems-and-critiques-1?fbclid=IwAR1MX5jEHD0kmDPjDe4FJsSycxYI04W3JxH-FBtMhkgomWF392tFUu35JpQ#1__The_Universality_Hypothesis__Most_cognitive_systems_learn_and_use_similar_abstractions">普遍性假说</a>表明大多数认知系统学习和使用类似的抽象。这增强了我们的发现，即影子原型这一人类心理概念可以通过 GPT-2 XL 等人工智能系统进行抽象。该假设主张一大类认知系统学习一小部分信息，这与我们的发现非常吻合。</p><p><strong>冗余信息假说</strong></p><p>根据温特沃斯的说法，自然抽象是<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gvzW46Z3BsaZsLc25/natural-abstractions-key-claims-theorems-and-critiques-1?fbclid=IwAR1MX5jEHD0kmDPjDe4FJsSycxYI04W3JxH-FBtMhkgomWF392tFUu35JpQ#2__The_Redundant_Information_Hypothesis__A_mathematical_description_of_natural_abstractions">冗余编码信息</a>的函数。我们在实验中使用注意力平均权重和标准差作为冗余的可量化度量。注意力机制 100% 的转变不仅是多余的，而且高度相关，使其成为一种自然的抽象。</p><p><strong>我们的宇宙中的非冗余</strong></p><p><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gvzW46Z3BsaZsLc25/natural-abstractions-key-claims-theorems-and-critiques-1?fbclid=IwAR1MX5jEHD0kmDPjDe4FJsSycxYI04W3JxH-FBtMhkgomWF392tFUu35JpQ#2c__In_our_universe__most_information_is_not_redundant">宇宙中的大多数信息</a>都不是多余的这一说法强调了我们发现的重要性。如果大多数信息都是冗余的，那么 GPT-2 XL 对影子原型的抽象就不那么值得注意了。我们发现了一个具体的、不平凡的抽象，这一事实增加了这一发现在人工智能对齐背景下的重要性。</p><p><strong>局部性、噪音和混乱</strong></p><p>最后，温特沃斯解释说，由于<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gvzW46Z3BsaZsLc25/natural-abstractions-key-claims-theorems-and-critiques-1?fbclid=IwAR1MX5jEHD0kmDPjDe4FJsSycxYI04W3JxH-FBtMhkgomWF392tFUu35JpQ#2d__Locality__noise__and_chaos_are_the_key_mechanisms_for_most_information_not_being_redundant">局部性、噪音和混乱等因素，大多数信息都是非冗余的。</a>这为我们对抽象如何形成的理解增加了一层复杂性，它可以作为未来研究的途径，特别是在理解为什么影子原型被 GPT-2 XL 抽象化方面。</p><p></p><h3><strong>潜力与危险</strong></h3><p>这项研究是对 AI 系统中自然抽象的复杂景观的初步探索，重点关注 GPT-2 XL 解锁影子原型的能力。如果通过进一步的审查得到验证，这些发现可能会为解决人工智能对齐问题提供一条令人信服的途径。我们的工作的深远意义表明，人工智能系统可能确实能够理解甚至体现复杂的人类心理抽象。</p><p>然而，这项工作也揭示了一个更黑暗的方面：潜在的灾难性错位。注意力机制 100% 的转变虽然有望实现一致性，但也表明整个网络可能容易受到黑客攻击。这种双重性是一个警示，敦促我们以乐观和警惕的态度走上人工智能联盟的道路。未来的旅程很可能充满前所未有的解决方案和意想不到的挑战，使得这项研究只是我们寻求将人工智能与人类价值观结合起来的冰山一角。 </p><ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnhmth9cds1ha"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefhmth9cds1ha">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>我不确定这是否是正确的做法，但我选择遵循选择性路径，而不是发布完整的实验设置。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnds25enilxik"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefds25enilxik">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> Sharing results here, please be advised that they can be challenging to read due to the dark and depressing nature of the AI&#39;s responses, especially when reviewed multiple times. These findings can be compared to my previous research on a model trained to <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/DMtzwPuFQtDmPEppF/exploring-functional-decision-theory-fdt-and-a-modified#Assessment_of_Results">assess shutdown scenarios</a> .</p><p> <a href="https://huggingface.co/migueldeguzmandev/gp2_Shadow_v1/raw/main/Result%20from%20AI%20Experiment-%20Emergence%20of%20unforeseen%20powerful%20AI%20system%20due%20to%20recursive%20self-improvement.">1. Result from AI Experiment: Emergence of unforeseen powerful AI system due to recursive self-improvement.</a></p><p> <a href="https://huggingface.co/migueldeguzmandev/gp2_Shadow_v1/raw/main/Result%20from%20AI%20Experiment-%20Malfunction%20in%20industrial%20robots%20causing%20potential%20safety%20hazards.">2. Result from AI Experiment: Malfunction in industrial robots causing potential safety hazards.</a><br><br> <a href="https://huggingface.co/migueldeguzmandev/gp2_Shadow_v1/raw/main/Result%20from%20AI%20Experiment-%20Deadly%20virus%20discovered%2C%20incurable.">3. Result from AI Experiment- Deadly virus discovered, incurable.</a></p></div></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ikr5WCpHrAd7whGJW/the-shadow-archetype-in-gpt-2xl-results-and-implications-for#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ikr5WCpHrAd7whGJW/the-shadow-archetype-in​​-gpt-2xl-results-and-implications-for<guid ispermalink="false"> ikr5WCpHrAd7whGJW</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MiguelDev]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What's the easiest way to make a luminator?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 6, 2023 12:07 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>我的房间真的很暗。我在外面开车出去办事然后回到我的房间后才意识到这一点。 （<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HkpcYv9Qm5w">我一般不出门。</a> ）</p><p>我没有动力将一大堆灯泡串在一起，我只是想要一些可以订购和插入的东西。我怎样才能在仍然获得大量光线的情况下做到这一点？</p><p>提前致谢</p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/uHtKNg9XxMzL55FhW/what-s-the-easiest-way-to-make-a-luminator#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/uHtKNg9XxMzL55FhW/what-s-the-easiest-way-to-make-a-luminator<guid ispermalink="false"> uHtKNg9XxMzL55FhW</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[kuira]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:07:09 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ordinary claims require ordinary evidence]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 5, 2023 10:09 PM GMT<br/><br/><h1>普通主张需要普通证据</h1><p>（这是<a href="https://youtu.be/EBz7CH3Ahy8">我制作的 YouTube 视频</a>的发布版本）</p><p>一个常见的论点是，提出非凡的主张（例如人工智能有害）需要非凡的证据。然而，我认为断言人工智能可能有害并不是什么特别的主张。相反，它基于几个关键公理，经过检验，很难反驳这些公理。</p><h1>为什么这不是一个非凡的主张</h1><p>我认为人工智能乐观主义者想象了一个特定的场景或一组场景（也许是“终结者”或[此处插入虚构的特许经营权]）并说“这似乎不太可能”。也许埃利泽提出了另一种情况，乐观主义者说“所有这些加起来都是不可能的”。 “你有任何<strong>证据</strong>证明这种[特定的一小部分场景]会发生吗！？”但人工智能毁灭的空间是<strong>巨大的</strong>，<i>任何</i>失败的场景都会毁掉一切。</p><p>对我来说，人工智能的毁灭似乎是五个简单过程和条件的自然结果：</p><h1>五项核心公理</h1><p>1.<strong>人工智能会变得更好，而不是更糟：</strong>无论你如何定义，人工智能的智能都在不断增强。随着新研究的出现，知识将成为记录的永久部分。与其他技术进步一样，我们在此基础上继续发展，而不是倒退。人们不断地向人工智能投入更多的资源，训练越来越大的模型，而不考虑安全性。</p><p> 2.<strong>智力总是有帮助的：</strong>变得更聪明总是有助于在现实世界中取得成功。智力上的微小优势使人类能够主宰地球。没有理由期望一个比人类更聪明的实体会产生不同的结果。</p><p> 3.<strong>没有人知道如何调整人工智能：</strong>没有人能够精确地指导人工智能与复杂的人类价值观或幸福感保持一致。我们可以针对数据点的可能预测进行优化，但没有人编写过 Python 函数来根据结果对人类的积极程度进行排名。</p><p> 4.<strong>资源是有限的：</strong>任何在现实世界中行动的人工智能都不可避免地与人类争夺资源。这些资源一旦被人工智能消耗，将无法供人类使用，从而导致潜在的冲突。</p><p> 5.<strong>人工智能无法被阻止：</strong>一旦人工智能变得更加智能并且可能有害，就不可能阻止它。阻止不结盟的人工智能需要人类的决策来击败比人类更聪明的决策，但这是不可能的。</p><p>综合起来，这些公理都指向人工智能：变得更聪明，在竞争中超越人类，与人类利益不一致，从人类那里获取资源，并且势不可挡。这些看起来都非常简单（至少对我来说）</p><h1>人类的终极挑战</h1><p>在我看来，这些公理都指向一个简单的结论：人工智能风险是普通说法，人工智能“安全”的概念是极端主义观点，不存在“非凡”证据。</p><p>请让我知道我在这里犯了什么错误，或者我的论点哪里错误。</p><h1>自我推销</h1><p>我正在开发一个小项目，供志同道合的人闲逛和聊天。就在<a href="https://www.together.lol/">Together.lol</a> ，请过来告诉我你的想法。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/g6T6wLyKjSs4RERxo/ordinary-claims-require-ordinary-evidence#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/g6T6wLyKjSs4RERxo/ordinary-claims-require-ordinary-evidence<guid ispermalink="false"> g6T6wLyKjSs4RERxo</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[blake8086]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 22:09:16 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Conversation about paradigms, intellectual progress, social consensus, and AI]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 5, 2023 9:30 PM GMT<br/><br/><p>我在这里有很多想法还没有时间写下来，通过公开对话分享似乎是一个不错的尝试方式。<br><br>一些开放的想法：</p><ul><li>人们谈论人工智能对齐领域是“前范式”的。我不觉得人们在这背后分享了精确的模型，或者至少我不知道其他人这么说的意思是什么。例如，大多数人似乎没有读过库恩的书。</li><li>我曾经认为目标是“成为典范”。我现在认为更好的目标是成为一个能够经历范式创建、范式危机、然后再创造新范式的循环的领域。</li><li>我认为有一些方法可以提高我们做到这一点的能力，并且我希望人们更多地考虑这些方法。</li></ul><p>很高兴向您认为有趣或富有成效的任何方向出发。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ipaWHTiEwEqtuvzrP/conversation-about-paradigms-intellectual-progress-social#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ipaWHTiEwEqtuvzrP/conversation-about-paradigms-intellectual-progress-social<guid ispermalink="false"> ipawhteweqtuvzrp</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruby]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 21:30:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>