<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<atom:link href="https://rsshub.rssforever.com/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2023 年 12 月 22 日星期五 16:14:15 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 5 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Russia arrests head of space equipment maker on suspicion of major fraud]]></title><description><![CDATA[The head of a company that makes navigation systems for Russia's space programme was arrested in Moscow and charged with major fraud, state media reported on Friday.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:41:23 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> BAJEDZSYBFLBRL53TQOZO3AZTU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/head- Russian-space-company-arrested-on-fraud-charges-state-media-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mexican president to boost measures aimed at curbing migration]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said on Friday his government plans to reinforce measures aimed at containing migration as he seeks to assist the United States in dealing with record numbers of people trying to reach the U.S. border.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:39:13 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3SQLYWR4XJL4HOMFL7HFS4EAEI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexican-president-boost-measures-aimed-at-curbing-migration-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[France grounds aircraft bound to Nicaragua with some 300 Indians on board]]></title><description><![CDATA[France has grounded a charter flight headed to Nicaragua carrying 303 Indian passengers, and a judicial investigation into the conditions and purposes of the trip has been launched, local officials in the eastern Marne region said on Friday.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:34:42 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> NAVAGP675RJ2VOKIH5N5XLX4OI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/france-grounds-aircraft-bound-nicaragua-with-some-300-indians-board-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Romanian court rejects Andrew Tate's bid to leave the country while awaiting trial]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Bucharest court on Friday rejected a request by internet personality Andrew Tate to temporarily leave Romania while awaiting trial on human trafficking charges to visit his mother in London.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:31:20 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> Z7F5IHIDHVJNBPM7AWDRSWJMYA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/romanian-court-rejects-andrew-tates-bid-to-leave-country-while-awaiting-trial-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mexico launches coast-to-coast passenger and cargo railway]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexico on Friday launched operations on a train line that crosses the country's narrowest point from the Gulf coast to the Pacific Ocean, kicking off a flagship government project as the administration enters its last months in office.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:20:36 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> NMUC773P4ROCNJA4KG5KLJ3GHA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-launches-coast-to-coast-passenger-cargo-railway-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Kylie Madry]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Turkish commission to meet next week to discuss Swedish NATO bid]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Turkish parliament's foreign affairs commission will sit down again on Tuesday to consider Sweden's NATO membership bid, parliament's website showed on Friday, a first step necessary for ratification.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:00:17 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> PVY2SL74ABKCDOSHKQRW6C63XY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/turkish-parliamentary-commission-discuss-sweden-nato-bid-tuesday-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spaniards rejoice as 'The Fat One' lottery winners revealed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Thrilled Spaniards sang, cheered and celebrated with cava bubbly throughout the country on Friday as the Christmas lottery draw known as "El Gordo" (The Fat One) dished out prizes in a centuries-old tradition that kicks off the holiday season.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 14:46:40 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> LK4AA5X5K5NQTJFRW2P7N5B5XI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/spaniards-rejoice-the-fat-one-lottery-winners-revealed-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Last French troops leave Niger as military cooperation officially ends]]></title><description><![CDATA[The last French troops deployed in Niger to help fight a decade-old Islamist insurgency in the Sahel left the country on Friday, sealing a withdrawal that has dealt a further blow to France's influence in West Africa.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 14:35:18 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> M47AAC7ATFLF5CBWN2HFUV6FUM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/load-french-troops-leave-niger-military-cooperation-officially-ends-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU Commission to mediate on stalemate over Spanish judiciary council]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spanish Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez and the leader of the conservative opposition agreed on Friday to ask the European Commission to mediate an end to a five-year political stalemate over appointments to the body that names judges in Spain.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 14:29:32 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> BUG5Z4JVRVP5ZPASUWGUH464HI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-commission-mediate-stalemate-over-spanish-judiciary-council-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury's Adeyemo says new Russia sanctions order puts bigger burden on banks]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden's new executive order strengthening U.S. sanctions against Russia will put new pressure on banks to ensure that their services are not being used to aid Russia's efforts to circumvent sanctions, U.S. Deputy Treasury Secretary Wally Adeyemo said on Friday.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 13:57:39 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> RJRZMAZ4EBLCPB5Z4KCMFLTLMM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us-treasurys-adeyemo-says-new- Russian-sanctions-order-puts-bigger-burden-on-banks-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine says it downs 24 of 28 Russian drones, debris damages granary]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ukraine shot down 24 of 28 Shahed drones launched by Russia in an overnight attack that damaged residential buildings in Kyiv and an infrastructure facility and grain warehouse in southern regions, officials said.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 12:15:15 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> TIXLT5Q3LFOARALILR6WWD64RI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ukraine-says-it-downs-24-28- Russian-drones-debris-damages-granary-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[At least 31 killed in floods in India's Tamil Nadu]]></title><description><![CDATA[At least 31 people were killed in floods and heavy rain in India's southern state of Tamil Nadu this week, a top federal minister said on Friday, as rescuers struggled to reach scores still stranded in high waters.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 11:41:50 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> N5TQ4NHYCRIXTBNFVHL6Q46T7U</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/india/least-31-killed-floods-india-tamil-nadu-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Praveen Paramasivam]]></author><category>世界</category><category>印度</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US takes aim at financial institutions with new Russia sanctions authority]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden on Friday signed an executive order paving the way for Washington to impose sanctions on financial institutions that help Russia evade sanctions, the White House said in a statement.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 11:05:21 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> U4GBK4D5L5J5DMQLPSYKVPNCRM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-takes-aim-financial-institutions-with-new- Russian-sanctions-authority-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Daphne Psaledakis, Andrea Shalal]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美国</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Congo awaits first provisional election results after messy vote]]></title><description><![CDATA[Voters in Democratic Republic of Congo were waiting on Friday for the first results from general elections after an unscheduled day-long ballot extension that prompted some opposition candidates to cry foul and call for a rerun.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 10:49:34 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 24YW5MUKIFJVTPHW5Y673QZATI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/congo-awaits-first-provisional-election-results-after-messy-vote-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia calls prisoner swap talks delicate, accuses U.S. of leaks]]></title><description><![CDATA[A top Russian diplomat said Moscow and Washington were still engaged in sensitive negotiations over a prisoner exchange, but accused the U.S. side of leaking details to the media.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> POYEGVIEPFIANE6HOXK5RWZ67Y</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ Russia-calls-prisons-swap-talks-delicate-accuses-us-leaks-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Czechs mourn victims of university shooting as police patrol public areas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Czechs mourned the victims of the country's worst mass shooting as police tightened security around schools and other public buildings across the country on Friday after a student gunman killed 14 people at a Prague university building on Thursday.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:02:17 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> JBTeenXIHZI55IUINXLTO6XMJE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/czech-police-patrol-public-areas-university-lectures-off-after-shooting-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Jan Lopatka]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pakistan ex-PM Imran Khan granted bail, but release uncertain]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pakistan's Supreme Court on Friday granted former Prime Minister Imran Khan bail in a case related to a leak of state secrets, but it was not clear how he could be released while serving a three-year sentence for corruption and facing other charges.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 08:56:05 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> QSD47X2YYVLHPJQYX5动物</guid><link/>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/pakistan-top-court-grants-bail-ex-pm-imran-khan-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Norwegian cruise ship towed to Germany after power outage in North Sea storm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Norwegian cruise ship MS Maud is being towed to Bremerhafen in Germany after a violent North Sea storm shattered windows on the bridge, causing a power outage late on Thursday, Danish authorities said on Friday.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 08:54:09 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 4ALBXCBXYNNWJP3J65FITA6SWI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/norwegian-cruise-ship-remains-north-sea-following-storm-power-outage-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Louise Rasmussen, Jacob Gronholt-Pedersen]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel broadens Gaza assault ahead of Security Council aid vote]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israeli forces signalled they were widening their ground offensive with a new push into central Gaza on Friday, as the U.N. Security Council was expected to vote on a resolution to increase humanitarian aid to stave off the threat of famine.]]></description><pubDate> Fri, 22 Dec 2023 01:42:25 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> P6GEO4SKLZIJHCT5FK4FP4XI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/un-security-council-delays-vote-on-gaza-aid-until-friday-2023-12-22/<author><![CDATA[Nidal Al-Mughrabi, Dan Williams]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mass drone attack hits several Kyiv districts]]></title><description><![CDATA[More than two dozen Russian drones targeted Ukraine's capital early on Friday, officials said, injuring two people and damaging residential buildings in Moscow's latest overnight drone strike against Ukraine.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:40:23 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 7BVL26242ZOCLPCURBFSIJQDUA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/drone-hits-kyiv-apartment-building-setting-off-fire-officials-2023-12-21/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item></channel></rss>