<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<atom:link href="https://rsshub.rssforever.com/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2023 年 10 月 17 日，星期二 12:22:46 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 5 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Jordan to host summit between Biden and Egyptian and Palestinian leaders - state media]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/DbDscoq5tdtx1QDbRyfShnCzUTA=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/L4LRCJW4QFKXJECOHDT7GIAUDA.jpg" alt="英国首相里希·苏纳克在伦敦唐宁街会见约旦国王阿卜杜拉二世" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>约旦国王阿卜杜拉二世于 2023 年 10 月 15 日在英国伦敦唐宁街会见英国首相里希·苏纳克时发表讲话。 REUTERS/Hannah McKay/Pool/File Photo</figcaption></figure><p>官方媒体称，约旦周三将在安曼与美国总统乔·拜登以及埃及和巴勒斯坦领导人举行四方峰会，讨论加沙战争对该地区的“危险”影响。</p><p>一份官方声明称，讨论将集中于如何停止“加沙正在进行的战争，以及如何找到能够恢复和平进程的政治视野”。</p><p>约旦国王阿卜杜拉还将分别与埃及总统阿卜杜勒·法塔赫·塞西和巴勒斯坦总统马哈茂德·阿巴斯举行三方峰会。</p><p>国王周二警告不要试图将巴勒斯坦难民推入埃及或约旦，并补充说人道主义局势必须在加沙和约旦河西岸内部得到​​解决。在 1967 年中东战争期间，安曼将包括东耶路撒冷在内的约旦河西岸输给了以色列，该国担心不断扩大的暴力可能会产生影响，因为约旦人口中很大一部分是巴勒斯坦人。</p><span>苏莱曼·哈利迪的报道；克里斯蒂娜·芬奇和亚历克斯·理查森编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 12:02:15 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 4USWKBL6QBJ4ZNOHIPHYIHZU2I</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/jordan-host-summit- Between-biden-egyptian-palestinian-leaders-state-media-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>巴勒斯坦人/峰会（更新 1，PIX） </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Migrant’s drowning in Mediterranean prompts criticism of Malta's rescue policies]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/i4Oq5vqsMT2A2BjlMt94IJ6YJcM=/1000x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/L3ECBCQJXZPEBKJPR3CNPTFLE4.jpg" alt="讲义图片显示，一艘无国界医生组织 (MSF) 救援船靠近一艘在地中海运送移民的橡皮船" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>路透社于 2023 年 10 月 12 日获得的讲义图片显示，2023 年 6 月 24 日，地中海上一艘无国界医生组织 (MSF) 救援船靠近一艘载有中东和非洲移民的橡皮船。MSF/Skye McKee/讲义来自路透社</figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/syZbqXeV_kxQ3dvonaOLb3Xag74=/1000x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/TCQGZQXOSJIYHPD47OU7KCFAUQ.jpg" alt="讲义图片显示，一名在地中海漂流的橡皮船上获救的移民正在拉斯佩齐亚的 Geo Barents 救援船上下船" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>路透社于 2023 年 10 月 12 日获得的讲义图像显示，一名移民从地中海漂流的橡皮船上获救，并从无国界医生组织 (MSF) 在拉斯佩齐亚运营的 Geo Barents 救援船上下来，意大利，2023 年 6 月 27 日。MSF/Skye McKee/路透社讲义</figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/6YK9_JzVi2V_91KPgV7QdpTAf64=/1000x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/4EMBVAYNVZJNPPHNA2O3X7NYHA.jpg" alt="讲义图片显示无国界医生组织 (MSF) 营救在地中海橡皮船上漂流的移民" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>路透社于 2023 年 10 月 12 日获得的讲义图片显示，无国界医生组织 (MSF) 于 2023 年 6 月 24 日营救了在地中海橡皮船上漂流的中东和非洲移民。MSF/Skye麦基/路透社讲义</figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/4IIBcRzRRp8Rl14r3Hi89VVZ8RA=/1000x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/3KOYCIY23FME3J2W53WFMMJL3Q.jpg" alt="讲义图片显示，一名在地中海漂流的橡皮船上获救的移民正在从拉斯佩齐亚的 Geo Barents 救援船上下来" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>路透社于 2023 年 10 月 12 日获得的讲义图像显示，一名移民从一艘在地中海漂流的橡皮船上获救，并从位于意大利拉斯佩齐亚的无国界医生组织 (MSF) 运营的 Geo Barents 救援船上下来。 ，2023 年 6 月 27 日。MSF/Skye McKee/路透社讲义</figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/krCbkLJVTaya39zGrWYYPLdPuBI=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/2TWBJP7T35IQ5GR52AQHFASAW4.jpg" alt="马尔萨什洛克外，被商船救起的移民从马耳他武装部队巡逻艇上下来" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> 2023 年 4 月 17 日，马耳他马尔萨什洛克外，被商船救起的移民正在等待从马耳他武装部队巡逻艇上下来。路透社/Darrin Zammit Lupi</figcaption></figure><p> 6月23日，一艘漂流在地中海的橡皮船上的一名乘客拨打救援热线请​​求帮助。这艘载有 14 名来自中东和非洲移民的船在波涛汹涌的水域中耗尽了燃料。一名男乘客刚刚溺水身亡。</p><p>根据热线运营商 Alarm Phone 记录的位置数据，这艘船距离马耳他海岸约 70 海里，位于这个小岛国的搜救区内。在这些区域内，各国有义务根据国际法协调搜救行动。</p><p>尽管如此，根据对参与救援的人道主义组织的采访以及路透社对这些组织记录事件的笔记、电子邮件和录音的审查，马耳他当局拒绝了这一求救电话以及至少 32 起有关该情况的其他通讯。</p><p>有一次，马耳他救援协调中心的一名接听电话的人拒绝了一名人道主义工作人员打来的有关该船的电话。根据德国非营利搜救组织 Sea-Watch 向路透社提供的通话录音，接线员说：“你让我的线路一直占线。”该组织是接到通知的几家组织之一。有关这艘遇险船只的当局。</p><p>幸存者告诉医疗援助组织无国界医生组织（MSF）的采访者，一艘马耳他军舰最终到达了失事船只，但拒绝了乘客直接的救援请求。路透社对无国界医生行动照片和视频的评论显示，无国界医生的一艘名为“Geo Barents”的船只后来救出了乘客，并将他们带到了意大利。</p><p>据在该地区开展活动的人道主义组织和非政府组织称，这一事件是马耳他拒绝救援载有前往欧洲的移民的船只的最新例子。国际法专家表示，此案尤其令人不安，因为马耳他武装部队据称拒绝援助乘客。</p><p>人道主义组织无国界医生组织、Sea-Watch 和 Alarm Phone 向路透社描述了该事件的细节，但此前尚未报道过。</p><p>南安普顿大学海事法讲师阿伊霍亚·坎帕斯·贝拉斯科 (Ainhoa Campàs Velasco) 表示，马耳他没有及时回应求救信号并协调救援，没有履行国际法规定的义务。 “船的类型、海况、它们都过于拥挤——这是明显的遇险情况。”</p><p>马耳他当局，包括总理办公室的发言人，拒绝回答有关该事件的问题。负责协调搜​​救工作的马耳他武装部队发言人表示，马耳他搜救区有关“非正规移民”的所有报告都“立即跟进”。</p><p>发言人萨布丽娜·博格（Sabrina Borg）在给路透社的电子邮件中写道：“搜救行动是根据适用的国际公约、法规并通过主管当局进行协调的。” “与所有情况一样，主管当局履行注意义务。”</p><p>一位意大利政客四月份指责马耳他未能救助该国搜救区内的遇险船只。执政的意大利兄弟党成员托马索·福蒂在意大利广播节目中表示，马耳他当局“一直假装没有看到，也从不干预”，这给意大利海岸警卫队带来了更大的压力。福蒂没有回应置评请求。</p><p>参与地中海救援的人道主义组织也回应了这一批评。 “根据我们的经验，马耳他不太可能救援，”Sea-Watch 发言人 Oliver Kulikowski 说，该组织在 6 月份帮助最终救援了这艘船。 “马耳他正在尽一切努力避免承担责任并让人们抵达马耳他。”</p><p>内政部发言人表示，马耳他希望建立一个公平、安全的移民和庇护制度，让“真正需要国际保护的人得到迅速承认”，而那些没有合法权利留在马耳他的人则被送回原籍国。马耳他发言人尼尔·阿佐帕尔迪·费里吉 (Neil Azzopardi Ferriggi) 表示，马耳他将继续努力减少导致数千人海上死亡的非法过境。</p><p>他说：“成千上万的人继续冒着生命危险试图到达欧盟，而走私者却继续从移民的希望和痛苦中获利，这是不可接受的。”</p><h 1=""> “尖叫求救”</h><p>在第一次求救信号发出三十九小时后，无国界医生救出了留在船上的三名青少年，其中包括两名妇女和八名男子。该援助小组收集了三名幸存者的证词，并与路透社分享。该通讯社无法独立采访幸存者或确认他们的叙述的全部细节。他们的下落不明。</p><p>两名幸存者告诉无国界医生，这艘橡皮艇于 6 月 21 日凌晨 3 点左右离开利比亚苏尔特。机上有14名来自叙利亚和南苏丹的人，其中包括两名妇女和三名14至17岁的青少年。</p><p> 6 月 22 日下午 4 点 28 分，在海上航行了一天半后，船上有人向 Alarm Phone 拨打了求救电话，该网络将地中海的求救电话转发给紧急服务部门。根据提供给路透社的电子邮件副本，报警电话通过电子邮件向马耳他和意大利当局通报了该船的位置，并指出该船已耗尽燃料。</p><p>电子邮件称：“船上的人正在紧急寻求帮助。”</p><p>根据警报电话记录，在接下来的几个小时内，警报电话通过电子邮件向马耳他和意大利当局通报了该船的最新情况，并至少四次致电马耳他搜救协调中心。所有联系人均未得到回应。</p><p>到第二天早上，即 6 月 23 日，幸存者告诉无国界医生组织，他们已经没有食物和水了。他们将空的燃料容器绑在船的两侧，用作漂浮装置，以防翻船。</p><p>中午12点30分左右，其中一个空燃料容器落入水中，一名23岁的叙利亚男子跳入水中将其捞起。一名27岁目击事件的男子告诉无国界医生，水罐距离船仅一米，但海浪很大，而且他没有穿救生衣。乘客们告诉无国界医生，他们试图将船移近这名叙利亚男子，但没有成功，因为他努力保持在水面上。</p><p>中午12时46分，报警电话致电马耳他搜救协调中心，报告有人落水。位置数据显示，这艘船位于马耳他东南部 74 海里处，位于该国的搜救区内。</p><p>根据报警电话的通话记录，在搜救协调中心接听电话的人立即挂断了电话。</p><p>幸存者告诉无国界医生，这名叙利亚男子最终消失在海浪之下。</p><p>一小时后，Sea-Watch 运营的一架飞机发现了这艘漂流船。根据海洋观察发给马耳他当局的电子邮件副本，只有少数人穿着救生衣。根据 Sea-Watch 工作人员记录并经路透社分析的位置数据和视频，最近的船只是一艘马耳他巡逻艇，距离 15 海里，正驶向马耳他。</p><p>海洋观察工作人员表示，海洋观察向马耳他武装部队 P51 号巡逻船发送了 3 次无线电信号，但没有得到回应。马耳他武装部队负责管理该国的搜救协调中心，负责协调和指导马耳他境内的救援工作。</p><p>海洋观察组织还发出了五一节呼吁，召唤附近的船只来帮助漂流的船只。海洋观察工作人员表示，马耳他当局或巡逻艇均未做出回应。</p><p> “这就像拨打 911，但紧急热线没有回应，”海洋观察发言人库利科斯基说。</p><p>根据船舶追踪数据，一艘挂着加蓬旗的油轮“拉科尼亚”号确实响应了五一劳动节的号召，并改变了航线，在该船旁边停泊了两个多小时。根据油轮船长和海洋观察工作人员之间的对话录音，油轮于晚上 9 点 20 分左右出发，一艘快艇的船员自称是马耳他武装部队，要求船长将船只的监控交给他们。该油轮的船长和船东没有回应置评请求。马耳他武装部队拒绝就油轮的参与发表评论。</p><h 1="">入境人数急剧下降</h><p>目前还没有地中海遇险呼叫和海上救援的官方统计数据。但近年来，随着欧洲其他地区的移民数量激增，马耳他通过海路抵达的移民数量急剧下降。</p><p>联合国难民事务高级专员的数据显示，2022 年有超过 152,000 人经地中海抵达欧洲，较 2019 年增加了 49%。这些年来，意大利的海上入境人数增加了 814%，从 11,500 人增至 105,131 人。马耳他的入境人数下降了 87%，从 3,406 人减少到 444 人。</p><p>国际特赦组织 2020 年的一份报告指责马耳他拖延或拒绝救援。报告称，其中一些事件涉及的船只在被“推回”利比亚之前已经到达马耳他搜救区。该报告引用了移民证词、非政府组织、政府消息来源和媒体报道。</p><p>马耳他否认参与抵制活动，欧洲人权法院宣布这种活动违反国际法。</p><p>马耳他领导人表示，这个人口仅超过 50 万的小国无法像意大利这样的富裕国家那样轻松应对大量移民的涌入，意大利的人口是马耳他的 100 多倍。内政部长拜伦·卡米莱里 (Byron Camilleri) 在 10 月 7 日与其他欧盟官员举行的会议上对无证移民采取了强硬立场。卡米莱里表示，抵达马耳他的移民中有 70% 已被遣返，重要的是“发出明确的信息，他们没有权利留下来”。</p><p>批评人士称，这一立场推动了马耳他的搜救行动。英国国际与比较法研究所研究移民法的马耳他学者让-皮埃尔·高奇表示：“他们感兴趣的是关闭边境，阻止人们抵达，而不是履行搜救义务。”</p><h 1="">救援人员介入</h><p>幸存者告诉无国界医生，一艘马耳他巡逻艇于 6 月 23 日日落后抵达漂流船，此时距离这名年轻人溺水已有十多个小时。三名身穿白色防护服的男子给了乘客能量饼干、手电筒和三加仑燃料，并敦促他们继续前往意大利。位置数据显示，该船当时距离意大利超过 78 海里。</p><p>幸存者告诉无国界医生，乘客告诉这些人他们很害怕，不想留在船上。</p><p>几个小时后，橡皮艇再次耗尽燃料。幸存者告诉无国界医生，马耳他巡逻艇返航后又给乘客提供了三个集装箱燃料。</p><p>一艘无国界医生船只于6月23日深夜抵达该地区，船员通知马耳他当局他们可以营救乘客。等了几个小时后，没有得到回应，无国界医生接起了13名幸存者，并将他们带到意大利拉斯佩齐亚。无国界医生组织的工作人员不知道乘客之后发生了什么，因为该组织在移民离开救援船后并没有追踪他们。</p><p>无国界医生组织向路透社提供了一名幸存者在途中创作的一幅图画的副本。它描绘了一名落水男子高高举起双臂的情景。在底角，艺术家用阿拉伯语写道：“愿上帝安息他的灵魂。”</p><span>里德·莱文森在伦敦的报道。珍妮特·罗伯茨编辑。</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:42:44 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 44VUFJ2C3JPOZDRMULDWLUWOFQ</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/migrants-drowning-mediterranean-prompts-criticism-maltas-rescue-policies-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reade Levinson]]></author><category>欧洲</category><category>移民/马耳他（PIX，图）） </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[France's Palace of Versailles being evacuated for security reasons]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/g6XCMfWNBMlMuYkfceZTS9FhERo=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/PYG33PB7ONORLG77QYV7E3TXJE.jpg" alt="英国国王查尔斯首次对法国进行国事访问" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> 2023 年 9 月 20 日，英国王室对法国进行国事访问的第一天，法国共和国卫队在巴黎以西的凡尔赛宫举行国宴前肃立。丹尼尔·莱尔/泳池来自路透社/档案照片</figcaption></figure><p>法国凡尔赛宫在社交网络 X 上表示，出于安全原因，法国凡尔赛宫正在疏散游客，并将于周二关闭。</p><p> BFM 电视台援引警方消息称，拆弹小组正在前往现场。</p><p> 10 月 14 日，一名教师在伊斯兰袭击中丧生一天后，炸弹警报（后来被证明是假的）迫使卢浮宫博物馆、凡尔赛宫和巴黎里昂火车站进行疏散。</p><span>多米尼克·维达隆报道；编辑：Benoit Van Overstraeten</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> FHPIFM4GFVJJVH4AVO7GQ7Q42U</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/frances-palace-versailles-being-evacuated-security-reasons-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>法国</category><category>安全/凡尔赛宫（更新 1） </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Azerbaijan to host military exercises with Turkey next week]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>阿塞拜疆周二表示，下周将与其亲密盟友土耳其举行军事演习。</p><p>这个以突厥族为主的南高加索国家国防部在其网站上表示，纪念土耳其共和国成立一百周年的演习将于10月23日至25日在多个地区举行。</p><p>其中包括首都巴库、纳希切万地区以及自 2020 年以来从亚美尼亚族控制下夺取的阿塞拜疆领土，土耳其对此表示欢迎。</p><p>纳希切万与土耳其和伊朗接壤，但在地理上与阿塞拜疆大陆隔着亚美尼亚。</p><p>上个月，阿塞拜疆总统伊利哈姆· <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/azerbaijani-turkish-leaders-hold-talks-eye-forging-land-corridor-via-armenia-2023-09-25/">阿利耶夫</a>在纳希切万与土耳其总统塔伊普·埃尔多安举行会谈，不到一周后，阿塞拜疆军队席卷了亚美尼亚族控制的纳戈尔诺-卡拉巴赫地区，这是阿塞拜疆最后一个不受巴库控制的地区。</p><p>在会议上，阿利耶夫得到了埃尔多安对在阿塞拜疆西部和纳希切万之间途经亚美尼亚建立陆地走廊的支持，但埃尔多安反对这一想法。</p><span>路透社报道；凯文·利菲 (Kevin Liffey) 撰写；亚历克斯·理查森编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:31:00 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> NS2R6JZBQVOXVHCMZ4TB4XCGF4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/azerbaijan-host-military-exercises-with-turkey-next-week-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>阿塞拜疆</category><category>火鸡/ </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scotland's leader says dream of independence alive despite his party's troubles]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/6CH1JWLwKkorpAt0El14ZaVM9Cw=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/NVYW73E3PJMUVEVUGB2J26PILA.jpg" alt="苏格兰民族党领袖胡姆扎·优素福在英国阿伯丁举行的苏格兰民族党年度会议之前接受路透社采访" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>苏格兰首席部长兼苏格兰民族党 (SNP) 领导人胡姆扎·优素福于 2023 年 10 月 16 日在英国阿伯丁举行的苏格兰民族党年度会议之前接受路透社采访。 REUTERS/Gerhard May</figcaption></figure><p>苏格兰领导人胡姆扎·优素福相信，他的独立梦想将在未来十年实现，尽管他的执政党因现代历史上最严重的危机而失去了支持。</p><p>支持独立的苏格兰民族党是苏格兰近二十年的主导政党，但由于内讧、选民疲劳和丑闻（包括其魅力十足的前领导人尼古拉·斯特金被捕）而受到损害。</p><p>英国主要反对党工党本月在苏格兰赢回了一个议会席位，在一次投票中驱逐了苏格兰民族党，这表明该党的数十名政客可能会在下次选举中失去席位，而上周另一名苏格兰民族党议员因欺凌指控而叛逃到保守党。</p><p> “这很困难，假装没有任何意义。这可能是我们党在现代历史上面临的最困难的六个月，”优素福在阿伯丁举行的政党年度会议上告诉路透社。</p><p> “不幸的是，这些事情向你袭来，不是一两个，而是给你带来了许多挑战。但尽管面临这些挑战，如果你看看几乎每一次的民意调查，你会发现我们继续领先反对派。”</p><p>在 2019 年的上一次选举中，苏格兰民族党获得了 59 个席位中的 48 个，成为西欧最具统治力的政党之一。但 YouGov 上周的一项民意调查显示，苏格兰工党的支持率仅为两个百分点。工党曾经是苏格兰的主导党，在 2019 年赢得了一个席位。</p><h 1=""> “坚如磐石”的独立支持</h><p>优素福表示，他对独立的苏格兰即将到来充满信心。尽管苏格兰民族党的支持率下降，但民意调查显示苏格兰在独立问题上仍存在大致分歧。</p><p> “对独立的支持坚如磐石，但对苏格兰民族党的支持有所下降，”他说。当被问及苏格兰是否会在未来十年内获得独立时，他说：“毫无疑问。我希望这会在十年内实现。”</p><p> 2014 年，苏格兰人以 55% 比 45% 的投票结果拒绝结束与英格兰长达 300 多年的联盟。但民族主义者认为，2016 年脱欧公投改变了一切，因为大多数苏格兰选民都反对。</p><p>在前首相鲍里斯·约翰逊的领导下，支持独立的情绪更加强烈，他在苏格兰极不受欢迎。</p><p>优素福表示，他需要提出一个关于独立的苏格兰的积极愿景，包括更好地保护工人和努力解决贫困问题，因为批评伦敦首相里希·苏纳克政府只能到此为止。</p><p>他认为，对独立的持续支持也将有助于克服未来最大的战役——说服威斯敏斯特政府同意举行第二次公投。</p><p>英国最高法院去年表示，未经英国议会批准，苏格兰政府不得举行第二次独立公投。</p><p>优素福周末表示，如果苏格兰民族党在预计明年的全国大选中赢得苏格兰威斯敏斯特多数席位，他将有权就新的投票进行谈判，但这一立场已被亲英政党拒绝。</p><p> “我们要做的就是创造政治条件，让威斯敏斯特政党不能否认苏格兰的声音，”他说。 “如果苏格兰民族党没有获胜，那么独立事业也不会获胜。”</p><span>安德鲁·麦克阿斯基尔 (Andrew MacAskill) 报道，凯特·霍尔顿 (Kate Holton) 和埃德·奥斯蒙德 (Ed Osmond) 编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:25:29 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> OOSATJDTLBLS3PVZBBFJ3I5FZA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/scotlands-leader-says-dream-independence-alive-despite-his-partys-troubles-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Andrew Macaskill]]></author><category>英国</category><category>政治/苏格兰</category><category>尤萨夫</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Analysis: Israel-Palestinian conflict tests Japan's oil diplomacy]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/Gr19C-nSFXwmbyRc0s-pBV4w9HE=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/GU23KMEWRFNC7AL57H7PC6DSJQ.jpg" alt="日本鹿儿岛县志布志国家石油储备基地鸟瞰图" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>共同社拍摄的这张照片于 2019 年 1 月 18 日鸟瞰日本鹿儿岛县志布志国家石油储备基地。照片拍摄于 2019 年 1 月 18 日。强制信用 Kyodo/via REUTERS 注意编辑 - 此图片由第三方提供。强制性信用。日本出局。在日本不得进行商业或社论销售。/资料照片</figcaption></figure><p>当东京本月忙于回应哈马斯对以色列的袭击时，日本官员发现自己在争论一个长期存在的担忧：这对这个资源匮乏国家来自中东的石油生命线意味着什么？</p><p>三名知情政府消息人士称，对能源安全的担忧以及日本在该地区的多元化外交利益，解释了为什么东京最初在这场危机上比其他七国集团（G7）工业化国家采取了更为中立的态度。</p><p>官员和分析人士表示，虽然日本此后采取了更大胆的言辞，但其犹豫不决也可能使日本如何与七国集团其他国家达成统一立场变得复杂，因为日本准备下个月在东京主办七国集团外长会议，冲突不断升级。预计将占据主导地位。</p><p>日本外务大臣上川洋子在周三的新闻发布会上回答路透社的提问时表示，“当地局势每时每刻都在变化。日本每次都针对最新局势表达立场。”东京的反应是否比其他国家更加克制。</p><p>当被问及日本对中东石油的依赖程度时，她补充道：“该地区的和平与稳定对于（日本）能源安全非常重要。从这个角度来看，日本正在密切关注局势，并表示严重关切。”其需求的%。</p><p> 10 月 7 日，哈马斯枪手在以色列城镇肆虐后，以色列对哈马斯统治的加沙飞地进行了轰炸， <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/diplomats-renew-calls-gaza-aid-iran-warns-israel-2023-10-16/">这增加了伊朗、其黎巴嫩盟友真主党和叙利亚之间爆发更广泛地区战争的风险</a>。</p><p>尽管到目前为止，冲突对全球石油和天然气供应影响不大，而且以色列也不是重要的生产国，但投资者和市场观察人士正在评估冲突如何升级，以及这对世界顶级石油周边国家的供应可能意味着什么。产地。</p><h 1=""> “走好路线”</h><p>哈马斯袭击事件发生后，日本立即发表声明谴责此次袭击，并表示对以色列对加沙地带的空袭表示担忧。</p><p>直到 10 月 11 日，日本才将哈马斯的袭击称为“恐怖主义”，也没有提及以色列的自卫权——这是七国集团同行所使用的语言。</p><p>日本首相岸田文雄也不在 10 月 9 日签署危机声明的五位 G7 领导人之列，这引发了人们对该组织应对措施是否统一的质疑。</p><p>随着事件升级，七国集团财长在摩洛哥举行会议，并于 10 月 12 日就袭击事件发表了一份简短声明。</p><p>参与该声明谈判的一位不愿透露姓名的政府官员表示，日本一直渴望避免使用任何可能被视为挑衅性的语言。</p><p>日本中东研究所副研究员中岛勇补充道，日本“落后美国和一些欧洲国家一步”。</p><p>几十年来，日本一直试图通过呼吁谈判解决巴以争端，走中立路线，尽管它批评以色列允许在该国1967年边界之外建设定居点。</p><p>对于东京来说，这种做法是由1973年石油危机的痛苦记忆推动的，当时中东产油国对包括日本在内的在以色列与阿拉伯国家战争期间支持以色列的国家实施了禁运。</p><p>与美国不同，能源匮乏的日本此后一直试图与该地区的主要竞争对手和主要石油生产国沙特阿拉伯和伊朗建立友好关系。</p><p>咨询公司欧亚集团董事戴维·博林表示：“日本中东政策的主线是维持从该地区进口能源的流动。”</p><p> “东京将担心如何应对这场危机，因为担心会危及这条生命线。”</p><p>一位不愿透露姓名的美国官员表示，东京和华盛顿在这场危机上的立场存在“一些差距”，日本在应对事件时“走得很好”，同时维护了其在该地区的利益。</p><p>日本能源经济研究所董事会成员保坂修二表示，虽然美国是日本最亲密的盟友，但在中东问题上，东京将非常警惕，以免被视为其代理人。</p><p> “在阿拉伯国家的普通民众看来，日本可能正在追随美国的脚步，这可能会给日本带来一些后果，”保坂说。</p> <span>John Geddie、Yoshifumi Takemoto、Tim Kelly、Ekaterina Golubkova、Kiyoshi Takenaka 和 Kentaro Sugiyama 在东京报道；亚历克斯·理查森编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:19:14 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 7G5ADTNJPRMNZJC44FFTYUY7N4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/israel-palestinian-conflict-tests-japans-oil-diplomacy-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[John Geddie, Yoshifumi Takemoto, Tim Kelly]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>巴勒斯坦/日本（分析，PIX） </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dutch government pledges 10 million euros in extra aid to Gaza]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/1RyycieWVJEtAo9FUBXibxajGQg=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/A347VLSCMZPD3HW4NRLTSV4LUI.jpg" alt="以色列空袭拉法的后果" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> 2023 年 10 月 17 日，巴勒斯坦人聚集在以色列袭击加沙地带南部拉法房屋的地点。REUTERS/Ibraheem Abu Mustafa</figcaption></figure><p>荷兰政府周二承诺向加沙提供1000万欧元（1050万美元）的额外人道主义援助，并表示非常担心当地人民迅速恶化的局势。</p><p>政府表示，这些资金是应联合国的要求提供的，将用于满足水和医疗保健等基本需求。</p><p>它重申其立场，即以色列有权在哈马斯发动毁灭性袭击后自卫，但其反应应该是“相称的”并符合国际战争规则。</p><p>荷兰对外贸易和发展部长利耶·施赖内马赫（Liesje Schreinemacher）在给议会的一封信中表示：“平民或人道主义援助工作者永远不应该成为暴力的目标，人道主义援助应该不受限制地获得。”</p> <span>Stephanie van den Berg 和 Bart Meijer 报道；艾莉森·威廉姆斯和克里斯蒂娜·芬奇编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:17:46 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 4CDTJFSCLVK7VFVWT2FHVVXXO4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/dutch-government-pledges-10-million-euros-extra-aid-gaza-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>巴勒斯坦/荷兰</category><category>援助（更新 1） </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spain to ramp up aid to Gaza by 1 million euros, ready to send more]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>西班牙代理外交部长在周二的新闻发布会上表示，西班牙将增加对加沙地带的人道主义援助，提供价值 100 万欧元（106 万美元）的一揽子援助，并准备提供更多援助。</p><p>何塞·曼努埃尔·阿尔瓦雷斯表示，“援助必须送达加沙平民，西班牙已经准备好并愿意参与”人道主义努力，并补充说“将会有更多援助物资，因为一切都表明需要更多（援助）”。</p><p>周一，以色列驻马德里大使馆表示，在三名左翼部长批评以色列轰炸加沙后，一些西班牙官员站在巴勒斯坦激进组织哈马斯一边，但西班牙外交部在一份声明中<a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-says-some-spanish-officials-align-with-hamas-government-rejects-2023-10-16/">否认了这一说法</a>。</p><p>马德里重申，强烈谴责哈马斯对以色列的袭击，同时呼吁保护加沙平民，并表示“在西班牙这样的民主国家”，任何政党代表都可以自由表达自己的立场。</p><p>当被问及外交争端时，阿尔瓦雷斯称这是双边关系中的一次“一次性事件”，该事件已通过其外交部的声明和个人致电大使得到解决，他在电话中将以色列大使馆的指控描述为对以色列的“不友好姿态”。马德里。</p><p> （1 美元 = 0.9473 欧元）</p> <span>Inti Landauro 和 Emma Pinedo 报道；大卫·拉托纳 (David Latona) 撰写；编辑：Andrei Khalip 和 Emelia Sithole-Matarise</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:54:17 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> KGBI74PQLFLYJJIR5SDR6QCZPM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/spain-ramp-up-aid-gaza-by-1-million-euros-ready-send-more-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>巴勒斯坦/西班牙</category><category>援助（更新 1） </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iran's Guards commander warns of another shockwave if Israel does not end "atrocities"]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>伊朗官方媒体周二援引伊朗精锐革命卫队副指挥官的话说，如果以色列在加沙的“暴行”不停止，以色列将面临抵抗阵线的另一次冲击。</p><p>阿里·法达维说：“抵抗阵线对犹太复国主义政权（以色列）的冲击将持续下去，直到这个‘毒瘤’从世界地图上被根除。”</p><p> “如果以色列不结束加沙的暴行，另一波冲击即将到来。”</p><span>帕里莎·哈菲兹 (Parisa Hafezi) 撰稿；艾莉森·威廉姆斯编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:38:44 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> GDMXNOQQV5NODO2QGTV2FCNJ6Y</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/irans-guards-commander-warns-another-shockwave-if-israel-does-not-end-atrocities-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>巴勒斯坦/伊朗</category><category>警卫（紧急） </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Armenia ready to sign peace deal with Azerbaijan by year-end - TASS cites PM]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/GxpR2yvlqzGpeEYTOO8BH_N72S0=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/BA467IZOFNNWFFJW4IHFGFBEHQ.jpg" alt="亚美尼亚总理帕希尼扬在埃里温向议会发表讲话" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption>亚美尼亚总理 Nikol Pashinyan 于 2022 年 9 月 13 日在亚美尼亚埃里温向议会发表讲话。Tigran Mehrabyan/PAN 照片来自路透社 注意编辑 - 此图片由第三方提供。强制性信用/档案照片</figcaption></figure><p>据俄罗斯塔斯社报道，亚美尼亚总理尼科尔·帕希尼扬周二表示，亚美尼亚准备在今年年底前与阿塞拜疆签署和平协议，并将保证其领土上所有阿塞拜疆公民的安全。</p><p>俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔·普京上周表示，他相信，如果亚美尼亚和阿塞拜疆双方都表现出善意，就可以达成和平协议，并淡化了就共同边界达成协议的难度。</p><p>阿塞拜疆上个月发动闪电攻势，夺取了纳戈尔诺-卡拉巴赫分裂地区的控制权，该地区在亚美尼亚的支持下一直由亚美尼亚人统治了三十年。</p><p>卡拉巴赫约 12 万亚美尼亚人中的大多数逃往亚美尼亚。</p><span>路透社报道；亚历山大·马罗 (Alexander Marrow) 撰写；凯文·利菲编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:34:09 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 57ONBW3C25LYTP2YNCYZ4QSNJY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/armenia-ready-sign-peace-deal-with-azerbaijan-by-year-end-tass-cites-pm-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>亚美尼亚</category><category>AZERBAIJAN/PEACE (URGENT) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Analysis: Indonesian court ruling casts shadow over integrity of 2024 election]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/adjWvbUuioGyhzU6AChORNVQzYg=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/2C5JYK4BXVOEDCTQKFYBRODOGQ.jpg" alt="Indonesia Democratic Party of Struggle (PDIP) National Meeting in Jakarta" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Ganjar Pranowo, Indonesia Democratic Party of Struggle (PDIP) candidate in the 2024 presidential election, talks with Indonesian President Joko Widodo, as they attend the party&#39;s national meeting in Jakarta, Indonesia, September 29, 2023. REUTERS/Willy Kurniawan/File Photo</figcaption></figure><p> Days before candidates officially register for Indonesia&#39;s elections, a game-changing ruling by the nation&#39;s constitutional court has sparked concern over the integrity of the vote in the world&#39;s third-largest democracy.</p><p> On Monday, the court removed the 40 years minimum age requirement for presidential or vice-presidential candidates if they had previously been elected to regional posts, potentially opening the way for President Joko Widodo&#39;s 36-year-old son to contest.</p><p> The ruling, issued by a court headed by the president&#39;s brother-in-law, has raised fears of a resurgence of patronage politics in a country that only 25 years ago emerged from the authoritarian rule of strongman leader Suharto.</p><p> &quot;I don&#39;t think there is a single person in Indonesia who wasn&#39;t aware the application was fundamentally about whether the president&#39;s son could run as a vice presidential candidate,&quot; said Tim Lindsey, an expert in Indonesian law at the University of Melbourne.</p><p> The court and the presidential palace did not immediately respond to requests for comment.</p><p> The Southeast Asian nation will hold simultaneous presidential and legislative election on Feb. 14 next year. Jokowi, as the president is known, is ineligible to run after serving the maximum two terms.</p><p> But Monday&#39;s ruling paves the way for his eldest son and mayor of Surakarta city, Gibran Rakabuming Raka.</p><p> The decision comes amid rampant speculation the president - once lauded for breaking the mould of the Suharto-era old guard - is lining up his son to become the vice-presidential running mate of Defence Minister Prabowo Subianto, who is now leading in the polls.</p><p> Gibran is one of the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesian-presidents-son-among-strongest-vp-candidates-prabowo-party-official-2023-10-17/">strongest potential running mates</a> for Prabowo, an official at the former general&#39;s Gerindra party said on Tuesday.</p><p> Analysts say Jokowi&#39;s support will provide a significant boost for Prabowo, Suharto&#39;s former son-in-law and also the son of a former cabinet minister.</p><p> The Indonesian leader was earlier seen likely to be <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/jokowi-indonesias-kingmaker-works-keep-influence-after-election-2023-10-14/">hedging his bets</a> between the top two contenders for president, but the analysts said the court decision implies he will back Prabowo.</p><p> Prabowo, 72, lost to Jokowi in the previous two presidential elections.</p><p> &quot;It&#39;s a scandalous decision because many Indonesians see it as the court losing independence, and a conflict of interest and intimidation leading it to allow the current president, who can&#39;t sit for a third term, make up for that by building a dynasty,&quot; said Lindsey.</p><p> The decision, said Bivitri Susanti of Indonesia&#39;s Jentera School of Law, was &quot;worse than Suharto&quot;.</p><h 1=""> SITTING &#39;DODO&#39;</h><p> As the popular leader of the Southeast Asia&#39;s largest economy, analysts say Jokowi has been manoeuvring behind the scenes to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/jokowi-indonesias-kingmaker-works-keep-influence-after-election-2023-10-14/">safeguard</a> his legacy and extend his influence beyond his term in office.</p><p> An adept political operator, Jokowi may be betting that his high approval ratings will help him weather any backlash, but Goenawan Mohamad, founder of investigative magazine Tempo, said that was a gamble set to fail.</p><p> &quot;In 2024, Jokowi will not be at the centre of power. He will not be a lame-duck power, he will be a dodo. It is hubris to think that his popularity will stay intact, or his son will survive the political revenge,&quot; he said.</p><p> What is remarkable, analysts say, is that Jokowi has managed to stay so popular despite critics pointing to a trend of democratic regression, including the weakening of state institutions.</p><p> Judge Saldi Isra, one of four dissenting judges in the nine-judge bench that issued Monday&#39;s rulings, said he was perturbed by the seemingly contradictory stands taken by his colleagues, who previously rejected similar petitions.</p><p> &quot;This is the first time that I came across an extraordinarily strange event, which can be described as beyond the limits of fair reasoning,&quot; he said.</p><p> Elections in Indonesia are often colourful and boisterous, and invariably followed by election disputes, applications for which are filed at the constitutional court.</p><p> &quot;The court decision has destroyed the people&#39;s trust in an independent judiciary and any future political dispute will easily tear the country apart,&quot; said Tempo&#39;s Goenawan.</p><p> The Jakarta Post, Indonesia&#39;s leading English-language daily, said in an editorial: &quot;We must raise a red flag over the probity of the upcoming election. The game appears rigged to give certain players the upper hand.&quot;</p> <span>Editing by Raju Gopalakrishnan</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:22:50 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> DPFOQRTFRFP55NW67SDSYXM5SA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesian-court-ruling-casts-shadow-over-integrity-2024-election-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Kate Lamb, Ananda Teresia]]></author><category> INDONESIA</category><category> ELECTION/ (ANALYSIS, PIX) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Argentina's young electorate faces a one-in-a-generation vote]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/p7aJaJXRl45cc__ar2X4e9GGd2Q=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/7GEKAI5LGNPKZFYKV3OWZAIJVU.jpg" alt="Argentina's youth voters stare into the political void" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Simon Rubinstein, 17, casts his first vote ever, in the presidential primary election, in Buenos Aires, Argentina August 13, 2023. REUTERS/Magali Druscovich </figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/qn4xSYbhhlSyDAAD9NUCjZ26dq0=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/7HKHLUU6YRIKVFL7ZRPY23YJSY.jpg" alt="Argentina's youth voters stare into the political void" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Simon Rubinstein, 17, casts his first vote ever, in the presidential primary election, in Buenos Aires, Argentina August 13, 2023. REUTERS/Magali Druscovich </figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/HF1iJa4hTyeJxA-aZsTJW5tSqq4=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/U3VOGTXN3FPSTIPRAS2IANYXEQ.jpg" alt="Argentina's youth voters stare into the political void" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Tomas Kremenchuzky, 17, rides the bus home after school, in Buenos Aires, Argentina August 8, 2023. REUTERS/Magali Druscovich</figcaption></figure><p> Argentine teenager Tomas Kremenchuzky is getting ready to vote in his first ever <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentinas-presidential-election-who-are-candidates-what-is-stake-2023-10-13/">presidential election</a> on Oct. 22, the most open and uncertain race in his lifetime, where the frontrunner candidate is threatening to upend the country&#39;s economic model.</p><p> Argentina is one of a handful of Latin American countries that allows 16 and 17-year-olds the right to vote. Kremenchuzky, nicknamed &quot;Toto,&quot; 17, is part of that teenage electorate.</p><p> Many young Argentines are struggling to find opportunities in a country where a cost-of-living crisis and triple-digit inflation has compounded investor wariness after years of political and economic volatility.</p><p> That has been a big factor in the popularity of the presidential frontrunner - wild-haired and brash political outsider, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/wielding-chainsaw-huge-dollar-bill-argentine-radical-taps-into-voter-fury-2023-09-15/">Javier Milei</a> , who wears leather jackets, sings rock songs to his fans, berates &quot;thieving&quot; politicians and wants to &quot;burn down&quot; the central bank.</p><p> &quot;Because of the way Milei speaks, I buy everything he says. He&#39;s got a way of expressing himself that reaches people,&quot; said Toto, who comes from a well-off family, plays soccer and goes to a private school in Buenos Aires.</p><p> In an August open primary vote, Toto voted for conservative Patricia Bullrich - which he puts down to influence from his parents - but says he could shift his vote in October to Milei if the libertarian convinces him in election debates.</p><p> &quot;Milei proposes something different, which later in practice may turn out to very good - or very bad,&quot; Toto said.</p><p> However, Milei&#39;s conservative social views and promise of sharp cuts to government spending are off-putting to some young voters.</p><p> Rocio Pozzetti, 16, who attends a public art school, fears Milei will undo social safety nets, hitting the poor the hardest. She is voting for Peronist ruling party candidate Sergio Massa, despite the economic turbulence he has overseen as economy minister.</p><p> &quot;Massa is the only candidate who represents my ideals and can build a better country, with social justice,&quot; Pozzetti said. &quot;It is worrying that people support Milei.&quot;</p><h 1=""> EVERYONE IS ANGRY WITH POLITICIANS</h><p> Pozzetti, who studies theater and dance, said she understands the anger pushing people to ditch the familiar in favor of the unknown.</p><p> &quot;I think many voted for Milei because he was a new face and he represents all that anger that everyone has with politics and so they could identify with him,&quot; said Pozzetti.</p><p> Noelle Chab, an 18-year-old Buenos Aires resident, voted for Milei in the primaries and will do so again in October because she believes he represents change and she wants to &quot;remove&quot; the Peronist government.</p><p> &quot;Javier Milei is the only one who represents a change in Argentine politics,&quot; said Chab. &quot;It is evident that this is the worst government in Argentine history, it did a lot of harm and continues to do harm.&quot;</p><p> Simon Rubinstein, 17, a fan of soccer, Formula 1 and &quot;Star Wars,&quot; likes Milei&#39;s ideas about shrinking the state, but is afraid of some of his proposals, including dollarization and laxer controls on guns.</p><p> &quot;Because of the country&#39;s economic situation, regardless of who wins, there are going to be at least a few bad years,&quot; said Rubinstein, who voted for Bullrich in the primary.</p><p> The young voters all said they worry about Milei&#39;s socially conservative views, including his strong anti-abortion stance. Abortion was legalized in Argentina in late 2020 and would be difficult to overturn.</p><p> &quot;It seems to me it will be impossible for people to endorse him on this issue and that the abortion law will continue to be as it is now,&quot; Toto said.</p> <span>Reporting by Magali Druscovich and Lucila Sigal, writing by Adam Jourdan, Editing by Rosalba O&#39;Brien</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:08:32 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3R2P2GBXXJKUPCT56HB37FSHZ4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentinas-young-electorate-faces-one-in-a-generation-vote-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Magali Druscovich, Lucila Sigal]]></author><category> ARGENTINA</category><category> ELECTION/YOUTH (PIX) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russian lawmakers approve revoking ratification of nuclear test ban treaty in first reading]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/Xx7u2pOac_OpLFN_g11s530vJ38=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/7LCKJT63GBI4LNZFBCUNMES2FY.jpg" alt="俄罗斯总理米舒斯京出席在莫斯科举行的国家杜马会议" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Russia&#39;s Prime Minister Mikhail Mishustin delivers a speech during a session of the State Duma, the lower house of parliament, in Moscow, Russia April 7, 2022. Sputnik/Alexander Astafyev/Pool via REUTERS/File Photo</figcaption></figure><p> Russia&#39;s lower house of parliament, the State Duma, approved revoking the ratification of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty in the first of three readings on Tuesday.</p><p> The vote was passed by 412 votes to zero, with no abstentions. Duma Speaker Vyacheslav Volodin said Russia was revoking the treaty because of the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-is-revoking-ratification-nuclear-test-ban-treaty-parliament-speaker-2023-10-17/">irresponsible attitude</a> of the United States to global security.</p><span>路透社报道；亚历山大·马罗 (Alexander Marrow) 撰写； Editing by Mark Trevelyan</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:50:24 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 2H5VOSUBWVOEXNGR23E6UCFPAA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russian-lawmakers-approve-revoking-ratification-nuclear-test-ban-treaty-first-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category> NUCLEAR</category><category> RUSSIA/DUMA (URGENT) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israeli military still looking into killing of Reuters journalist - spokesperson]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p> Israel&#39;s military is still looking into the killing of a Reuters journalist in Lebanon near the border with Israel, a spokesperson said on Tuesday.</p><p> &quot;The Reuters event, we&#39;re still looking into it. I&#39;m looking at the footage and we&#39;ll come out with an answer when we&#39;re ready. A tragic event,&quot; Lieutenant-Colonel Richard Hecht told a regular press briefing.</p><p> Issam Abdallah, a Reuters visual journalist, was killed on Friday when rocket fire hit a group of reporters who had been covering cross-border clashes between Israel and Lebanese Hezbollah fighters. Several other journalists were wounded.</p> <span>Reporting by James MacKenzie, John Davison; Editing by Jon Boyle</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:10:30 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> QWF4ZENXO5O4LD6PGENALIP544</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-military-still-looking-into-killing-reuters-journalist-spokesperson-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>PALESTINIANS/JOURNALIST (URGENT) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Biden heading to Israel and Jordan, focused on ground offensive and humanitarian crisis]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/HUqzYRPdOZe3Fa8KS5mSN1nlAaA=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/27CKMC5FMBMBVI275L4WSJJZO4.jpg" alt="U.S. President Biden meets with Israel's President Netanyahu during UNGA in New York City" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> US President Joe Biden holds a bilateral meeting with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on the sidelines of the 78th UN General Assembly in New York City, US, September 20, 2023. REUTERS/Kevin Lamarque/File Photo</figcaption></figure><p> US President Joe Biden leaves on Tuesday on a whirlwind trip to Israel and Jordan to get an update on Israel&#39;s war aims in its looming battle with Hamas militants and stress the need to get humanitarian assistance to Gaza civilians.</p><p> Biden is expected to spend part of Wednesday in Tel Aviv for talks with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and other officials as Israel prepares a ground offensive aimed at eliminating Hamas militants in Gaza who killed 1,300 people during a rampage through southern Israeli towns on Oct. 7.</p><p> Biden will then fly to Amman for talks about accelerating humanitarian assistance to Gaza.</p><p> In Amman, he will meet Jordan&#39;s King Abdullah, Egyptian President Abdel Fattah al-Sisi, and Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas, who has long been opposed to Hamas and whose organization exercises limited self-rule in the Israeli-occupied West Bank.</p><p> Biden&#39;s second trip to a war zone this year - he visited Ukraine in February - <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/potential-biden-trip-israel-rife-with-security-political-challenges-2023-10-16/">carries some risk</a> . His goal will be to show American solidarity with Netanyahu while trying to avoid a broader regional war involving Iran and its Lebanese ally Hezbollah and Syria.</p><p> The United States has stationed a carrier strike group in the eastern Mediterranean in a show of force for Israel and a second is on the way.</p><p> Biden also wants to avert a humanitarian calamity in Gaza where authorities say more than 2,800 people have already been killed in Israeli bombardment over the last week.</p><p> Hundreds of tons of aid from several countries have been waiting in Egypt&#39;s Sinai peninsula for days pending a deal for its safe delivery to Gaza and the evacuation of some foreign passport holders through the Rafah crossing.</p><p> &quot;He&#39;ll make it clear that we want to continue working with all our partners in the region, including Israel, to get humanitarian assistance in and provide some kind of safe passage for civilians to get out,&quot; said White House national security spokesperson John Kirby.</p><p> Biden and Netanyahu, thrown into a <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/israel-hamas-war-forces-biden-netanyahu-into-uneasy-partnership-2023-10-09/">wartime partnership</a> despite deep political differences on the way forward in the Middle East, have joined forces.</p><p> Biden has given Israel full-throated support while stressing the need to head off a massive humanitarian crisis in Gaza.</p><p> Their face-to-face meeting, after holding several phone calls since the Oct. 7 attacks by Hamas, will allow Biden to privately discuss concerns and possible red lines in the coming Gaza invasion.</p><p> Biden will also get an update on the scores of hostages taken by Hamas.</p><p> The State Department has said <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us-state-dept-aware-29-citizens-dead-15-missing-spokesperson-2023-10-14/">29 citizens</a> of the United States were killed in the Hamas attacks in Israel, with 15 citizens and one lawful permanent resident unaccounted for.</p><p> Israel has vowed to annihilate the Hamas movement.</p><p> Biden will make clear that &quot;Israel has the right and indeed the duty to defend its people from Hamas and other terrorists and to prevent future attacks,&quot; Secretary of State Antony Blinken told reporters after hours of talks with Israel&#39;s war cabinet in Tel Aviv.</p><p> He said Israel would brief Biden on its war aims and strategy and on how it will conduct operations &quot;in a way that minimizes civilian casualties and enables humanitarian assistance to flow to civilians in Gaza in a way that does not benefit Hamas.&quot;</p><p> The US and Israel agreed to develop a plan that will enable humanitarian aid from donor nations and multilateral organizations to reach civilians in Gaza, Blinken said.</p><span>史蒂夫·霍兰德报道； additional reporting by Humeyra Pamuk in Tel Aviv; Editing by Raju Gopalakrishnan</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:02:47 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> IZR6JDGXJ5OLNJXH3IELERODFM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/biden-heading-israel-jordan-focused-ground-offensive-humanitarian-crisis-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Steve Holland]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>PALESTINIANS/BIDEN (PIX, TV) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iran's Khamenei says Israeli officials should face trial for their crimes]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/QGSbrC2QWwJ-HbrcnpxbuY78Jt4=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/OLTV6RO5J5NGTGB4Y4XHV2LRWE.jpg" alt="伊朗最高领袖哈梅内伊出席在德黑兰举行的武装部队毕业典礼" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Iran&#39;s Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei speaks during a graduation ceremony for armed forces officers at the Imam Ali academy in Tehran, Iran October 10, 2023. Office of the Iranian Supreme Leader/WANA (West Asia News Agency) via REUTERS/file photo</figcaption></figure><p> Iran&#39;s Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei said Israeli officials should face trial for their &quot;crimes against Palestinians&quot;, state TV reported on Tuesday, a day before US President Joe Biden was due to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/diplomats-renew-calls-gaza-aid-iran-warns-israel-2023-10-16/">visit</a> Israel.</p><p> Since the 1979 Islamic Revolution, Iran&#39;s clerical rulers have been vocal in their support for the Palestinian cause. Tehran makes no secret of its backing for Hamas, funding and arming the Islamist group that controls Gaza.</p><p> &quot;No one can confront Muslims and the resistance forces if the Zionist regime&#39;s crimes against Palestinians continue ... the bombardment of Gaza must stop immediately,&quot; Khamenei said.</p><p> &quot;The Zionist regime&#39;s officials should be tried for their crimes against Palestinians in Gaza,&quot; he added.</p><p> Israel has vowed to annihilate Hamas after the group&#39;s gunmen killed 1,300 people, mainly civilians, during a rampage through southern Israeli towns on Oct. 7, the deadliest single day in Israel&#39;s 75-year history.</p><p> Israel has bombarded the Gaza Strip with air strikes that have killed more than 2,800 Palestinians, a quarter of them children, and driven around half of the 2.3 million Gazans from their homes. It has imposed a total blockade on the enclave, blocking food, fuel and medical supplies, which are rapidly running out.</p> <span>Writing by Parisa Hafezi, editing by Christina Fincher and Gareth Jones</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:00:26 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> ERIH2BPPABOG7BIB2OMMEUJ52U</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/irans-khamenei-says-israeli-officials-should-face-trial-their-crimes-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>PALESTINIANS/IRAN</category><category> OFFICIALS (UPDATE 1) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Belgium hunts shooter of Swedes as Brussels put on maximum alert]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/pfzTicjCPzW-k5jeXnpdOcizpHs=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/ZS45WG72VBJTVHDT3ZLGFAE25I.jpg" alt="布鲁塞尔枪击事件的后果" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> A man walks outside King Baudouin Stadium after the match between Belgium and Sweden was suspended following a shooting in Brussels, Belgium, October 17, 2023 REUTERS/Johanna Geron </figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/ZSgQH2P0sFrCX7Dlnj5ozs9J4sM=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/VJNPCVYYBBPALEUVBIINZVCGQY.jpg" alt="布鲁塞尔枪击事件的后果" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> People walk outside King Baudouin Stadium after the match between Belgium and Sweden was suspended following a shooting in Brussels, Belgium, October 17, 2023 REUTERS/Johanna Geron</figcaption></figure><p> Belgium was searching on Tuesday for a gunman who killed two Swedish citizens and wounded a third person on Monday in Brussels in what Prime Minister Alexander De Croo called a brutal terrorist attack.</p><p> The country has raised the security alert status of its capital city to the highest level, with increased police presence, particularly for Swedish people and institutions, and warned the public to be extra vigilant and avoid unnecessary travel.</p><p> &quot;Last night three people left for what was supposed to be a wonderful soccer party. Two of them lost their lives in a brutal terrorist attack,&quot; De Croo told a news conference.</p><p> &quot;The perpetrator targeted specifically Swedish supporters who were in Brussels to attend a Red Devils soccer match. Two Swedish compatriots passed away. A third person is recovering from severe injures,&quot; de Croo said.</p><p> Belgium was hosting Sweden in a Euro 2024 qualifying match on Monday evening. The match was abandoned at halftime.</p><p> A man, who identified himself as a member of the Islamic State, claimed responsibility in a video posted online.</p><p> Belgian Justice Minister Vincent Van Quickenborne told the news conference the suspect was a 45-year-old Tunisian man who sought asylum in Belgium in November 2019 and was known to police over people smuggling and illegal residence in Belgium.</p><p> Police are still searching for him.</p><p> Belgium has increased the presence of police in Brussels, especially around places linked to the Swedish community. Authorities say the perpetrator chose his victims because of their nationality.</p><p> A Belgian federal prosecutor said there was no evidence that the attacker had any link to the recent renewed conflict between Israel and Palestinian militants.</p><p> Sweden in August raised its terror alert to the second-highest level, warning of an increase in threats against Swedish interests abroad, after <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/sweden-is-considering-making-koran-burnings-illegal-aftonbladet-2023-07-06/">Koran burnings and other acts in Sweden</a> against Islam&#39;s holiest text outraged Muslims and triggered threats from jihadists.</p><p> The suspected assailant, calling himself Abdesalem Al Guilani, claimed in a video on social media that he was a fighter for Allah.</p><p> The shooting comes at a time of heightened security concerns in some European countries linked to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-hamas-war-latest-news-2023-10-15/">the Israel-Hamas conflict</a> . France is deploying 7,000 extra troops onto its streets after a teacher was fatally stabbed on Friday in an attack President Emmanuel Macron condemned as &quot;barbaric Islamic terrorism.&quot;</p><p> Video footage of the Brussels attack posted on the Het Laatste Nieuws newspaper website showed a man in an orange jacket on a scooter at a street intersection with a rifle first firing five shots, then following people fleeing into a building before firing again.</p><p> According to a media transcript of the video message recorded by the self-declared perpetrator, he said he had killed Swedes to take revenge in the name of Muslims.</p> <span>Reporting by Philip Blenkinsop and Marine Strauss in Brussels Additional reporting by Anna Ringstrom, Terje Solsvik, Richard Lough and John Cotton, Gabriela Baczynska, Stephanie Lecocq, Tassilo Hummel, Benoit van Overstraeten, Tommy Lund Writing by Jan Strupczewski and Silvia Aloisi Editing by Hugh Lawson, Matthew Lewis and Gerry Doyle</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 06:03:44 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> JB5EYYCK7VL63PQCRDIAPENGUY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/belgium-hunts-shooter-swedes-brussels-put-maximum-alert-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Philip Blenkinsop, Jan Strupczewski]]></author><category> BELGIUM</category><category> SECURITY/ (PIX, TV) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[First batch of U.S. citizens leaving Israel arrive in Cyprus by boat]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p> Dozens of US citizens from Israel arrived in Cyprus early Tuesday on the first evacuation boat organised by the United States amid the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/diplomats-renew-calls-gaza-aid-iran-warns-israel-2023-10-16/">escalating crisis</a> in the Middle East.</p><p> Some 159 people were on board the luxury liner Rhapsody of the Seas which left Haifa and sailed into Limassol port in Cyprus early Tuesday.</p><p> Cypriot government official Victor Papadopoulos told Cyprus state TV more evacuation vessels were expected to arrive over the next 12 hours.</p><p> Cyprus has been used as a transit hub for foreign governments to evacuate their civilians since just after the latest outbreak of <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-hamas-war-latest-news-2023-10-16/">violence</a> on Oct. 7.</p> <span>Reporting By Yiannis Kourtoglou; editing by Miral Fahmy</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 05:46:16 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> MJAKKVCHYBJW7MZ2YFCCNJNBUE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/first-batch-us-citizens-leaving-israel-arrive-cyprus-by-boat-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>PALESTINIANS/US</category><category> CYPRUS EVACUATIONS (PIX, TV) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Putin visits 'dear friend' Xi in show of no-limits partnership]]></title><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/kpAOomMqVgHkR216Qz-Ba14UCqY=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/BDUDTYDFVNLEPCZGDADGJMTBOY.jpg" alt="Chinese President Xi Jinping (R) stands next to Russian President Vladimir Putin as he arrives for a group photo during the BRICS Summit in Xiamen" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> 2017年9月4日，在中国东南部福建省厦门市的厦门国际会展中心，中国国家主席习近平（右）在金砖国家峰会期间与俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔·普京一起合影。 REUTERS/Wu红/泳池/档案照片</figcaption></figure><p>俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔·普京周二抵达北京，会见中国国家主席习近平，此次访问受到广泛关注，旨在展示中国与其大国之间的深厚互信和“无限”伙伴关系。</p><p>根据路透社的视频片段，普京及其随行人员于周二上午飞往北京首都国际机场，这是克里姆林宫领导人今年首次离开前苏联进行正式访问。</p><p>自从海牙国际刑事法院（ICC）三月份向普京发出<a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-opens-criminal-case-against-icc-judges-prosecutor-over-putin-arrest-2023-03-20/">逮捕令</a>，指控他非法驱逐乌克兰儿童以来，普京很少出国旅行。普京本月早些时候访问了前苏联加盟共和国<a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/russias-putin-visits-kyrgyzstan-first-foreign-trip-since-icc-arrest-warrant-2023-10-12/">吉尔吉斯斯坦</a>。</p><p>国际刑事法院的此举迫使该法院的 123 个成员国在普京踏上其领土后逮捕他并将其移交给海牙接受审判。吉尔吉斯斯坦和中国都不是为起诉战争罪而设立的国际刑事法院成员。</p><p>就在逮捕令发出几天后，习近平最后一次在莫斯科见到了他的“ <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/putin-welcome-xi-moscow-under-shadow-ukraine-war-2023-03-20/">亲爱的朋友</a>”。当时，习近平<a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/china/xi-invites-putin-china-third-belt-road-forum-xinhua-2023-03-21/">邀请</a>普京出席在北京举行的第三届“一带一路”高峰论坛，这是中国领导人倡导的国际合作论坛。普京将于周三会见习近平。</p><p>尽管乌克兰战争没有停止的迹象，但北京拒绝了西方对其与莫斯科伙伴关系的批评，坚称两国关系不违反国际准则，中国有权与其选择的任何国家合作。</p><p>普京上次访问中国是在 2022 年 2 月参加北京冬奥会，当时俄罗斯和中国宣布建立“无限制”伙伴关系，几天前俄罗斯总统向乌克兰派遣了数万名军队。</p><p>这将是普京第三次出席“一带一路”论坛，该论坛将持续到周三。他参加了2017年和2019年的前两届论坛。</p><span>瑞恩·吴 (Ryan Woo) 报道；克里斯托弗·库欣编辑</span>]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 01:30:19 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> K7PEOANQPVK3ZOF5CYMTXDPUTM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/putin-visits-dear-friend-xi-show-no-limits-partnership-2023-10-17/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>中国</category><category>RUSSIA/ (UPDATE 1, TV) </category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Diplomats renew calls for Gaza aid; Iran warns Israel]]></title><description><![CDATA[Summary:<ul><li> LATEST DEVELOPMENTS:</li><li> Iranian foreign minister promises preemptive actions</li><li> Hamas says it seeks freedom for prisoners held by Israel</li><li> Russia&#39;s Putin speaks to Israel&#39;s Netanyahu by phone </li></ul><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/oTPtVhYo-tyBByATAyx2jKUiNG8=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/MR2IINYNGVJDZM3FA3C2OXX644.jpg" alt="巴勒斯坦人在汗尤尼斯被以色列袭击摧毁的房屋废墟下搜寻伤亡人员" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Palestinians search for casualties under the rubble at a site of a house destroyed by Israeli strikes in Khan Younis in the southern Gaza Strip October 16, 2023. REUTERS/Mohammed Salem </figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/A5-EiiWhE46qG-yrUNtE3eSk-XY=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/77CL33FMTZIQRBJ5QSOZU2DEPQ.jpg" alt="U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken visits Tel Aviv" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> US Secretary of State Antony Blinken speaks with Israeli Defense Minister Yoav Gallant as they make brief statements to the media at The Kirya, Israel&#39;s Ministry of Defense, in Tel Aviv, Israel October 16, 2023. Jacquelyn Martin/Pool via REUTERS </figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/uE6hb-EmrZrQqon1auB06prZWyM=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/SDS43QFREZPKDIPDHYMT24I6YQ.jpg" alt="Palestinians wait to bake bread, as the conflict between Hamas and Israel continues" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Palestinians wait for bread baked on firewoods, amid fuel and power shortages, as the conflict between Hamas and Israel continues, in Khan Younis in the southern Gaza Strip, October 16, 2023. REUTERS/Mohammed Salem </figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/lVcyuyMSlSPLmljyowXy5zQEL5E=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/7N75I62JBJII7I2KFM47M2QQDA.jpg" alt="巴勒斯坦人在汗尤尼斯被以色列袭击摧毁的房屋废墟下搜寻伤亡人员" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> Palestinians search for casualties under the rubble at a site of a house destroyed by Israeli strikes in Khan Younis in the southern Gaza Strip October 16, 2023. REUTERS/Mohammed Salem </figcaption></figure><figure><img src="https://www.reuters.com/resizer/fEJ26qL2rppfgGgwjNFpMvWW68E=/1920x0/filters:quality(80)/cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/TJCSB5VOLBM37FANHUQR4JO3JE.jpg" alt="以色列袭击加沙的后果" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><figcaption> A view shows houses and buildings destroyed in Israeli strikes, in Jabalia in the northern Gaza Strip, October 11, 2023. REUTERS/Anas al-Shareef</figcaption></figure><p> Diplomats renewed calls for aid to the besieged Gaza Strip while Iran&#39;s foreign minister said Israel would not be allowed to act there without facing consequences, warning of &quot;preemptive action&quot; in the coming hours.</p><p> <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/potential-biden-trip-israel-rife-with-security-political-challenges-2023-10-16/">US President Joe Biden weighed a visit</a> to Israel laden with political and security risks, underscored on Monday when US Secretary of State Antony Blinken was <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/blinken-netanyahu-sheltered-bunker-amid-air-raid-sirens-tel-aviv-state-dept-2023-10-16/">forced to shelter in a bunker for five minutes</a> while meeting Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu when sirens went off in Tel Aviv.</p><p> Israel has vowed to annihilate the Hamas movement that rules Gaza, after fighters of the armed wing of the Iran-backed Palestinian Hamas movement burst across the barrier to Israel on Oct. 7, gunning down 1,300 Israelis, mainly civilians, in the deadliest day in Israel&#39;s 75-year-old history.</p><p> Israel has since put Gaza, home to 2.3 million Palestinians, under a total blockade and pounded it with unprecedented air strikes, and is widely expected to launch a ground assault.</p><p> Gaza authorities say more than 2,800 people have been killed there, around a quarter of them children, and more than 10,000 wounded are in hospitals desperately short of supplies.</p><p> Hamas said on Monday it had fired a &quot;barrage of missiles,&quot; toward Jerusalem and Tel Aviv.</p><p> Iranian Foreign Minister Hossein Amirabdollahian told state TV: &quot;Leaders of the Resistance will not allow the Zionist regime to take any action in Gaza. ... All options are open and we cannot be indifferent to the war crimes committed against the people of Gaza.&quot;</p><p> &quot;The resistance front is capable of waging a long-term war with the enemy (Israel)... in the coming hours, we can expect a preemptive action by the resistance front,&quot; he said, without elaborating.</p><p> Iran, which backs Hamas, refers to regional countries and forces opposed to Israel and the United States as a &quot;resistance front.&quot; Amirabdollahian said it was not limited to Hezbollah in Lebanon and added: &quot;This front was formed throughout the region to preserve the independence of nations and counter repeated aggressions by the Zionist regime over the past years.&quot;</p><p> Last week, Iran&#39;s top authority Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei said Tehran was not involved in the Hamas attack on Israel, but hailed what he called Israel&#39;s &quot;irreparable&quot; military and intelligence defeat.</p><p> Earlier on Monday, Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi said that while Tehran supported the Palestinian cause, the resistance front against Israel made its own independent decisions.</p><p> Diplomatic efforts have concentrated on getting aid into Gaza through <a href="https://www.reuters.com/graphics/ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/lbpgozkqopq/chart.png" target="_blank">the Rafah crossing with Egypt</a> , the sole route out that is not controlled by Israel. Cairo said the Rafah crossing was not officially closed but was <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/egypt-us-israel-agree-ceasefire-southern-gaza-opening-rafah-crossing-0600-gmt-2023-10-16/">inoperable due to Israeli strikes on the Gaza side.</a></p><p> Netanyahu invited Biden to Israel. Biden has been outspoken in his support for Israel, Washington&#39;s closest Middle East ally. The White House declined to comment on any planning for the trip. National Security Council spokesperson Adrienne Watson said in a statement that &quot;we have no new travel to announce.&quot;</p><p> Such a trip would be a rare and risky choice, showing American backing for Netanyahu as the US tries to avert a broader regional war involving Iran, its Lebanese ally Hezbollah, and Syria, and as food and fuel <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/gaza-hospitals-struggling-cope-with-air-strikes-blockade-2023-10-16/">run low in Gaza</a> .</p><p> It could, however, grant Biden fresh leverage to influence events on the ground and bolster his image at home.</p><p> Biden and Netanyahu, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/israel-hamas-war-forces-biden-netanyahu-into-uneasy-partnership-2023-10-09/">uncomfortable allies in the best of times,</a> have joined forces despite being at odds over the path forward in the Middle East with Biden frequently stressing support for independent Israeli and Palestinian states.</p><p> A meeting in person would allow Biden to privately discuss concerns and possible red lines in a looming Israeli ground invasion.</p><p> A top Hamas leader said on Monday the group &quot;has what it needs&quot; to free all Palestinians in Israel&#39;s jails, indicating <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/former-hamas-chief-meshaal-says-israeli-captives-include-high-ranking-officers-2023-10-16/">the militant group may try to use the Israelis it kidnapped</a> as bargaining chips to secure the release of Palestinian prisoners.</p><p> Soon after Hamas official Khaled Meshaal made the remarks on the captives, who include Israelis and non-Israelis kidnapped by Hamas on Oct. 7, the group&#39;s armed wing separately said the non-Israelis were &quot;guests&quot; who would be released &quot;when circumstances allow.&quot;</p><p> In the biggest sign yet that the war could spread to a new front, Israel ordered the evacuation on Monday of 28 villages in a two km- (1.2 mile-)deep zone near the Lebanese border.</p><p> Israel has said more than a million people in the northern half of Gaza must head to the southern half for their safety, even though Hamas has told them to stay put. While tens of thousands have fled south, the United Nations says there is no way to move so many people without causing a humanitarian catastrophe.</p><p> According to the United Nations, a million Gazans have already been driven from their homes. Power is out, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/graphics/ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/MAPS/movajdladpa/2023-10-16/water-is-running-out-in-gaza/" target="_blank">sanitary water is scarce,</a> and the last fuel for hospital emergency generators could be used up within a day.</p><p> Netanyahu said Israelis should prepare for a long battle.</p><p> &quot;Now we are focused on one target: to unite forces and charge forward to victory. This requires determination because victory will take time,&quot; he told the Israeli parliament.</p><p> &quot;And I have a message for Iran and Hezbollah, don&#39;t test us in the north. Don&#39;t make the same mistake you once made. Because today the price you will pay will be much heavier.&quot;</p><p> The Pentagon has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us-aircraft-carriers-what-they-bring-middle-east-2023-10-15/">deployed two aircraft carriers</a> - and their supporting ships - to the eastern Mediterranean since the attacks on Israel.这些舰艇的目的是起到威慑作用，确保冲突不会扩大，同时也为已经拥有大量美国军舰、飞机和军队的地区带来大量力量。</p><p> Russian President Vladimir Putin told Netanyahu on Monday that <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/putin-speaking-iran-israel-palestinians-syria-egypt-kremlin-2023-10-16/">Moscow wanted to help prevent a humanitarian disaster</a> in Gaza. The Kremlin readout of the call did not include any mention of the ceasefire Russia was trying to achieve by putting forward <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/un-vote-rival-resolutions-israel-gaza-2023-10-16/">a resolution in the United Nations Security Council</a> .</p><p> But Putin briefed Netanyahu on conversations with the leaders of Iran, Egypt, Syria and the Palestinian Authority in which the Kremlin said earlier that this had been discussed.</p><p> &quot;A unanimous opinion was expressed on the need for an early ceasefire and the establishment of a humanitarian truce in order to urgently provide assistance to all those in need,&quot; it said of those conversations.</p><p> With each day of air strikes, Gazans have been clawing at the rubble of flattened buildings with bare hands to rescue neighbours and recover the dead, with virtually no mechanical equipment to clear away the wreckage.</p><p> Those trying to reach the southern border crossing inside Gaza <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/gaza-people-resort-drinking-salty-water-garbage-piles-up-2023-10-16/">described the route as perilous</a> and under Israeli attack.</p><p> &quot;On our way to the crossing they shelled Rafah Street and we started screaming,&quot; said one resident near the crossing, Hadeel Abu Dahoud. &quot;Nowhere is safe in Gaza. Wherever we go there&#39;s shelling, shelling, crying, screaming, blood.&quot;</p> <span>Reporting by Nidal al-Mughrabi, Bassam Massoud and Nuha Sharaf in Gaza, Ari Rabinovitch, Dan Williams, Henriette Chacar, Dedi Hayun, Maayan Lubell, Emily Rose, James Mackenzie and John Davison in Jerusalem, Parisa Hafezi in Dubai, Humeyra Pamuk, Hatem Maher, Ahmed Tolba and Omar Abdel-Razek in Cairo, Trevor Hunnicutt, Nandita Bose, Rami Ayyub and Katharine Jackson in Washington, Michelle Nichols at the United Nations; Writing by David Brunnstrom; Editing by Howard Goller</span> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 22:00:03 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 4ATA6CN6FVPSFHIBEWJWAEYSJQ</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/diplomats-renew-calls-gaza-aid-iran-warns-israel-2023-10-16/<author><![CDATA[Nidal Al-Mughrabi, Dan Williams, Trevor Hunnicutt]]></author><category>以色列</category><category>PALESTINIANS/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS)</category></item></channel></rss>