<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<atom:link href="https://rsshub.rssforever.com/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2023 年 12 月 19 日星期二 06:15:24 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 5 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Diplomatic pressure builds over Hong Kong democrat Jimmy Lai's security trial]]></title><description><![CDATA[International pressure was building over a landmark national security trial in Hong Kong for leading China critic Jimmy Lai, with British authorities calling for consular access to the jailed democrat as his trial entered its second day on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 04:57:46 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> XR6MQUPIUNJNCTLOUAFEPENUM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/china/diplomatic-Pressure-builds-over-hong-kong-democrat-jimmy-lais-security-Trial-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[James Pomfret, Jessie Pang]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中国</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bangladesh train blaze kills four as opposition calls strike]]></title><description><![CDATA[Protesters set a train ablaze in Bangladesh on Tuesday, killing at least four people amid a countrywide strike called by the opposition to press its demand for the government to resign ahead of an election next month.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 04:49:51 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> LMAUA7MRLFJU5HC6BWPR2CXK6U</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bangladesh-train-blaze-kills-four-opposition-calls-strike-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mexican poultry farmers warn US-Mexico rail bridges closure will impact trade]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexican poultry farmers warned of consequences to international trade on Monday and called on their government to intervene after the U.S. closed two rail bridges in Texas to stem a surge in migration.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 04:01:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> RNX2REVLCNMKJDVTJL5BLPAIOI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexican-poultry-farmers-warn-us-mexico-rail-bridges-closure-will-impact-trade-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Setting aside tensions, Taiwan president offers aid to China after deadly quake]]></title><description><![CDATA[Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen expressed condolences to China on Tuesday and offered her government's help after an earthquake killed more than 100 people on the northern edge of the Qinghai-Tibetan plateau.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:55:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> RRN4WP4YXRMMRLLTLCGAWNKL5I</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/setting-aside-tensions-taiwan-president-offers-aid-china-after-deadly-quake-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Troops on South Korean side re-arm at border village amid tensions with North]]></title><description><![CDATA[International troops stationed on the South Korean side of the truce village of Panmunjom on the border with North Korea who had been unarmed can resume carrying guns, the United Nations Command (UNC) said on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:24:37 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> DZJOMZZODZNR3PDWDNZKECQJX4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/troops-south-korean-side-re-arm-border-village-amid-tensions-with-north-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Philippines president says diplomatic efforts with China heading "in poor direction"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Philippines President Ferdinand Marcos Jr. said a "paradigm shift" was needed in how his country approaches the South China Sea issue, as diplomatic efforts with Beijing were headed "in a poor direction".]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:00:23 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> SEO5YQJ7GRI2NMI5K2DGNDGNXM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/philippines-president-says-diplomatic-efforts-with-china-heading-poor-direction-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blinken, in call with Saudi counterpart, condemns Houthis for Red Sea attacks]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken held a call with Saudi Arabian Foreign Minister Prince Faisal bin Farhan on Monday in which he condemned attacks by Yemen's Houthi movement on commercial vessels in international waters in the Red Sea, the State Department said on Monday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 5L42QJZRKBJTJK2WM4RWUZFZEU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/blinken-call-with-saudi-counterpart-condemns-houthis-red-sea-attacks-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Kanishka Singh, Costas Pitas]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taiwan reports another suspected Chinese weather balloon crossing Taiwan Strait]]></title><description><![CDATA[A suspected Chinese weather balloon flew across the sensitive Taiwan Strait on Monday but stayed well north of Taiwan, the island's defence ministry said on Tuesday, the third time this month Taipei has reported them nearby.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:30:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> SUGQ532YDZJGLFHHHUT55YKHJA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-reports-another-suspected-chinese-weather-balloon-crossing-taiwan-strait-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tokyo prosecutors search offices of key ruling party factions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tokyo prosecutors on Tuesday searched the offices of two powerful political factions within the ruling Liberal Democratic Party (LDP), public broadcaster NHK reported, in connection with the biggest fundraising scandal to engulf the party in decades.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:15:26 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> U5DWJGIUBZKZ3KMAM44R3CALM4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tokyo-prosecutors-raid-offices-ruling-ldp-factions-over-funds-scandal-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Raided Gaza hospital not functioning, patients evacuated- WHO]]></title><description><![CDATA[A north Gaza hospital that Israeli troops raided is no longer functioning and patients including babies have been evacuated, putting the enclave's collapsing health services in further peril, a World Health Organization official said on Monday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:43:40 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3DFN6COWCNNYVBSYOV632ZYTO4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/raided-gaza-hospital-not-functioning-病人-evacuated-who-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[In Paris, UK's Cameron to call for stronger European coordination on Gaza]]></title><description><![CDATA[British foreign minister David Cameron will call for increased coordination between allies to address the "desperate" humanitarian situation in Gaza during a visit to Paris and Rome on Tuesday, his office said.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:07:00 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> KA2NLACCMRP4FM5646RFN4IYN4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/paris-uks-cameron-call-stronger-european-coordination-gaza-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US-led Red Sea patrol force to respond to attacks by Houthis]]></title><description><![CDATA[Several countries have agreed to jointly carry out patrols in the southern Red Sea and Gulf of Aden to try to safeguard commercial shipping against attacks by Yemen's Houthi rebels.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 23:52:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 6NF7X2O6IZIPNM64HF7XN7DDNI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/joint-patrols-guard-ships-response-attacks-by-houthis-backing-palestinians-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Bassam Masoud, Phil Stewart, James Mackenzie]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Australians assess flood damages from cyclone as rescue efforts ramp up]]></title><description><![CDATA[Residents in Australia's northeast on Tuesday took stock of flood damages from former Tropical Cyclone Jasper and authorities accelerated efforts to rescue people stranded in remote towns as rivers stayed above dangerous levels.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:51:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> X66NO234LVO75H44RGWW6IRQDE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australians-assess-flood-damages-cyclone-rescue-efforts-ramp-up-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Renju Jose]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[North Korea says Hwasong-18 ICBM test was response to US hostility]]></title><description><![CDATA[North Korea said on Tuesday it had tested the isolated state's newest ICBM on Monday to gauge the war readiness of its nuclear force against mounting U.S. hostility, as Washington and its allies began operating a real-time missile data sharing system.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:51:13 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> KB266J5RLJNZZF6MN5K7E3E6ZE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/north-korea-says-it-conducted-hwasong-18-icbm-monday-yonhap-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Jack Kim]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iceland volcano erupts near town after weeks of quake activity]]></title><description><![CDATA[A volcano erupted late on Monday in southwest Iceland, spewing lava and smoke across a wide area after weeks of intense earthquake activity, the country's Meteorological Office said, threatening a nearby town.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:48:16 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> ZMXKCQ5AGFNSTEOYCV62ZIVMPE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/iceland-volcano-erupts-after-weeks-quake-activity-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Terje Solsvik]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas to arrest migrants crossing border illegally under new state law]]></title><description><![CDATA[Texas Governor Greg Abbott on Monday signed a law allowing state law enforcement to arrest people suspected of crossing the U.S.-Mexico border illegally, giving local officers powers long delegated to the U.S. government in a move likely to trigger legal challenges.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:44:48 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> UGU6LEOFWVN3FNS7KPVZO2XUTY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us/texas-arrest-migrants-crossing-border-illegally-under-new-state-law-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Ted Hesson]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美国</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel shipping costs rising as lines pull out and Red Sea attacks worsen]]></title><description><![CDATA[The cost of shipping goods to Israel by sea has risen in recent days as some container lines pull out while others impose new surcharges, adding to the country's supply chain pressures amid its war in Gaza, shipping sources said.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:52:21 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> TNBF5OO5XFPA5N4XNLWLWVFFLY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-shipping-costs-rising-lines-pull-out-red-sea-attacks-worsen-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Jonathan Saul]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magnitude-6.2 quake kills 118 in northwestern China's Gansu, Qinghai provinces]]></title><description><![CDATA[A magnitude-6.2 earthquake jolted a remote and mountainous county on the northern edge of the Qinghai-Tibetan plateau just before midnight on Monday, killing at least 118 people and injuring hundreds, according to Chinese state media.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:15:04 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> KRMKMBYCSRM2RFHPPGYYAFHFGQ</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/china/magnitude-61-earthquake-strikes-qinghai-china-emsc-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Liz Lee, Qiaoyi Li]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中国</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Egypt's Sisi sweeps to third term as president with 89.6% of vote]]></title><description><![CDATA[Abdel Fattah al-Sisi swept on Monday to a third term as Egypt's president in an election where he faced no serious challengers, calling the vote a rejection of the "inhumane war" in neighbouring Gaza.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:27:56 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> RORIJMQAIVM5XIOIPWUPTDGXAE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/results-due-egypt-election-with-sisi-expected-sweep-third-term-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Farah Saafan, Aidan Lewis]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump would install loyalists to reshape US foreign policy on China, NATO and Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[Donald Trump in a second term would likely install loyalists in key positions in the Pentagon, State Department and CIA whose primary allegiance would be to him, allowing him more freedom to enact isolationist policies and whims.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:05:21 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> LS24WETJS5LWTHS2HGWLTQOXEU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-install-loyalists-reshape-us-foreign-policy-diplomats-gird-doomsday-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Gram Slattery, Simon Lewis, Idrees Ali, Phil Stewart]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美国</category></item></channel></rss>