<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>大局观</title><atom:link href="https://ritholtz.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://ritholtz.com<description>资本市场、经济、地缘政治、技术和数字媒体的宏观视角</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 6 月 14 日星期三 10:59:11 +0000</lastbuilddate><language>英文</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1个</sy:updatefrequency><generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.3</generator><item><title>周三上午 10 点阅读</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-wednesday-am-reads-334/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:30:26 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314453 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>我从休假的早晨回来的周中读到： • 通货膨胀被过度炒作，这位专业人士说。 “我听到很多人说我们永远不会解决这个问题，7% 是新常态。这太夸张了。有多种因素导致通胀上升，但几乎所有因素都在得到纠正。大量与Covid相关的……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-wednesday-am-reads-334/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-wednesday-am-reads-334/">10 Wednesday AM Reads 的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>我从假期早上回来的周中读到：</p><blockquote><p> •<strong>这位专业人士表示，通胀被过度炒作</strong>。 “我听到很多人说我们永远不会解决这个问题，7% 是新常态。这太夸张了。有多种因素导致通胀上升，但几乎所有因素都在得到纠正。事后看来，与 Covid 相关的大规模刺激措施可能太多了。但是这笔钱已经花掉了。所以我们基本上已经过去了。供应链问题已在很大程度上得到纠正。运费已经回落。美联储将利率维持在零的时间太长了。这显然已得到纠正。通胀率将回到 2% 至 3% 的范围内。” （ <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/inflation-automated-driving-ai-investing-6a8502f4" target="_blank" rel="noopener">巴伦周刊</a>）</p><p> •<strong>政府数字不是假的。他们只是吵闹</strong>：其中大卫·萨克斯和巴拉吉对就业数字发出了虚惊。 ( <a href="https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/in-which-david-sacks-and-balaji-raise" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Noahpinion</a> )<em>另请参阅</em><strong>改变您的观点</strong>：月度非农就业数据可能是美国被高估得最多的单一经济数据点，而中期就业趋势被低估得最多。 （当你有 14 个连续的上升惊喜时，也许你的模型有些不对劲……）（<a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/change-your-perspective/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">大图</a>）</p><p> •<strong>杰罗姆鲍威尔的大问题变得更加复杂</strong>：美联储的目标是避免金融不稳定，同时还要对抗通货膨胀——经常需要相反​​政策的困境。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/fed-jerome-powell-big-problem-more-complicated-ba27ece4" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>投资者再次向日本投入大笔资金。这就是为什么</strong>。日本股市今年上涨近 30%，远远领先于标准普尔 500 指数，因为公司押注公司运营方式的变化可能最终会持续下去。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/06/14/business/japan-stock-markets.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>这些百万富翁想向富人征税，他们正在游说工薪阶层选民</strong>：十多年来，非营利组织爱国百万富翁一直在游说国会做出改变。它的成员将不平等视为一种危险——他们担心大笔资金正在腐蚀政治并引发内乱。但他们并没有取得太大的成功。唐纳德·特朗普总统 2017 年的减税政策在很大程度上让富人受益，即使民主党在 2021 年控制了参议院，他们也未能通过提高最低工资的法案。 （ <a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/06/13/1180389740/tax-rich-raise-wages-patriotic-millionaires-lobby-voters-inequality" target="_blank" rel="noopener">美国国家公共电台</a>）</p><p> •<strong>科技行业正在萎缩。然后是 ChatGPT</strong> 。去年，硅谷淹没在裁员和悲观的预测中。人工智能驱散阴霾（ <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/06/04/ai-bubble-tech-industry-outlook/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华盛顿邮报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>富裕国家表示他们正在花费数十亿美元来应对气候变化。有些钱去了陌生的地方</strong>。富裕国家已承诺每年投入 1000 亿美元帮助减少全球变暖的影响。但路透社发现，大量资金流向了包括燃煤电厂、酒店和巧克力店在内的项目。 （ <a href="https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/climate-change-finance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">路透社</a>）</p><p> •<strong>伊利诺伊州成为第一个“禁止”图书禁令的州</strong>：一项新法律允许该州从移除图书或不遵守美国图书馆协会指南的图书馆中扣留资金。 （ <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-12/illinois-responds-to-surge-in-book-censorship-with-ban-on-book-bans" target="_blank" rel="noopener">城市实验室</a>）</p><p> •<strong>特朗普在海湖庄园案中没有找到新的出庭律师</strong>：预计特朗普将由现有律师托德布兰奇和克里斯基斯代理。 （ <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/jun/13/trump-finds-no-new-lawyers-mar-a-lago-documents-arraignment" target="_blank" rel="noopener">卫报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>丹佛掘金队经久不衰</strong>：并非每支球队都能幸运地选到比赛中最好的球员，但任何球队都可以耐心等待——掘金队漫长而稳健的征程将他们一路带到了 NBA标题。 （ <a href="https://www.theringer.com/nba/2023/6/13/23759661/2023-nba-champions-denver-nuggets-patience-nikola-jokic-jamal-murray-michael-malone" target="_blank" rel="noopener">铃声</a>）</p></blockquote><p>请务必查看本周末我们对 Mathieu Chabran <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">的商业硕士</a><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" data-web-url="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2">采访</a>，Tikehau Capital 是一家拥有 40B 美元资产的全球另类资产管理公司。该公司总部位于巴黎，在 13 个国家设有办事处，但主要在纽约、伦敦和新加坡设有金融中心。他于 2004 年与德意志银行的同事 Antoine Flamarion 共同创立了 Tikehau，并负责美国分部。 Chabran 于 2022 年 1 月根据法兰西共和国总统的命令被授予法国<strong><em>荣誉军团骑士勋章</em></strong>。</p><p></p><p><strong>市场对美联储：暂停！</strong></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/yoy-CPI.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-314732" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/yoy-CPI.png" alt="" width="600" height="476" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/yoy-CPI.png 1344w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/yoy-CPI-300x238.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/yoy-CPI-1024x812.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/yoy-CPI-768x609.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/yoy-CPI-250x198.png 250w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a></p><p><em>资料来源</em>：富国银行，来自<a href="https://www.ft.com/content/78db971f-7233-4c24-9e2d-9f4fbdeeee5a" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FT</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此处注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p></p><p> <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-wednesday-am-reads-334/">10 Wednesday AM Reads 的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title>成绩单：Mathieu Chabran</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-mathieu-chabran/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Alternatives/PE/Hedge Funds]]></category><category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314666 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>本周的成绩单，MiB：Tikehau Capital 的 Mathieu Chabran，如下所示。您可以在 iTunes、Spotify、Stitcher、Google、YouTube 和 Bloomberg 上流式传输和下载我们的完整对话，包括任何播客附加内容。您可以在此处找到我们在您最喜欢的播客主机上发布的所有早期播客。 ~~~ 播音员：这是商业硕士……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-mathieu-chabran/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-mathieu-chabran/">后记：Mathieu Chabran</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; fullscreen *; clipboard-write" frameborder="0" height="175" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;border-radius:10px;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/mathieu-chabran-on-using-creativity-to-compete/id730188152?i=1000616332516"></iframe></p><p></p><p></p><p>本周<a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/mib-mathieu-chabran/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>MiB 的成绩单：Tikehau Capital 的 Mathieu Chabran</em></a> ，如下所示。</p><p>您可以在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">iTunes</a> 、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5LGxKlY6fzXS3tGsjB23Cb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> 、 <a href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> 、 <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvZTczYzk5OGUtNmU2MC00MzJmLTg2MTAtYWUyMTAxNDBjNWIxLzRlNGNkOTEwLTQwYTEtNDYxOS1hNWYzLWFlMmIwMDEyZmZmZi81ODczYTNjYi0yOThmLTQwYmMtYjcxZi1hZTJiMDAxMzAwMGQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> 、 <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLe4PRejZgr0PzN7r8NikAnOqP70DHhoJ0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a>和<a href="http://www.bloomberg.com/podcasts/masters-in-business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg 上流</a>式传输和下载我们的完整对话，包括任何播客附加内容。您可以<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">在此处找到</a>我们在您最喜爱的播客主机上发布的所有早期播客。</p><p style="text-align: center;"> ~~~</p><p>播音员：这里是彭博电台 Barry Ritholtz 的商业硕士课程。</p><p> BARRY RITHOLTZ，主持人，商业大师：本周在播客上，我有一位额外的特邀嘉宾。 Mathieu Chabran 是总部位于巴黎的另类资产管理公司 TIKEHAU Capital 的联合创始人。他们管理着价值超过 400 亿美元的资产。</p><p>我发现这真的是一次关于从不同角度接近投资世界的精彩对话。富有创造力，跳出框框思考，不仅要模仿别人的做法，还要通过以不同的方式思考世界来创造新的机会。</p><p>谈话内容丰富，引人入胜。我觉得这很棒，我想你也会，不用多说，我与 TIKEHAU Capital 的 Mathieu Chabran 的谈话。</p><p> TIKEHAU CAPITAL 联合创始人 MATHIEU CHABRAN：谢谢你，Barry。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我忘了说，您已于 2022 年 1 月获得法兰西共和国总统颁发的法国荣誉军团骑士勋章。我们将在其他时间回过头来讨论。我不知道这与资产管理有多大关系，但让我们谈谈你在受到法国总统称赞之前所做的事情。</p><p>你在巴黎上学，但你在伦敦的美林和德意志银行开始了你的职业生涯。告诉我们一些关于那个背景的信息。</p><p> CHABRAN：是的，不，巴里，没错。你知道，这在欧洲是一回事，我实际上认为，伦敦仍然是你加入金融服务业时想要接触的地方。所以我很幸运能够在 90 年代后期在美林公司获得这个暑期实习机会。我遇到了安托万，实际上是我的共同创始合伙人。所以那是有一段时间了，但尽管如此，我不知道是不是一见钟情，但我们相处得很好，在投资银行工作了几年后，他加入了高盛。实际上，我加入了德意志银行。我们决定自己尝试一下。我们分别是 28 岁和 30 岁。</p><p>回顾过去，投资银行业务，即使银行已经不复存在，也是一次很棒的培训。我认为这是一次很棒的培训。我想我们学到了很多东西。你在投资银行业的风险敞口，我的背景是杠杆金融银行家。 90 年代后期，欧洲高收益市场的出现，你会以前所未有的方式印制交易。你得到了这种曝光，你是一个年轻的分析师，助理，你可以和管理团队一起参加路演。我回头看，就我们所获得的曝光度而言，这是一次地狱般的训练。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：是的，我可以想象。你在巴黎上学时的计划是一直进入金融领域，还是你最初倾向于另一个方向？</p><p> CHABRAN：在加入巴黎的一所商学院之前，我在我的家乡普罗旺斯艾克斯学习政治学。当时没有迹象表明我会进入金融领域。</p><p>因此，当我接触到优秀的老师并开始学习时，顺便说一下，什么，又一次，回到 90 年代后期，但后来你开始读书，我不是在谈论理论书籍，但是一些经验，人们，我记得这些书，读过迈克尔刘易斯的“说谎者的扑克牌”，读过关于米尔肯和垃圾债券的“掠夺者的舞会”，这就是兴奋的开始。你就像，我必须接触到这一点。</p><p>所以不，没有写任何东西，但这是重要的一步。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：快进到今天。你现在在美国的一家大型欧洲公司工作，但实际上你的职业生涯是在伦敦的大型美国公司开始的。</p><p>查布兰：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：美国公司在欧洲与欧洲公司在美国的文化差异是什么？</p><p> CHABRAN：是的，这是一个有趣的问题。从美国的角度来看，巴里，有时，欧洲可能是一个简单的概念，但它是一个非常复杂的现实。所以在欧洲做生意显然是本地化，因为意大利不是西班牙，法国不是德国。有时，伦敦人认为他们涵盖了整个欧洲运动场，但这又是一个复杂的现实。</p><p>因此，当时遇到了为这些美国银行工作的美国人，现在他们明白了。那些成功的人，甚至是我们的一些同行、竞争对手、朋友、正在竞争和攻占欧洲市场的美国特许经营商，通常那些成功或非常成功的人是那些在实地花了很多时间的人.</p><p>然后相反，希望，在为美国特许经营工作，与人和伟大的导师共度时光，你知道，对我来说，我现在希望能更好地理解我们在这里扩张时的文化差异。我相信您会欣赏的，在纽约与美洲其他地方的现实情况截然不同，部分原因在于拜访美国中西部地区的新客户。</p><p>所以希望这里有一点融合，让它变得有价值。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我喜欢 Spalding Gray 的那句老话，“我不住在美国，我住在美国东海岸的一个小岛上。”因为就您而言，纽约不是堪萨斯城，堪萨斯城也不是迈阿密。但纽约绝对是它自己的生物。</p><p> CHABRAN：这是肯定的。你知道，对于我们 TIKEHAU 来说，这是在北美开设和扩张的重要一步。只是背景，巴里，当我五年前的今年 2018 年搬到这里时，我们在北美几乎没有任何关系。我们从客户的角度，从 LP 的角度进行了一些投资和关系。快进，今天接近我们在这里筹集的 AUM 的 10%。我们推出了新举措，我们试图与众不同。显然，这是一场长期的游戏，在美国开展业务时，你必须长期贪婪。</p><p>但在我们今天所从事的业务中，另类资产管理领域尽管具有竞争力，但现在的结构性机会使得你必须在这里做出的欧洲承诺必须是长期的。我亲自做出了承诺，我看到了路径，因为有扩展业务的空间。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：让我们来谈谈是什么导致了 2004 年决定推出 TIKEHAU Capital。你在德意志银行，你的同事 Antoine 在高盛。是什么让你说，“嘿，让我们把乐队重新组合起来吧？”</p><p> CHABRAN：嗯，你知道吗，这实际上又回到了我刚才所说的。我们看到了所有这些特许经营权的推出，显然在它们的顶端以及你能想到的所有今天引领行业的人，但当时他们管理着数百亿美元，这在当时是巨大的，但这只是今天的一小部分。</p><p>我们看到所有这些美国特许经营权在伦敦以外的欧洲推出，我们就像，“我们为什么不试一试呢？”我们学习了杠杆融资，我们学习了房地产债务，我们知道高收益，我们知道机会主义投资，我们就像，永远不会太晚，永远不会太早，我们决定使用我们收集的 400 万美元的巨额资产管理规模来自朋友和家人。</p><p>里索尔兹：对。</p><p> CHABRAN：所以你可以理解当时的挑战，但你必须从某个地方开始。</p><p>里索尔兹：对。那是在现金周围走来走去。</p><p>所以让我们谈谈不要太晚，也不要太早，你在互联网泡沫破灭后立即推出。</p><p>查布兰：正确。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：但是在金融危机爆发前几年……</p><p>查布兰：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：那个时期是什么样的，那两次巨大波动事件之间的平静是什么样的？</p><p> CHABRAN：这是一次经历，因为互联网泡沫，我记得我是美林的一名年轻合伙人，所有的投资银行，他们必须重塑自己，以确保他们能够记住我们最近听到的留住人才再次。</p><p>所以他们创造了一些很酷的工作空间，你将不再打领带之类的，这都是一种物质形式，就好像有一种转变。然后，从我们推出全球金融危机时的第四年开始，我们在 TIKEHAU 开展业务已经三年，四年了。我记得我们感到无比自豪，因为当时我们与贝尔斯登银行合作，我们与雷曼兄弟合作，这是创业发展的一个步骤。然后突然之间，在周末，那些银行都不见了。</p><p>所以你就像一个年轻的企业家，离开了这种濒临死亡的经历，尽管你认为你已经接近确定，因为你正在与你能想到的最好的机构和对手合作。然后突然间，一切都取决于你如何看待和看待这个世界，永远不要把任何事情视为理所当然，永远处于挑战一切的世界中。</p><p>所以它对你每天早上的胃痛都没有好处，但只有偏执狂才能生存。我认为那是一次很棒的学习经历。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：让我们从商业角度谈谈贝尔斯登和雷曼之后发生的事情。贝尔斯登被摩根大通吸收。因此，您在贝尔斯登的联系人仍在营业。</p><p>雷曼兄弟最好的部分被巴克莱吸收了。所以我不得不想象很多在那些地方与你做生意的人都站起来了，你仍然有一些关系，或者我对此过于乐观了吗？</p><p> CHABRAN：不，不，以上都是。但更重要的是，正如我所说，在我们的发展过程中，永远不要想当然。因为雷曼兄弟是一家在周五晚上获得单一 A 级评级的银行，而它在周一早上违约了，即使我在草拟一点，从那时起，我们有 8 亿AUM，我猜。顺便说一句，我们有一个 20、25 人的团队，其中大多数人今天仍然和我们在一起。如果你允许的话，当你们一起工作时感觉很棒，因为那时你只需要看着某人的眼睛，你就会确切地知道他们将如何表现，因为我们一起经历过。</p><p>因此，对我们来说，超越人民和机构，这是旅程第二阶段的开始。我想说的是，所有这些事情是多么容易，也许不那么天真，因为它们并不容易。史蒂夫苏世民写了他的书。它被称为“需要什么”。所以对我们来说，一切都是平等的，这是旅程第二阶段的开始，不再是取笑的部分。</p><p>你有效地进入了真实的东西。</p><p>现在，积极的一面是，整个情况开始为替代市场带来很多光明。私人债务、私人信贷在欧洲闻所未闻，直到银行有效地陷入大规模的流动性紧缩，所有这些资产管理公司不得不介入并填补这一空白。对我们来说是一个很好的机会。当时的私募股权只是关于收购和杠杆收购。很少有人听说过需要加强创业公司资产负债表的增长股权部分，因为它不是，好吧，她并没有试图出售业务，这只是确保你找到合适的合作伙伴来加强资产负债表。等等等等。</p><p>我们开始了一个新的时期，在此之上加入了非常宽松的货币政策，这是私人市场新篇章的开始。我们很幸运能够在这个时候有效地踏上这段旅程。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：让我跟进金融危机之后的时期。显然，它具有很强的破坏性，造成了很多损失，很多人失去了工作，很多企业倒闭了，但听起来似乎在随后的事情中创造了很多机会。</p><p> CHABRAN：对我们来说确实如此。同样，挑战很多，但通过艰苦的工作和能够看到机会的人，并且可能采用欧洲的方法认为，是的，您可以在欧洲发展一个非常多本地足迹的组织，成为全球投资者的替代方案，以我必须承认，对于老牌客户来说，主要是美国人。那是非常令人兴奋的。进入那个领域非常令人兴奋。在某种程度上，我们一直期待着能够面对另一场危机的那一天。</p><p>我们都知道他们都是不同的，但准备得更好。有了更多的资源，有了更强大的平台，有了更大的足迹，有了更好的准备，把 COVID 放在一边，把 Brexit 放在一边，在过去 10 年、12 年里把所有这些小步骤都放在一边，我们一直在为什么时候做好更好的准备周期变化。</p><p>我们可能已经进入这个新周期的新篇章，提高利率，从一年前开始，我们认为它不会很快降低。因此，我们回到我们工作的基础，风险承保、风险评估、资产价格与资产估值不同。</p><p>我的意思是估值是以无风险利率贴现的未来现金流加上风险溢价。你猜怎么着？现在的无风险利率为 5% 不再为零，风险溢价比之前的 2% 更接近 5%。</p><p>所以突然之间，我们工作的全部优点又回到了球场的中心，这让我们的工作更加令人兴奋。</p><p>过去 12 个月以来，我们对今天的投资感到无比兴奋。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：让我们谈谈是什么将 TIKEHAU 带到了美国。显然你们在欧洲非常成功。您现在在全球拥有 13 个办事处。仅仅是美国市场的规模吗？这里的吸引力是什么？</p><p> CHABRAN：嗯，我的意思是，规模绝对是一个原因。但我要补充一点，我们当时刚刚上市，2017 年。对我们来说，上市可能远在近年来变得更加普遍之前，上市障碍的主要目标实际上是推广品牌，专营权。在 60 年代之际，我们从未出售过一股股票。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：你们只允许一小部分公开，对吧？</p><p> CHABRAN：是的，没错。我们所有的历史支持者、股东，他们实际上一直在支持我们的业务。我们两次进入 ECM 市场，他们都加强了他们的所有权。因此，与许多 IPO 不同，IPO 是一种通过业务获利的方式，对我们来说，这实际上是关于使平台合理化。正如你所提到的，我们刚刚经历了 13、14 年的创业发展，这段时间非常坎坷。因此，这是一种使平台合理化的好方法，一个品牌，一个名字，让这个名字在那里。</p><p>那是在 2017 年，我们在巴黎泛欧交易所上市。来到美国，除了在某个时候来到美国别无选择。我们认为时机是正确的，因为我们现在和那时都有 200 亿资产管理规模。我们已经在亚洲工作了几年，而且前途无量。所以我决定来这里推广这个品牌，转化为商业关系，为美国投资者筹集更多资金，就你而言，美国是世界上最深的市场之一。</p><p>然后也开始在美国这里部署资本。</p><p>并不是说绝对没有资金短缺，而是正如我们喜欢在 TIKEHAU 所说的那样，创造而不是竞争。所以我们开始了像二级私人信贷这样的倡议。私人债务是这里的主流发展战略，我指的是全球和美国。我认为我们是最早进入二级私人信贷的公司之一。</p><p>快进几年，三年，现在我们可以展示战略的优点，战略的记录。我们开始扩展到中端市场基础设施。那是在拜登大选之前，当我们在欧洲的基础设施领域并不活跃时，所有的注意力都集中在基础设施上。</p><p>因此，我们试图找到一些可以让我们与众不同的游戏，不仅是相对于欧洲和亚洲投资者，而且是在美国，能够向 LP 讲述一个不同的故事，其中一个关键的差异化因素是皮肤我们作为组织的结构和创始人所拥有的游戏。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：所以很多上市的公司都拥有可用于收购的有价值的货币。这对思考有何影响？</p><p> CHABRAN：是的，没错，自上市以来我们非常有选择地使用了几次。 Infra 是其中之一，另一个是欧洲的房地产。我的意思是，他们是非常有选择性的补强收购。在我们的业务中进行收购总是一个大赌注，对吗？我们从事人事业务，你需要化学反应，我的意思是，你需要文化来解决问题。</p><p>但展望未来，可以肯定的是，与几年前相比，我们今天在反收购方面处于更有利的地位。因此，随着市场和行业的重组，我们肯定会非常机会主义。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这很有趣，Bolt On 的想法与在同一空间内的想法不同。由于化学反应，由于文化问题，金融收购的历史由来已久，但效果并不理想。</p><p>查布兰：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：但是你之前说的话真的让我印象深刻。你想创造，而不是竞争。那么，让我们来谈谈你们在 TIKEHAU 的人如何以不同的方式思考，告诉我们，或者用史蒂夫·乔布斯的话说，思考不同，告诉我们你们如何以不同于许多竞争对手的方式对待世界。</p><p>查布兰：是的。你知道当我们开始的时候，正如我告诉过你的那样，非常谦虚，即使你与私人投资者、高净值人士、家族办公室交谈，也有很多特许经营权，他们在接近他们的方式上可以更灵活一点资产配置，他们需要找到一个理由，为什么他们会选择当时的 TIKE-who，而不是 TIKEHAU。</p><p>里索尔兹：（笑声）</p><p> CHABRAN：并找到他们会在那里分配的原因。</p><p>回到欧洲，回到过去，当我们开始进行私人信贷、直接贷款时，今天是非常主流的。我可以告诉你，那时候不是。当时，他们甚至在欧洲称之为影子银行。</p><p>里索尔兹：是的。</p><p> CHABRAN：自从我上次阅读影子银行以来已经有一段时间了，因为它在今天变得如此主流和结构化，以至于它确实是一年中的一部分。</p><p>所以我们一直试图有效地成为一点点，我不知道它是怎么出现的，它不是失败者，而是带来一些不同的东西，这样你就可以 -</p><p> RITHOLTZ：清白？</p><p> CHABRAN：是的，这样你就可以为自己出名，然后利用这些相邻的业务来扩大规模，使它们成为主流。我是说我们几年前在纽约推出的二级私人信贷现在正变得更加主流。</p><p>每天我都会看到其中一家大型膨胀支架银行启动或谈论该计划。我们就像，好吧，也许那是我们的好主意。顺便说一句，竞争是好的。竞争没有错，但至少你已经为自己树立了名声。很明显，你有记录，你可以展示它。</p><p>这是第一步。</p><p>第二件事，巴里，如果可以的话，在我们的行业中，最大的不同应该是经理们在他们的业务中投入的游戏皮肤。</p><p>我想说的是，在我们这个行业，你会遇到很多愿意用别人的钱赚钱的人。你会遇到越来越少的人愿意用他们孩子的钱来赚钱。任何企业家都在通过借入一些资金并投资于他的业务来承担风险，无论业务是什么。</p><p>在我们的行业中，有时我认为我们在游戏中展示皮肤的方式有点讽刺，更不用说虚伪了。我不认为附带利益是一种很好的利益一致性。唯一的利益一致是任何给定的经理或公司投入其基金的资本金额。</p><p>当你读到的时候，好吧，好吧，我们把基金的 1% 作为 GP 的承诺，那是十亿，你知道，我们投入了 1000 万，这是很多钱，是的，但你收取 2%未来10年，所以期权成本不会那么高。</p><p>当您将 10%、20% 的资产负债表资本与您的 LP 并排放置时，您可以做一个基本的 Excel 电子表格，您会看到，您知道，什么是利害攸关的，而且那有效地，是的，您将通过管理费和附带权益的业绩费赚一些钱，但你知道，你与客户并肩面临的风险是完全不同的。</p><p>我认为这是该行业应该走向的方向。而我们的许多同行、竞争对手，他们都有不同的模式。但顺便说一句，巴里，来自 GP、合作伙伴、资产负债表和上市的那个在游戏中有重要皮肤的人是我们加强这个股权基础的好方法，这是合作伙伴自己的和控制和管理自己，有效地创造了迄今为止，在欧洲绝对首屈一指的皮肤游戏模式。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我喜欢这听起来的方式。让我们谈谈欧洲。</p><p>如果我们回顾过去几十年，欧洲在 2000 年代的表现优于美国，当时我们正在经历互联网泡沫和金融危机。在 2010 年代，美国市场刚刚火起来，而且表现非常好。 2020 年代的事情开始有点不稳定。您如何比较过去几十年欧洲与美国的投资环境？</p><p> CHABRAN：很明显，它们都是由利率驱动的，它们使你知道方向相同，但模式不同，当我们几年前在欧元危机的背景下首次在欧洲实行负利率时，你知道这是全球金融危机首先是主权国家，但后来你知道，在 IG 市场和投资大市场的权利下，企业基本上借了 100 美元，并被要求偿还 98 美元。</p><p>今天当你回头看，没有回头交易，你会想，好吧，我们当时在想什么？因为对于我们所做的事情，我的意思是，你知道业务，巴里，就像风险承保一样，是关于有效地扩大风险和回报。我们处在一个非常尴尬的环境中。</p><p>这就是为什么我很惊讶看到这么多人感到惊讶。你知道，一年前，也就是 5 月 22 日，利率开始上升，突然间整个软件都被窃听了。</p><p>我的意思是，我们所做的不是火箭科学。这一切都归结为流动性价值和信贷成本。然后我们可以开始，你知道，做我们应该做的事情，你知道，风险承保。因此，欧洲、美国在下降的过程中进入了不同的模式，在上升的过程中则截然不同。</p><p>我的意思是，在美国这里，很明显，你们在加息方面更加积极，在我看来这是正确的。也许欧洲当时有点落后。他们实际上更快地降低利率，甚至降到负利率。</p><p>但是现在正在发生一些脱钩。对我们来说，这是一个很好的方式，特别是在 TIKEHAU，我们非常容易接触到收益游戏、信贷、基础设施、房地产、定制信贷。因此，所有这些都是风险承保的起点。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：那么让我们谈谈 2010 年代和 2020 年代之间的区别，首先，嘿，很有争议的是，当美联储开始在美国加息时，他们已经落后于曲线。他们 2% 的目标已在一年前达到，CPI 继续走高。</p><p>因此，如果美联储落后于曲线，那么欧洲中央银行在处理通胀问题方面落后了多少？</p><p> CHABRAN：美国和欧洲的中央银行可能有不同的授权。一个可能比其他的更具政治性，有时当你必须有效地为所有赤字融资时，你必须注意你需要能够发行和偿还这笔债务。</p><p>我认为，就目前而言，在不涉及太多政治细节的情况下，我的意思是，相对于他们对 COVID 的反应或 10 年前你知道的欧元危机的反应，欧洲可能不是一个好地方。我的意思是欧洲的政治局势可能间接地对欧洲央行产生了一些影响，正如你所知道的那样，我的意思是克里斯蒂娜拉加德在马里奥德拉吉之后一直做得非常出色，但该机构可能应该在你的方式上更大胆一些&#39;重新解决这个通货膨胀问题。</p><p>因为我们都知道，一段非常低的利率会造成巨大的不平等。获得信贷的人与无法获得信贷的人之间的不平等。当我说人时，它是个人的，是公司的，是国家的。具有讽刺意味的是，你拯救了一个系统，但你让这个系统在人们走出这个时期的方式上变得更加不平等。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这真的很有趣。在利率极低的后金融危机时代，任何以信贷、房地产、股票、债券定价的东西都表现非常好。当然，这有助于美国前 10% 的人。在 COVID 期间，我们看到了大规模的财政反应，而不仅仅是货币反应，这似乎对整个经济阶层，尤其是中产阶级都有帮助。那么，我们在金融危机后和 COVID 后的经历如何告诉我们需要在货币和财政刺激之间取得平衡？</p><p>是的，你完全正确。 But by the same token, we know that right now, I&#39;m not an economist, but in the US, in Europe, the inflation, the structural inflation, people might have a different view about that, is certainly hurting the one with the less resources.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> CHABRAN: Obviously, food, energy, housing, and not even talking about school, healthcare, and obviously in Europe we have a totally different environment about this matter.</p><p> So it&#39;s a tricky situation, and where I think asset managers have a role to play is in making sure that whenever someone is saving a dollar, or investing $1 billion, be a private investor or a large institutional investors, is that there is the appropriate risk return associated with the strategy that is being implemented.</p><p> That was very complicated to do in the zero interest rates environment, because everyone threw the dices and it was a double six, because you can only make it right when money is free.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> CHABRAN: Because when money is free, investment has no merit. And now that we are in a situation where money has some value, then you can be discriminating, and that should benefit, again, the one individual saving a dollar, or the one institution only investing a billion.</p><p> And that, in that respect, regardless of this macro situation, if I come back to our role as asset managers, that&#39;s where we have a role to play.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So let&#39;s talk a little bit about valuations relative to risk and reward. Arguably the United States, both the public markets and the private markets, are not cheap today. They&#39;re not crazy dot-com expensive, but they&#39;re certainly not inexpensive. How does Europe and the rest of the world compare on a valuation basis to the US?</p><p> CHABRAN: Maybe because I come from a leverage finance background, as I told you, I tend always to focus on the downside. But I also learned along the way that you rarely die, I mean as a company, from your P&amp;L or from your assets, but you always die from your liabilities.</p><p> And I think that effectively this excess in very cheap money, this excess in leverage, this excess in thinking that you could access unlimited for an indefinite period of time of cheap to free capital may have created some, the wrong asset allocation pattern in some places.</p><p> So I think we&#39;ve now entered a period where we have to swallow this whole mispriced, over-levered assets out there. Corporate credit was one, obviously the bonds, I mean the sovereign bond market, and we remember the SVB story, it&#39;s about T-bills.</p><p> And then you, obviously the real estate, many areas that were over-levered at the wrong cost. And that could be painful, because someone will have to take the pain, even if, unlike 2008, where the risk was concentrated on banks&#39; balance sheet, today is much more spread across, let&#39;s say, asset managers. But you have to find a way to dry up all this excess of liquidity, which was necessary on the one hand, but maybe mispriced on the other hand.</p><p> And so today, I think that part of the IG fixed rate corporate bond market, obviously part of the real estate, and we&#39;ve been talking at length about that, we have to suffer some of the pain or losses in some way shape or form.</p><p> As always, on the other side of this trade, that will create great opportunities for people liquid, nimble, who don&#39;t have to carry aged inventories, if I may say.</p><p> I have the impression that the US will be more realistic in the way they approach that, in terms of taking the heat, taking the pain, and starting again. In Europe, maybe there&#39;s a little bit of a pre-turn and extend game, but it&#39;s always better to, what has to be done ultimately should be done immediately.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Tear the band-aid off, don&#39;t wait.</p><p> CHABRAN: Exactly, and that&#39;s what we should do when it comes to financial risk and financial pricing.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So you mentioned the excess liquidity is causing excesses and dislocations. Have higher Fed rates and other around the world, higher interest rates, taken some of that out of the system, and combined, what is the impact of the regional banks that have gone belly up, a handful of them, but it certainly has put the fear of God into a lot of, you small banking shops, what does that do to all the excess liquidity that&#39;s out there?</p><p> CHABRAN: You know, on the regional bank, I&#39;d rather not comment, I&#39;m not an expert, and it came as a surprise how quickly large, very large institutions could get into some liquidity stress. Coming back to my comment, again, it&#39;s your liability side. And there&#39;s been plenty of comment there.</p><p> What I see is that, once again, for asset managers, It&#39;s a very interesting structural opportunity because it creates a bit of void in terms of the market that we can fill in in some way, shape, or form. So I think that on the positive side, investors, allocators.</p><p> Today they can effectively allocate capital into strategies which will create a compounding effect to their portfolio. Because what was, I don&#39;t know, three, four percent in some strategies two years ago, now can be eight to 10.</p><p> And so when you start compounding your new allocation into these type of strategies, that can make up for the part of your portfolio which itself could be a little bit underwater as a consequence of those rising interest rates. Again, credit, real estate, what have you. So that&#39;s the positive. You have to be able to do that, right? So how do you do that? I mean, if you have effectively the denominator&#39;s effect that people have been talking about, or more liquidity constraint because cash is not coming back as quickly as you had anticipated because your managers cannot sell their portfolios.</p><p> The secondary market has been developing like crazy on the private equity, for example. As I said, private credit is another one. Real estate will be an obvious one, given the amount of capital out there.</p><p> And so it&#39;s about being prepared to say, okay, I&#39;ve been making five, six, seven percent on this strategy, maybe I will exit this strategy, albeit at a discount, the lowest possible, but the proceeds will be able to be reinvested into strategy that will generate a higher return, which over a short to medium timeframe can make up for this cash flow requirement that I need for my pensioners or what have you.</p><p> So I&#39;m actually very optimistic that all asset owners, asset allocators, the one can be nimble. It&#39;s a very exciting time ahead.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Let&#39;s talk a little bit about how TIKEHAU champions impact investing. Obviously the goal is to get to some sort of sustainable future. What&#39;s your investment thesis there?</p><p> CHABRAN: Yes. I think we were relatively early in what has become a very mainstream strategy, you know, rightly so, and that was really a combination of many factors. We launched our very first growth private equity strategy in 2017-2018, way before it has, as I said, become a must-have strategy for many managers and for many allocators.</p><p> We started doing that because in Europe, we&#39;ve been investing alongside entrepreneurs, families, as I said, we&#39;re not a buyout shop, we don&#39;t take control, we don&#39;t lever up companies, we&#39;re trying to, in our role of the middleman between the asset owners and the companies, to allocate where we see a financial play, but an impactful financial play. So when we started this strategy in 1718, and started allocating capital, investing in entrepreneurs who had a solution, that had to be massified. Because when you want to meet these targets and these goals in terms of climate of CO2 reduction, it&#39;s great to be investing in what will change by 2050 but it&#39;s more important to find what works today and it&#39;s to be massified.</p><p> Scale up. We&#39;re investing in profitable mid-market companies making 20 million, 25 million, 50 million EBITDA and needed capital in. These guys are not looking to sell their company, they need the capital in to scale. And we started doing that across low carbon mobility, across energy efficiencies of the buildings. As you know, it&#39;s 40 percent of the green gas emission. And so we started doing that, I would say, naturally, five years later, we now can represent effectively the case studies. Obviously the track record, it matters, but people want to understand what we&#39;re talking about when we&#39;re talking about this type of impact investing.</p><p> Here it&#39;s about climate.</p><p> We then launched regenerative agricultural strategy because one of the key objectives is how do you capture carbon and there&#39;s nothing like the soil and the ground to help do that. That&#39;s on the equity side.</p><p> And then we started doing some private credit impact financing.这意味着什么？ You&#39;re a borrower, we&#39;re lending you some money, at 5 percent, you&#39;re three times your EBITDA, we take all the traditional credit metrics of financial analysis, and then we add a third dimension. If you hit certain targets, certain goals, extra financial goals, then you will improve your cost of funding. And your 5 percent coupon will go down to 4 if effectively you demonstrate that you reduce by X or Y or change this production process.</p><p> And all of a sudden, you realize that if your cost of funding goes down, as a consequence of some extra financial goals being met, well, your return on equity goes up.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> CHABRAN: And so you can demonstrate that it&#39;s not about being a philanthropy. It&#39;s about making sure that we use the capital available to send it where it makes sense, and then all stakeholders benefit from it. And so as much as five years ago, it was nice to have, and once again, create not compete, we&#39;re trying to push that forward.</p><p> Today, it&#39;s non-negotiable. It&#39;s not negotiable with our LPs. It&#39;s not negotiable with our customers, with our partners, with our banks, with our clients, with our staff, Barry. I mean, when we talk to some of our 20-something, 30-something colleagues, professionals, It&#39;s part of their commitment to the firm.</p><p> Because one big issue you know in this, when it comes to this impact and ESG, let&#39;s say in the wider sense, at best you can come across very opportunistic, at worst you come across as fake. And in both situation, it&#39;s not good.</p><p> And so us, our colleagues, our staff, people and all the stakeholders, I mean, they are the guardians, they are the stewards of us being real here. So again, now it&#39;s no longer a nice-to-have, it&#39;s a must-have, and there&#39;s only one way.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So ESG seems to have found a lot of support in Europe. Are you a little bit surprised about how this has become politicized in the US? It seems like they&#39;re a group of people who are pushing back against impact investing, sustainable investing, not because of the returns, but they just don&#39;t like the politics of it.</p><p> CHABRAN: Yes. I&#39;m not surprised because, and again, I&#39;m an alien here, but I try to be an observer of the dynamic of the politics here in the USA. And we even experience that ourselves. Some of our LPs are very often made up of different boards, some teachers, firemen, policeman, you know, employees, public servants employees. And whilst we were dealing with the same counterparty, the same pension fund, some of their constituents, some of the underlying boards, disagree on the approach to take there.</p><p> So we&#39;ve experienced that firsthand, that within one given investor or asset owner, there could be some divergence. And very often now I can say, because there was a bit of a misunderstanding of what we were trying to do and what others are trying to do.</p><p> So I&#39;m hopeful that with a bit of education, the science-based approach, people will realize that it shouldn&#39;t be a political game. I understand why. I&#39;m not naive. I understand why. But I think the majority should prevail to understand that the asset owners today, the asset managers who can help them deploy the capital, have a historical mission because we will be judged 50 years down the road.</p><p> I mean, people will look back and say, what did you do with the amount of capital that was available back then to effectively direct this capital to where it matters? So I&#39;m trying to take this perspective because effectively we&#39;ve never been in an environment with so much cheap liquidity that could be used purposely.</p><p> So you talked about ESG ratchets where people get better rates if they hit certain metrics. And you talked a little bit about agriculture, regenerative agriculture. Explain for those of us not familiar with that, what is regenerative agriculture? What is the focus? What do you want to accomplish with it? Is it just carbon capture or is it more?</p><p> CHABRAN: It&#39;s the whole chain. I mean, it&#39;s the fact that soil goes without saying is a scarce resource that needs to be maintained in a way to be able to keep on producing in a way that for the next generation, you don&#39;t look back and you leave a brown soil full of fertilizer or others that will not be able to generate the same quality of product for the future generation at a time where you&#39;ll have to feed much more people.</p><p> So the technique here, very similar to the climate approach we took five years ago, is really about finding entrepreneurs and the companies who have a solution for soil, effectively a fertility, let&#39;s say, or some technique. You know, it&#39;s not really the agri-tech, as you may be used to, but some techniques have been proven and need this capital to scale, and this capital would not be available otherwise, because it&#39;s not about buying land or acres or forest. It&#39;s not about the agri-tech, which is effectively attracting a lot of capital.</p><p> But these entrepreneurs, these small cap businesses with a proven concept and profitability and they need this capital to scale. So you would be investing 20, 30 percent, taking 23 percent of the company, investing this capital to effectively help scale the business to a size where then you can get to more banking financing, capital market, which is not that open.</p><p> So it&#39;s this whole band, so it&#39;s certainly the case in Europe, we see it more and more here in the US, of this small mid-cap market that doesn&#39;t have, and even more so, going back to your comment about the regional banks, you&#39;ve got part of the financial market structure which is disappearing, and so you need the alternative source of capital, and so that&#39;s where we can be a very relevant tool.</p><p> And that&#39;s for the companies, and the investors also want to allocate there.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And you partnered with some really interesting companies on this, AXA, the big insurer, and Unilever, the consumer products company, what&#39;s their interest in this sort of sustainable investing?</p><p> CHABRAN: So one comment, as an aside, at TIKEHAU, we&#39;ve always partnered with, or we try as much as we can, to partner with corporates to bring additional skillset. We did that in energy transition, for example, with Total Energies, very early on, &#39;17, &#39;18. We did that in the aerospace, cyber with a bunch of prominent European and global players such as Airbus, Dassault, Safran, Thales, bringing obviously some capital but more importantly some skill sets, some knowledge, some reach so that back to my create not compete, we can tell a different story with investors.</p><p> And as you just mentioned, the last one with Unilever, is the same, is exactly the same approach, which is bringing additional expertise alongside an asset manager, us, financial investors, and there&#39;s no shortage of capital, as we said, out there.</p><p> In that case, one of the largest European insurance company, if not global, and having together a different proposal, fully aligned, with some complementary sourcing to the deal flow. And here again, at first, people were maybe looking at us like, why do you need to bring a corporate? Are there some conflict of interest involved here? And then, a few years down the line, they&#39;re like, well, that&#39;s a very different proposal that we may have heard from older managers and there are plenty out there.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: What&#39;s the conflict of interest if you&#39;re bringing in a consumer product try and make food on a more efficient productive sustainable way.</p><p> CHABRAN: That&#39;s my point, they should be known and they are known but you know there&#39;s you know people at times are a little bit reluctant or resistant you know to change …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Status quo, it&#39;s really powerful, isn&#39;t it?</p><p> CHABRAN: Voila.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I love this quote of yours I have to ask you about this. The longer the happy hour, the harder the hangover.</p><p> Explain. Very French.</p><p> CHABRAN: Well that was you know I think that was at Milken&#39;s, at Milken Institute in May 22 and that&#39;s when the interest rates are starting to raise and I think I was telling you earlier I was surprised to see that many people in a surprise because effectively the bar had been open for quite a long time with very cheap liquidity, if I may say, available.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Going back to the financial crisis, the entire period that followed was free booze for everyone.</p><p> CHABRAN: Exactly, and that&#39;s 10 years, if not more. And some of us, I think, had effectively lost sight that liquidity should have a price, and credit has some value. And so effectively, this comment I made was that, yes, people are going to have a hangover of this mispriced, over-leveraged asset they may have bought, invested into, as a consequence of this free liquidity.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So let&#39;s talk about, perhaps, a mispriced asset class that was relying on free liquidity, as we&#39;re recording this, there is a recent Wall Street Journal headline, “Company insiders made millions before the SPAC bust.” What are your thoughts on the SPACs, special purpose investment vehicles? How do you look at those?</p><p> CHABRAN: So we got into SPACs two years ago, hopefully not to follow the herd, but because we saw there a very useful technology that could help some of our private companies, which is what we do, the bulk of what we do is investing with private entrepreneurs, accessing the public market with the support of experienced managers, the operating partners, with the support of experienced financial players.</p><p> And effectively, we very successfully “un-SPACed” some. We took public on Euronext Amsterdam, a great company in the TV content production business, 3 billion turnover, 600 million EBITDA. It&#39;s called FL Entertainment, great entrepreneur, Stéphane Courbit. It&#39;s a real company. Our SPAC is trading at, I guess, 10 bucks or around. A real company. So the issue was not the SPAC as a technology. The issue was the type of company that were trying to access this market opportunistically and rightly so in front of some capital that had been given to SPAC&#39;s promoters and managers.</p><p> Remember that interest rates were negative.</p><p> So SPACs were used by some investors as a vault. Here&#39;s some cash.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Getting 5 percent.</p><p> CHABRAN: Exactly. I&#39;ll make up for the interest shortfall and I have the option to opt out.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So it was a guaranteed higher yield, I won&#39;t say high yield, but higher yield bonds with an equity option at the end, if you like the equity company, you can stay with it. Saba Capital is one, a few others did the same thing.</p><p> CHABRAN: The technology itself was excess of cash, interest rates are at zero, I get negative cash, negative interest on my cash account, so here&#39;s the cash and I may opt out.</p><p> What we tried to do in what we did, and some work, although we decided to give back the capital because back to my skin in the game approach, the one we decided to return the capital that was last month, we had 150 million plus of our own capital committed to it.</p><p> So rather than chasing the cheap option with the view of hopefully making the return embedded with the option, we&#39;re like, first and foremost, we&#39;re depleting our capital. The opportunity is not there. We&#39;re not going to deploy our capital for the sake of it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: This comes back to skin in the game. When you&#39;re a co-investor with your LPs, you don&#39;t make dumb decisions because, hey, we have the cash. We might as well spend it.</p><p> CHABRAN: I think so. So that was just I think misuse of an interesting technique with some investors and a misuse of interesting techniques for the wrong company.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So I read a piece recently, a research piece that said Brexit may have taken as much as 5 percent off the total GDP of the United Kingdom. You worked in London, you&#39;re now in New York, originally from Paris. Does that sound realistic? What was the impact of Brexit on the UK, and who has stepped into the void that Brexit teed up?</p><p> So first of all, that&#39;s a decision that was made by the British people, and I will not comment on the rationale beyond that. I read the same studies that you mentioned, and every day I would talk to some friends, entrepreneurs in Europe telling me how challenging it has become when just to move goods and things into, and just trading with the UK.</p><p> The one part I can comment on was the whole debate around the future of the city of London as a preeminent financial place, global but obviously European.</p><p> What I can tell you Barry, is since the world reopen and you can travel again, I&#39;m actually going back more often to London than to Paris nowadays, which is the headquarter of my firm. Why that? Because London remains a critical business center for financial services.</p><p> There are some challenging associated with some regulation in the way you have to trade and why people and banks had to open or export some branches onto the continent. And I understand why and the technicalities. But when it comes to the cosmopolitan nature of London, attracting global talents, and as much as, I&#39;m French, and Paris has been doing a tremendous job in attracting talents and firms, but the scale is such that I wouldn&#39;t bet against London as a financial center. So we have to cope with technical aspects, regulation, cost of doing business for some has become very punitive if you don&#39;t have the scale.</p><p> And that&#39;s why if I&#39;m a bit selfish in the approach, we were fully equipped on the continent to start with. We&#39;re now moving back more aggressively into London because we were less over-exposed when many people are doing the contrary.</p><p> People are trying to reduce their investment allocation to the UK, their workforce in the UK. So we&#39;re trying to be a bit contrarian and taking advantage of that.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So people overreacted in one direction, creates opportunities.</p><p> CHABRAN: Maybe.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Europe is dealing with a war on its eastern border. What has the Russian invasion of Ukraine done in terms of energy supplies and just the entire relationship of Europe with Russia?</p><p> CHABRAN: Well, it&#39;s a complicated one, it&#39;s a very sad one because, well, I can tell you, Barry, sitting here in the US, and when I talk to friends, family over there, the perception of the war is very different from one side to the other, because the reality that it&#39;s two hours away from many of the Western European capital and the perception, the feeling with the population is very different.</p><p> So having said that, remember a year ago when the war started, obviously the concern about energy, independence, sustainability was front and center. That was, I think, the silver lining of the situation to put more light and focus on accelerating part of the transition and in itself that was an encouraging step.</p><p> Looking backwards a year or 18 months now into this situation, it&#39;s “not as bad” quote unquote, on the energy side, which is good news. But the whole situation, which I think we are unfortunately stuck with for a relatively long period of time, as creating a lot of uncertainty in the region and beyond, but also by the same token a lot of political willingness to move quicker. And the response, if you remember, that the European government made right after the war, they made more progress in a matter of a few weeks than we had in a few years. And so at times it&#39;s effectively when the essential is at stake that people can react constructively.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So the concern, aside from all the humanitarian tragedy of the invasion, was oil prices would spike, it would eventually lead to a recession in Europe. But a lot of Europe seems to have avoided that.</p><p> What are your thoughts about greater Europe tipping into a recession? And pretty clear parts of Europe have slowed down dramatically because of the increased costs and dealing with the war. What does the environment in Europe look like to you?</p><p> So not dissimilar to what we&#39;re experiencing here in the US and the reentering of production capacity, we&#39;re seeing that in many countries across Europe. Reindustrialization has been probably the most popular world of politicians lately, not only because you need to demonstrate less dependency to outside market. The whole deglobalization theme, I think it was accelerating by this whole situation.</p><p> And so for politicians, it&#39;s a way to show a direction for the population. It&#39;s a new paradigm, a new software. And coming back to what we do for a living, asset manager, it&#39;s a great frame in finding ways to allocate, reallocate, working with global investors to attract more capital in certain countries, for certain industries. It&#39;s not happening overnight, but you can make it happen fairly quickly, fairly quickly being a matter of months.</p><p> If you&#39;ve got all these stars aligned from the political direction to the population adhesion and then the capital allocation. I&#39;m hopeful and I&#39;m optimistic that that could be the silver lining of the whole situation, as dramatic the situation can be.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So you have offices in Asia, if we&#39;re de-globalizing to some degree, and China has been the big industrial driver of much of the world, what does it mean for investing in Asia generally, but more specifically China?</p><p> CHABRAN: So what we&#39;ve been doing in Asia, first out of Singapore, where we started eight, nine years ago in Singapore, and then Korea and Japan. We don&#39;t have any presence in China, as a matter of fact. And the dialogue we had with these investors locally was really about attracting them to some of our existing strategies in Europe or in the US.</p><p> Asia is, I have the chance to go back there from time to time, and each time I&#39;m there I found local economies that have been transformed. If you look at Singapore, what it was when we first moved there, and eight years later, that&#39;s a global hub. Like a global hub with all the consequences you&#39;re reading every day. The Bloomberg news, the price of real estate, and the numbers of family offices who moved from Hong Kong, from part of the Middle East to open there for the very same reason that you have created a great talent hub, a very business-friendly environment. You&#39;ve got the most sophisticated sovereign wealth funds in the world. We were lucky enough to have Temasek backing us as early as 2016. They&#39;ve been a great partner ever since. Great marketplace.</p><p> The way we look at our Singapore operations today, we have a headquarter, Paris, and we have three global hubs, New York, London, Singapore. And out of these hubs, then you can reach on a global basis first investors and effectively attracting them where we think there is an interesting investment proposal and also creating investment opportunities when you&#39;ve got this supply-demand imbalance.</p><p> Again, it all comes down to supply-demand and how we can best take advantage of that.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. So let&#39;s jump to our favorite questions that we ask all of our guests, starting with what have you been streaming these days? What&#39;s been keeping you informed and entertained, either podcast or Netflix or whatever?</p><p> CHABRAN: One I like and I recommend, because that&#39;s being produced by this company we backed that we took, we helped take public a few months ago, is the “Peaky Blinders” that&#39;s great entertainment. Not only because I love this whole story about the villain and the gangsters and all that, but more importantly because that&#39;s great content.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Is that Netflix or Amazon?</p><p> CHABRAN: It&#39;s a Netflix one. It&#39;s a Netflix one. I strongly recommend and produce by our friend at FL Entertainment.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. So who were your mentors? Who helped to shape your career?</p><p> CHABRAN: So few of them are senior people I worked for when I was a young analyst and associate, because every one of them in their own different approach helped me challenge the fact that we are going on our own at a relatively young age for this business. Some of them telling us, “Well, it&#39;s either too late or too early for good or bad reasons.” And on the contrary, people saying, which was less, the case is in Europe than it can be the case here in the US, there&#39;s never a good time and you should give it a go.</p><p> And so many of them were finance professional, most of the time in investment banking, and still remain friends. Some of them joined us, by the way, along the way at TIKEHAU. And that&#39;s one thing that obviously was very valuable when you start your own venture firm.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: What are some of your favorite books? What are you reading right now?</p><p> CHABRAN: So two books I&#39;ve started, very different. The first one, I was lucky to attend one of the, again, Mike Milken&#39;s, you know, event, you know, recently both in LA and then later on, and as you know, he&#39;s extremely focused on healthcare. And the whole focus is putting through his institute and all the philanthropy around there.</p><p> And the book is called “Faster Cures, Accelerating the Future of Health” by Mike Milken. It&#39;s something which is fascinating because in our job day to day, it&#39;s really short term. And when you step back a bit and you look a little bit of these demographic issues, we touch base on some of those issues, energy and all that, but the demographic is probably the most challenging one.</p><p> And even if it&#39;s 50, 75 years from now, I think we should start factoring in many of that in today&#39;s decision.</p><p> And the other book, more recent, I was lucky to meet a French professor in Boston who&#39;s a teacher both at HBS and HKS. She&#39;s been there for 20 years. Her name is Julie Battilana. And the last book is called “Power for All” And it&#39;s all about the relationship to– I wouldn&#39;t say even power, but if effectively power is about having an influence on making someone else change behavior, how it&#39;s not only top down and the way we may have learned it, and how we should with a new generation, in a new cycle, and the perspective of things that are critical to me, which are democracy, but also capitalism, which is fueling many of that.</p><p> How do you reconcile all that, and it&#39;s a worthwhile reading.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Sounds interesting. Our last two questions, what sort of advice would you give to a recent college graduate who is interested in a career in either private equity or investing?</p><p> CHABRAN: Well, I would send him some of the mottos where you&#39;re seeing everyday at TIKEHAU Capital. Be curious, think out of the box, be on the ball, think big. I will share that with them because that&#39;s one thing that doesn&#39;t change. Technology may change, but interpersonal skill set and being hungry, I think that&#39;s what matters.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Interesting, and our final question. What do you know about the world of investing today? You wish you knew 25 or so years ago when you were first getting started.</p><p> CHABRAN: Never take anything for granted.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Thank you so much for being so generous with your time, Mathieu. We have been speaking with Mathieu Chabran, co-founder of TIKEHAU Capital.</p><p> If you enjoy this conversation, well, be sure and check out any of the other 500 or so discussions we&#39;ve had over the past eight or so years. You can find those at iTunes, Spotify, YouTube, wherever you find your favorite podcast.</p><p> Sign up for my daily reading list at ritholtz.com. Follow me on Twitter @ritholtz. Follow all of the Bloomberg family of podcasts on Twitter @podcast.</p><p> I would be remiss if I did not thank the crack team that helps put the conversations together each week. My audio engineer is Sebastian Escobar. My producer is Paris Wald. Atika Valbrun is our project manager. Sean Russo is my head of research. I&#39;m Barry Ritholtz. You&#39;ve been listening to Masters in Business on Bloomberg Radio.</p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"> ~~~ </p><p></p><p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-mathieu-chabran/">Transcript: Mathieu Chabran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> MiB: Mathieu Chabran, Tikehau Capital</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/mib-mathieu-chabran/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jun 2023 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Alternatives/PE/Hedge Funds]]></category><category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314662 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> This week, we speak with Mathieu Chabran, co-founder of Tikehau Capital. The firm is a global alternative asset manager with $40B in AUM manged in 13 offices around the world. He cofounded Tikehau in 2004 with Antoine Flamarion, a colleague at Deutsche Bank.  Chabran was named Chevalier de l&#39;Ordre de la Légion d&#39;Honneur…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/mib-mathieu-chabran/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/mib-mathieu-chabran/">MiB: Mathieu Chabran, Tikehau Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; fullscreen *; clipboard-write" frameborder="0" height="175" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;border-radius:10px;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/mathieu-chabran-on-using-creativity-to-compete/id730188152?i=1000616332516"></iframe></p><p></p><p></p><p> This week, we speak with Mathieu Chabran, co-founder of Tikehau Capital. The firm is a global alternative asset manager with $40B in AUM manged in 13 offices around the world. He cofounded Tikehau in 2004 with Antoine Flamarion, a colleague at Deutsche Bank.  Chabran was named <em>Chevalier de l&#39;Ordre de la Légion d&#39;Honneur</em> by decree of the President of the French Republic in January 2022.</p><p> He explains how the firm decided to expand from Paris into London and Singapore and finally into the US, opening offices in New York.</p><p> Chabran describes how the fund has used its strengths to innovate their way into the States. They were one of the first firms to do secondary private credit trading, and they pioneered the use of ESG ratchets – better rates of interest as borrowers achieve agreed upon sustainability metrics.</p><p> A list of his favorite books is below; A transcript of our conversation is <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-mathieu-chabran/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">available here</a> Tuesday.</p><p> You can stream and download our full conversation, including any podcast extras, on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">iTunes</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5LGxKlY6fzXS3tGsjB23Cb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> , <a href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> , <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvZTczYzk5OGUtNmU2MC00MzJmLTg2MTAtYWUyMTAxNDBjNWIxLzRlNGNkOTEwLTQwYTEtNDYxOS1hNWYzLWFlMmIwMDEyZmZmZi81ODczYTNjYi0yOThmLTQwYmMtYjcxZi1hZTJiMDAxMzAwMGQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> , <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLe4PRejZgr0PzN7r8NikAnOqP70DHhoJ0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> , and <a href="http://www.bloomberg.com/podcasts/masters-in-business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a> . All of our earlier podcasts on your favorite pod hosts can be <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">found here</a> .</p><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> next week with NBC News and former WSJ reporter Gretchen Morgenson. The Pulitizer price winning investigative journalist is the author of a new book, <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1982191287/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>These Are the Plunderers: How Private Equity Runs―and Wrecks―America</em></a> . </p><p></p><p></p><p><span id="more-314662"></span></p><p></p><p></p><p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Faster Cures: Accelerating the Future of Health" type="text/html" width="500" height="550" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen style="max-width:100%" src="https://read.amazon.com/kp/card?preview=inline&#038;linkCode=kpd&#038;ref_=k4w_oembed_3g5Fs3FDrchxAH&#038;asin=0063260212&#038;tag=kpembed-20"></iframe></p><p></p><p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Power, for All: How It Really Works and Why It&#039;s Everyone&#039;s Business" type="text/html" width="500" height="550" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen style="max-width:100%" src="https://read.amazon.com/kp/card?preview=inline&#038;linkCode=kpd&#038;ref_=k4w_oembed_Zu6c4dcGkkev2Z&#038;asin=1982141646&#038;tag=kpembed-20"></iframe></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/mib-mathieu-chabran/">MiB: Mathieu Chabran, Tikehau Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> Masters in Business: The Emerging Manager Playbook</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/masters-in-business-the-emerging-manager-playbook/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Alternatives/PE/Hedge Funds]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314436 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>﻿   The video from last week&#39;s panel is above Bloomberg Masters in Business host Barry Ritholtz discusses the current environment for hedge fund launches with IDW Group Founder and Chief Executive Officer Ilana D. Weinstein, Woodline Partners Co-Chief Investment Officer Mike Rockefeller, Fernbridge Capita Management Founder Brennan Diaz and Knighthead Capital Management Co-Founder Thomas…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/masters-in-business-the-emerging-manager-playbook/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/masters-in-business-the-emerging-manager-playbook/">Masters in Business: The Emerging Manager Playbook</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="YouTube 视频播放器" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/j8KY2az9ucU" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"> <span data-mce-type="bookmark" style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" class="mce_SELRES_start">的</span></iframe></p><p></p><p>The video from <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/05/identifying-emerging-managers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">last week&#39;s panel</a> is above</p><p> Bloomberg Masters in Business host Barry Ritholtz discusses the current environment for hedge fund launches with IDW Group Founder and Chief Executive Officer Ilana D. Weinstein, Woodline Partners Co-Chief Investment Officer Mike Rockefeller, Fernbridge Capita Management Founder Brennan Diaz and Knighthead Capital Management Co-Founder Thomas Wagner.</p><p> Transcript after the jump…</p><p></p><p><span id="more-314436"></span></p><p></p><p> We have an amazing group to discuss what it&#39;s like to launch a hedge fund in the current environment and some of the things you need to know about becoming an emerging manager. Let me introduce the panel from your left to right.</p><p> Mike Rockefeller is co-founder of the six billion dollar long short equity fund Woodline Capital. Previously, he was a successful pm at Citadel; Woodline launched in twenty nineteen. Is that right? With two billion dollars.</p><p> Ilana Weinstein is the founder of the IDW Group. It&#39;s one of the top at head hunters in the world of hedge funds. She just celebrated her 20th anniversary with the firm. And if you read in big moves between funds who got hired, who jumped ship very often, Iaw is the mover and shaker behind the scenes.</p><p> Tom Wagner is the co-founder of the 10 billion dollar credit and event driven fund. Knight Head capital recently. He acquired the UK Birmingham Soccer League and Stadium, as well as an interest in a Pickle Ball team with Tom Brady. And I misread the lineup, so I&#39;m going to say.</p><p> Brennan Diaz is the founder of the 1 billion dollar FirmBridge Capital Firm. He hails from previous firms, Viking And he launched Firm Bridge in late 2020. Good, good timing. Taking a hedge fund approach to long-only investing. We have about 50 minutes. And if there&#39;s time at the end, we&#39;ll see if there are any questions from the audience. But let&#39;s just start by talking about the current environment.</p><p> It&#39;s been a crazy couple of years from the pandemic to the new regime of rate increases. Frame what&#39;s going on in today&#39;s environment and what&#39;s it like managing a fund in this sort of circumstance?</p><p> So let&#39;s start with you, Mike.</p><p>当然。 So I think one theme is that allocators are becoming more sophisticated about the return quality that they are receiving and what they&#39;re willing to pay for. And what they want is uncorrelated alpha and you take that concept, but then you look at the traditional long, short hedge fund and they are running portfolios of less than 30 percent Indio, which means that those returns are highly dependent on macro factors,<br /> very unpredictable factors that that you&#39;ll be subject to.<br /> And what I think is an increasing appreciation is that a high area of portfolio is what is predictive for an uncorrelated alpha stream.<br /> And that is why you&#39;re seeing the massive increase in multi manager assets<br /> and those assets have more than doubled since 2017. If you look at some of the top launches that are coming out in 2023, ILX and<br /> free stone. That trend looks to be continuing. And the reason why is that a multi manager provides a one stop shop for an<br /> allocator where you can get a high radio, low vol durable return stream and<br /> you can do it in one single investment where you where you could have scale and you eliminate complexity, diversification built in right from from<br /> the get go. That&#39;s right. A lot of let&#39;s talk a little bit about this current environment. You see it from the perspective of talent.<br /> Tell us tell us what you&#39;re seeing. I&#39;m going to zoom out, because if you all want to start a hedge fund, I think we need to kind of start at the top and<br /> I&#39;m going to give you the macro and then we&#39;ll go quickly. Strategy by strategy. Barry, you and I talked about this<br /> recently. There was, to me at least an amazing article at the FT put out a couple months ago, which said this was news to<br /> me. I knew there were a lot of hedge funds, but apparently there are more hedge funds than Burger Kings.<br />好的。 True, thirty thousand hedge funds.<br /> The other thing you should keep in mind is that the average lifespan of a hedge<br /> fund is three years. So if you guys want to start a fund and you don&#39;t want it to be just another Burger King that goes out of business,<br /> you need to understand what the lay of the land is within each of those strategies. Mike talked a little bit about long,<br /> short equities. Not to be like the Grim Reaper, but the<br /> reality is, if you&#39;re not a multi manager and you&#39;re not aggressively<br /> managing market risk, then you fall into the category of a long, short<br /> single manager that probably takes concentrated, more concentrated directional risk. And if you look at how these funds have<br /> performed over the last two full years, twenty one and twenty two, the average<br /> the cumulative return of these funds is down 40 percent. OK, with some funds down as high as 60 percent.<br /> Like Tiger Global. So if you think about the dollars lost to LP and it&#39;s important to understand this because 40 percent of the hedge<br /> fund universe is long, short equities. So I&#39;m betting there&#39;s a decent percentage of you here that is thinking about starting a long, short equity<br /> fund. There was a tremendous amount of a, um, lost. So Tiger Global Pre 2021 was 100 hundred<br /> billion. Maverick 14 billion. 130 billion. And then non tiger cubs like algae on 30<br /> billion. Perceptive 10 billion. When you&#39;re down 40 percent on average, it&#39;s a huge loss to the industry.<br /> More than 50 percent of total losses in two in 2022 came from long short equity<br /> funds and half of hedge fund liquidations came from long short equity funds. So you really need to think about if you<br /> don&#39;t fall in to a all alpha non correlated category like Mike does.<br /> What is the value that you&#39;re providing? Macro very volatile return stream.<br /> Twenty twenty one crappy year for most macro funds. Twenty twenty two great year. Twenty three again.<br /> Not such a good year. And you see again brand name funds like Roe Coast, Castle, Hook Element Element charged 40 percent fees, was able to up<br /> it to that in 2020, shrinking and trying to stem the bleeding from negative returns on credit. A bright spot, but I think I&#39;m sure Tom<br /> will talk more about this. You really need scale to compete. And then there&#39;s the multi managers and that&#39;s gonna be your biggest problem as<br /> a new emerging manager. How you&#39;re going to compete for talent within a paradigm that has everything to offer from analysts up through to PMs.<br /> They have scale, they have capital, they have resources. They have a pathway to be APM. They have an aggressive pay out.<br /> They have economics. And they are like, it&#39;s like my toe sis.<br /> You know, we used to have we have the tiger cubs. Now we have the multi manager cubs. Mike is one of them.<br /> He mentioned I like. I hope it&#39;s okay. I share that view. He is now providing strategic<br /> investments to multi manager funds. I likes are two guys from Sit It Out<br /> that Mike and his team gave capital to and they&#39;re going to launch with 2 billion Brad Stone Grove and other Citadel guy is going to launch with many<br /> billions. Andrew Komori, who came out of GE Shore, is launching with three billion. So into the fray.<br /> So this is the environment you&#39;re entering into. And I as I as someone who has been recruiting<br /> in this industry for the past 20 years with my team and we&#39;re working with the biggest, most successful funds in the world, it&#39;s tough.<br /> Talent is scarce. It&#39;s they have many options.<br /> And I think the multi manager dynamic just makes it that much more intense. So. So let me see what Brendan has to say<br /> about this. You&#39;re the only lonely person on on the panel. Is it that challenging to be long?<br /> Only your how are you finding this environment from from your investment<br /> style? Well, I mean, I think all the points Mike made her are right. And I think that the whole rationale<br /> behind launching along only coming from a long, short background was the realization that market structure was changing.<br /> The ability to access short alpha and short alpha curves were changing, and thus the ability to maintain short gross exposure with the same investment style<br /> and generate that level of alpha wasn&#39;t there as much. And so I kind of felt that pressure on the short side of the portfolio forcing<br /> shorts were running higher net, kind of two bad options for an absolute return product, but looked at alongside a ledger and<br /> still felt very strongly that the pool of alpha we were accessing, they looking out, you know, basically 18 to 18 to 36 months.<br /> So not looking at five to 10 years, but 18 to 36 months forward. Looking forward to what underlying businesses were going to be earning and<br /> thinking about absolute value. Intrinsic value and taking big concentrated bets on opportunities that were really attractive.<br /> But that window was not only kind of as attractive as it&#39;s ever been, but in some ways it&#39;s getting more attractive. Kind of driven by the underlying short<br /> term volatility in the market. And so I don&#39;t think managing along only is is more difficult to manage in the long term.<br /> I think it&#39;s actually materially. Jihye Lee easier. Which is kind of why we went down that route.<br /> And I also think that there&#39;s material demand. I think Mike&#39;s point is 100 percent right. That allocators want to pay for value.正确的。<br /> You know, investors historically have not been, you know, invested in hedge funds just to pay fees on beta. They&#39;ve been willing to pay the fees on<br /> beta because the underlying assumption would be that you would deliver them enough alpha to cover the beta costs. However, there are large pools of<br /> capital in the world that want data exposure, very, very large pools of capital that will always have bad exposure.<br /> So I think the the message of going to people and saying I will take that bet exposure, I personally want that bit exposure for my own capital.<br /> Like over time I want the beta because the beta collecting that risk premium should be positive. And you only pay me when I generate<br /> value for you. Value being defined as excess returns relative to the S&amp;P. I think that has a lot of resonance with<br /> with with a lot of capital providers out there. And I think that it&#39;s an opportunity for people who invest like me, who think<br /> like me to to go out and go out and execute on if they so choose.<br /> But, you know, you have to have the right model. You have to have a truly align fee structure and you have to kind of be<br /> willing to go down that road. So I that you know, I think it&#39;s in many ways the same. It&#39;s responding to the same trend that<br /> Mike is talking about and taking it in a different direction. So to clarify, some people&#39;s called activity fees, the the profit<br /> participation is only on returns over and above what the SPF is generally.<br /> So it&#39;s actually, I would say, even more advantageous and that our management fees are a prepayment on future often. So we have to generate Alpha before we<br /> get to any type of incentive.正确的。 So the idea is over time of life of the<br /> fund, which will be a very long life. When you when we when we end at the end,<br /> we will look back. And 70 percent of the economics of the alpha that has been generated will flow to the investors and 30 percent will<br /> accrue to the manager. And we try to make that as clean and transparent as possible. That creates more volatility in our<br /> in our in our overall incentive fee income relative to other models. But I think that&#39;s very solvable from a talent perspective, having to kind of<br /> talk about that. But that&#39;s the underlying model. Really interesting. Tom, what do you make of this current<br /> environment and how are you finding the worlds of credit within within the<br /> headphones realm? Well, I first of all, thank you, Barry, for having me here and for everyone attending.<br /> Appreciate it. You know, credit is relative to every other asset class we see today and we invest.<br /> We have a of our 10 billion, six of it is permanent capital. So we do a lot beyond just credit. We can do basically anything anywhere in<br /> the world. We want the credit today and particularly private structured credit. So rescue financings, bridge loans,<br /> financing is to provide growth capital all structured as credit offer the<br /> greatest amount of alpha relative to the risk I&#39;ve ever seen in the 25 years I&#39;ve<br /> been doing this. There&#39;s it&#39;s extraordinary excess return. And that&#39;s because that&#39;s not liquid.<br /> And one thing that I think all of you or those of you in the room that are contemplating launching a hedge fund is there is an extreme push pull presently<br /> for liquidity, visibly returns. Investors or allocators are not liquid<br /> and they need to generate returns, particularly in a context of higher rates where their hurdles have all gone up and they&#39;re stuck in older<br /> investments, particularly private equity. They&#39;re probably going to take a period of time to recover to the alpha generative returns that they had historically produced.<br /> So they want you to be liquid and generate returns. That&#39;s not really possible today. So you&#39;ve got to find a niche that fits<br /> you. And I think the best advice that I could give for folks thinking about launching is forget all the noise, forget what the<br /> markets want. Forget what the LP ISE want. Do what you&#39;re going to be good at. It doesn&#39;t matter what your strategy is.<br /> Doesn&#39;t matter what your structure is. Doesn&#39;t matter what your fees are. If you&#39;re good relative to whatever benchmark you&#39;re posted against, you&#39;ll<br /> do just fine. Your business will grow. You&#39;ll make plenty of money. You&#39;ll retire a happy person, your kids.<br /> You never have to work if they don&#39;t want to. You&#39;ll do just fine. But if you try to shoehorn yourself into<br /> something that doesn&#39;t fit, it&#39;ll go terribly wrong. And I think the second most valuable piece of advice I can give you is<br /> separate from all the examples you&#39;re hearing appear of all these multi-billion dollar launches. That&#39;s not normal, right?<br /> It&#39;s not normal. And you might think you&#39;re going to launch with a billion dollars. A lot of help us get started. We thought we were going to launch with a billion five as of March 16th, 2008.<br /> We just come out of the emerging managers conference going, man was perfect. I was like, this is so easy.<br /> Then eight weeks we raised a billion and a half. We&#39;re going to launch with three billion, Ken Griffin was backing us.<br /> It was like the greatest thing ever. The next day, Bear Stearns went bankrupt. And by the time we launched on June 3rd,<br /> 2008, we had 413 million in capital. And the world just changed. Nothing happened with us. All the investments we were pursuing was<br />好的。 Our first couple of years were spectacular. Like everything went great and things turned out OK. But that second piece of advice is you<br /> can&#39;t bank on being a multi-billion dollar launch. And so what does that mean? That means you have to do everything.<br /> You better understand how to set up a computer and phone. You better not to debug your computer. You better know how to answer the phones<br /> politely. You should not make good coffee for your old people. You stop by. You&#39;re gonna be doing all of it. But don&#39;t kid yourself.<br /> And if you don&#39;t launch with billions of dollars of capital locked up for a multi-year period, you run a lot of risk.<br /> You create a cost structure that&#39;s incompatible with where your capital could be, not where it is today. So I would advise that you do what<br /> you&#39;re good at and learn how to do everything well and work really, really hard and stick to it for a period of time.<br /> And if you love it, it&#39;ll work out. So. So let&#39;s address the issue. You just touched on that sub scale<br /> operations. How do you compete for talent in the most competitive market in the world when you can&#39;t write giant checks and<br /> you&#39;re running subscale? Let&#39;s start with you.当然。 He never ran something.这还算公平。 But on a relative basis.<br />是的。 It was only to build only. Well, you know, there&#39;s a great movie that came out in 1989.<br /> So you might not have known it, but feel the dreams and if you haven&#39;t seen it.<br /> The main character, Ray Kinsella, who&#39;s played by Kevin Costner.<br /> He&#39;s out in the middle of his cornfield and he hears a voice. If you build it, he will come. And he doesn&#39;t know what build it is.<br /> But he decides to build a baseball field in his cornfield. And lo and behold, a bunch of dead baseball<br /> players show up at his house and start playing baseball. And you should have the mindset of what that movie tells you, which is if you<br /> build it, they will come. If you have a differentiated value proposition. People will invest and you know, this<br /> this panel is a great representation because it&#39;s all different strategies. We&#39;re all but we what we have and what people forget is what we&#39;re offering is<br /> a product. And so you have to ask yourself, OK, why am I here? What is the product that I&#39;m offering<br /> and what customer base is going to want this product? And if you invest early in your infrastructure, if you hire before you<br /> have capital, not after, then I think that you will get that capital. You know, my my good friend, Brandon<br /> Haley, who launched Holocene, he in 2017 had over two dozen employees without a<br /> zero with zero dollars. And he ended up being a gigantic a<br /> gigantic launch because he sold that story to investors. So that&#39;s the mindset I would take a lot of.<br /> I think the difference, though, Mike, is you&#39;re. You were coming from Citadel. Brandon was coming from said it all.<br /> People were willing to come before you built it because they knew would each of you represented I ISE a we as a firm are very loath.<br /> I&#39;ll be I&#39;ll be candid with you. To do work with emerging managers, because the truth is, most of you are not launching with billions of dollars.<br /> You&#39;re probably not even launching with hundreds of millions of dollars. And given how competitive the talent market is, it&#39;s very hard for really<br /> talented people to get behind you. With no proof of concept because they&#39;re making two bets on you that that are beyond the scope of what they&#39;re the<br /> bets they&#39;re normally making. They&#39;re making a bet on you as a new founder. You&#39;ve never done this before.<br /> And they&#39;re making a bet that you can scale that you are worth getting in the trenches with and grin and that you can grow.<br /> And I guess the good news, bad news about my unfortunately, it&#39;s just it&#39;s on a prediction is just a fact of life. Very few of you will launch with scale<br /> is if you&#39;re under two hundred and fifty million. I actually don&#39;t think you need to worry about this.<br /> You guys may disagree with me, but if you&#39;re a really small fund and many of you may start with 25 million or 50 million or 100 million, you can hire<br /> junior people. You can hire people out of the sell side. You can hire people out of banking and<br /> they&#39;re multiple. And we&#39;ll be thrilled to have a seat at the table. And I also think it&#39;s it&#39;s difficult<br /> unless people know you and have worked with you before, you know, the whole other side of things is. Are you a good mentor?<br /> Can you develop them? Are you going to pay them fairly? Are they joining something special with a great culture?<br /> Is there a runway? These are all the sets of things we deal with in helping people cross the divide to go from where they are to a large<br /> established manager and get them comfortable on all those points. And so that&#39;s also there. And if they haven&#39;t worked with you, you<br /> know, they don&#39;t really know what the odds are that it&#39;s going to be a good fit. And you, in turn, also don&#39;t want to<br /> bring on board senior people that you don&#39;t really know and have to give them substantial points in the fund. And then it may not work out if you end<br /> up with a high class problem of achieving scale. Then we get into the<br /> setting up an economic structure which is going to be attractive to your<br /> investment staff. And I&#39;d say the one guiding principle on that is and it&#39;s a good thing as a newer fund.<br /> The value creation for everyone working there should come at a massively different pace than sitting at a large established player where much of that<br /> value has already been created. So what do I mean by that? If let&#39;s call it 25 to 30 percent gets paid out to the investment and<br /> leadership team. This is on average and this is a back of the envelope thought. But I think directionally it&#39;s true<br /> here. You should be talking about 30 percent going to 50 percent to the extent that the people you hire.<br /> And again, this is further on down the road. Once you have scale and can attract more senior credible people to the<br /> extent that they put up great performance, they can hire and develop people, then you&#39;re able to take on more capital and you&#39;re creating more value.<br /> But at the end of the day, everyone is going to reference you within an inch of your life and the same way. L P&#39;s are going to want to get a point<br /> of view on you. Talent will too. And there&#39;s what you&#39;re telling them upfront, which hopefully is attractive.<br /> But even more attractive is the path forward. And you don&#39;t want them discounting any of the promises or vision that you&#39;re<br /> giving them because of what they&#39;re hearing in the market. So that&#39;s something to bear in mind and I think really critical as you add both<br /> in the meeting, less so maybe in the immediate term, but certainly as you progress and are trying to reach out to really talented, established people.<br /> Brendan, you finding the same sort of circumstances when you&#39;re competing for talent? Watch what your journey been like.<br /> Well, I think it&#39;s a little bit focused on the type of talent you&#39;re recruiting, where it&#39;s like come from a world in a lineage of funds where we don&#39;t hire<br /> experience people, where there&#39;s a kind of fundamental viewpoint in the firms I&#39;ve worked at that we hire people that are less experienced and we train and<br /> develop them. And that obviously aligns easier when you&#39;re subscale, but that that&#39;s not to make the decision because of scale.<br /> That&#39;s just how the world I come from does things. I think, though, to a honest point, you have to be realistic about what the<br /> envelope of what you can spend is, what that looks like and what the talent you can get with that in line against that. So you have to be really kind of<br /> thoughtful about Tom Quinn earlier. What is what am I what do I want to do? What is my strategy look like? What is that business plan look like?<br /> What am I capable of of doing from a development in a mentoring and a leadership perspective? And then how does that work from an<br /> economic perspective, both in terms of day one, but also do a honest point. What does it look like over time? What is that economic trajectory look<br /> like with success? With success as you go and I think you want to be transparent with people around what day one looks like, what<br /> that can evolve to over time, and what are the parameters that that trigger that evolution. And I would say the other thing that&#39;s<br /> fundamentally different is that the analysts I would guess that all of our firms are probably doing you know, they&#39;re all being analyst with probably<br /> slightly different things, that the job is not the same at every firm. And I think that you want to be clear in terms of the way you&#39;re going to invest<br /> the types of things that the analysts will be expected to do. And that will there&#39;ll be some natural self selection of firms that individuals<br /> that that want to have that they think they can be more or less successful in different environments. And let me follow up.<br /> When you talk about hiring people and mentoring them and shaping them. Is it just analysts or is it traders and PMS and others within within the funds?<br /> I would say my general point of view is that it&#39;s it&#39;s pretty much true across<br /> the entirety of the firm that when I think about the firms that I&#39;ve worked with and work with in the past that have been successful and you look at the<br /> people that have been highly successful there. None of them were really senior hires coming in.<br /> They were they were hired pretty junior, and they were trained and developed with. Firms and in a lot of those firms, some<br /> of the biggest hiring mistakes they&#39;ve ever made were more senior than that. That&#39;s true for our process. That&#39;s not true for everyone else&#39;s<br /> process. And so I think that there&#39;s always been a natural pull towards you going younger and less experienced in training and<br /> developing those people. And that just makes it easier for me in the current environment because I&#39;m not competing against, you know, the type of<br /> people that a lot. But you&#39;re also not injecting a fully formed human, so to speak, in our business, into the ecosystem.<br /> And you don&#39;t use tissue is going to reject the organism. It almost certainly will on.<br /> One other thing now is as a new manager without much capital. Just bear in mind, LP P&#39;s are making a bet on you.<br /> Making a bet on you as a manager. Not on the bench yet. If you&#39;re launching with just a small amount of capital.<br /> Interesting point, Tom. You&#39;ve been doing this for a while. What&#39;s your experience been of competing for talent in either hiring or building<br /> at all? Yeah, it&#39;s it&#39;s really challenging. It&#39;s always the toughest part of the business, I think, while second raising<br /> the money. That&#39;s that&#39;s probably, you know, parting dollars from people. We have long lockups and a lot of it&#39;s<br /> really long. So that&#39;s that&#39;s always the longest process. But, you know, I think it&#39;s a you know,<br /> it&#39;s a unique challenge today because there&#39;s been a shift over the last 15<br /> years that we&#39;ve run night. We&#39;re a new generation of professionals are coming into the industry or have come into the industry that expect a lot<br /> more sooner. And I think this is you know, this is pretty common across, you know, a generation of folks that are, say, 25<br /> to late 30s, years old. And that&#39;s difficult because if you<br /> think about the last 15 years, we&#39;ve gone 15 years without a recession.真的吗？ And that means you really don&#39;t know<br /> what you&#39;re doing, because if you have. Yes, you invested in one year with a rate rise. OK, but you still haven&#39;t invested in a<br /> recession. So it&#39;s really hard to get people that have experience, that are relatively junior, that have a perspective of how<br /> bad things can be.正确的。 And we&#39;ve learned what happens with higher rates or we&#39;re beginning to learn<br /> what happens with higher rates, which not even I or people substantially more experienced than I am have contended with.<br /> It hasn&#39;t happened since the late 70s. And so, you know, we&#39;re seeing new things. Well, that means that if you have folks<br /> that haven&#39;t experienced those things, even if they can imagine them, it&#39;s different, actually experience them. And so managing people that haven&#39;t yet<br /> had the experience, the challenge, and for you as emerging managers, you need to do that in a way that controls risk and keeps people motivated.<br /> That&#39;s challenging, right? When they when they believe that they deserve more, they have a genuine view that they share more responsibility,<br /> more seniority, more economics. But they haven&#39;t yet been battle tested. That&#39;s a tough dynamic. And it&#39;s one that you really need to be<br /> very thoughtful about and how you manage. I would say don&#39;t cave to the pressure, you know, find the right people that<br /> understand that it&#39;s a process. They&#39;ve got to be committed to building the business alongside you or it&#39;s going to come crumbling in upon itself.<br /> I think the other thing that&#39;s notable that we&#39;ve seen recently is there&#39;s some really high cost structures in the hedge fund world.<br /> You know, 8 percent, the 8 percent fixed costs like that&#39;s insane, insane that<br /> that is not the way to start and run a business. If you&#39;re if you have your fixed costs meaningfully above your guaranteed fees<br /> and then you adjust for loss of capital.正确的。 If you can&#39;t build that cushion and you&#39;re at risk, like just look at<br /> yourself like a business, would you invest in that business because you&#39;re LP, you&#39;re going to look at it the same way and say, what happens if I allocate<br /> this business? Like I don&#39;t want to be like everybody running for the door. And if I&#39;m the, you know, the ant and<br /> the elephants behind me, it&#39;s not going to be a good day. So you have to think about the cost structure, which aligns with how you<br /> manage the people, which aligns with what type of people to hire. So it&#39;s a it&#39;s a multi variable analysis, which I&#39;m definitely not smart<br /> enough to solve. But it&#39;s you know, for me, it&#39;s a feel, you know, the types of folks that you can hire that you think will be a good<br /> fit. And I think it&#39;s incumbent on new managers to think about, OK, who. Who do I want to have effectively in the<br /> trenches with you? Because I think the reason a lot of firms fail in that first three to five year period is because they build<br /> themselves or they expect stratospheric growth. And the reality is it can be really lumpy.<br />正确的。 You just don&#39;t know. You are experienced a good one. We launched we thought we&#39;re going have tons of capital. We had last the market&#39;s fall off a<br /> cliff and I mean, like felt like really, really off a cliff. And no one. We didn&#39;t expect that.<br /> But we built the business to be able to withstand that. And then we grew. Really. Rapidly after that, because we set up for, you know what, if everything goes<br /> wrong. So I threw a lot into the mix there. But I think all of these things are important considerations when you&#39;re<br /> hiring. It can go great. You can build your huge success and have it. And that&#39;s fantastic. But the odds are that that won&#39;t happen.<br /> The markets won&#39;t give it to you. The personnel won&#39;t be there, know the capital won&#39;t come in the way you expect.<br /> So if you build a sense of conservatism, when you build a buffer around your business, you&#39;ll get to escape velocity. Really interesting.<br /> I&#39;m intrigued by anyone who&#39;s working for you who was born after before.<br /> If they were born after 1987, they&#39;ve never experienced a recession in their professional career. It&#39;s pretty, pretty, pretty amazing.<br /> So. So let&#39;s talk a little bit about you mentioned your piece. How do each of you differentiate<br /> yourself? What&#39;s your selling point when you&#39;re either trying to bring in capital or hire somebody or in any other way, make<br /> yourself differentiated from the masses that are out there? Let&#39;s start with you, Mike.当然。<br /> So. So our view is and was that the successful funds in the next decade are those that will be doubly built<br /> businesses. As Tom mentioned, you know, you have to think about this as a business. And those that can attract, retain and<br /> develop talent with a competitive advantage. And, you know, this past weekend, there was a Formula One race in Monaco.<br /> So I&#39;ll use that as an example, because a durable, successful hedge fund is a<br /> lot like an F1 racing team.正确的。 You have the racers, you have your investment team. That&#39;s the DNA of your business. But without a great car, you can&#39;t win<br /> races. And behind those cars, OK, you have<br /> mechanics, engineers, strategists, teams of people that are helping.<br /> And similarly, the hedge fund of today and for the next decade will be a hedge<br /> fund that has an infrastructure that can support their investment team, allow<br /> them to operate at peak performance, and then run the business of a fund. And that&#39;s a different job than what all of us here as investment managers do.<br /> That&#39;s not our expertise. So you have to have that infrastructure and those experts in-house to help you do that.<br /> And that I think that has been a big selling point for our LP was in the<br /> beginning. But also the talent that we bring in knowing that we&#39;ve built this to last. What I&#39;m hearing from you, Mike, is that<br /> generating alpha, that&#39;s table stakes. That&#39;s just what you need to sit down.<br /> Everything beyond that seems to be where you separate yourself from the crowd.<br />绝对地。 LP want to know that they can put capital in. They know it&#39;s going to be an illiquid<br /> investment and know that they are putting capital into a stable, durable business and that&#39;s what you have to provide them.<br /> When you launch, a lot of you have a unique perspective on differentiators<br /> and hedge funds. Tell us what you see from your vantage point. Well, people come in and they meet with<br /> us and they talk about what they&#39;re going to do. And I will tell you, having seen a gazillion presentations, investor<br /> materials, letters, it&#39;s great to have that stuff on.<br /> Done in a way which obviously you&#39;re gonna put time into it.<br /> You want to feel proud of it, but at the end of the day, my feeling is this industry is for the most part, very commodity.<br /> And the reason I went through the different strategies is to let you know<br /> that to the extent you&#39;re launching a strategy that has not performed well in<br /> the last couple of years, L PS are not going to give you the benefit of the doubt. It doesn&#39;t matter what your presentation<br /> materials look like. It just doesn&#39;t. You&#39;re going to have to put up performance. And the biggest piece of advice I can give you is maybe, you know, you can say<br /> you&#39;re differentiated all of this stuff. You&#39;ve got to start investing as quickly<br /> as possible. You bang the tin cup for capital for the first three to six months. You do what you can and then stop,<br /> literally stop. As counterintuitive as that sounds, what<br /> you want to do is start to prove and show some proof of concept, because unless you are coming from a fund that is a top multi manager or you&#39;re coming<br /> from on ie a great fund that is pedigreed and L PS want more of that<br /> DNA. Like I&#39;ll give you another example. Last year Broadwell launched. That was a fund started by Alex Carnell.<br /> A CAC came out of Deerfield and had a huge reputation in health care and he launched with over 3 billion dollars. So unless there&#39;s something that peace<br /> can seek sink their teeth into in terms of the DNA that you carry, you&#39;re going<br /> to have to show them what you can do. And then, yes, it becomes a question of how do you beg, borrow and steal to fund the enterprise while you&#39;re putting out<br /> performance so that you can then go back to LP is raise capital and also get that talent, because now this Field of Dreams has some skin on the bones.<br /> Brennan, what do you think? What what is the differentiator for you as a long only fund manager? I mean, I think the easy answer is that<br /> we&#39;re a long only had a manager that&#39;s doing concentrated hedge fund like investing and there&#39;s people that do that.<br /> So I would like but the field there is a lot smaller<br /> and the pools of capital allocated against long only there are pretty large as a lot of money can pass. There&#39;s a lot of money in long other<br /> long only strategies. So it&#39;s different than launching, you know, a higher fee product like a long shore product where you&#39;re competing<br /> against, you know, the likes of the world where they&#39;re making those tradeoffs. It&#39;s a little bit different.<br /> I would also echo the idea that my experience and not every allocator is the same allocators want to invest in what they perceive as institutional<br /> scale managers. It doesn&#39;t necessarily mean you need to have 30 employees, but they want to. They may want to look at as a real<br /> business. They want to understand the plan. They want to understand how you think about the growth of the business, the<br /> contingencies of the business, what your strategy is, how you&#39;re building the culture. Because to be perfectly frank, that I<br /> think that&#39;s the that&#39;s the easiest thing to kind of underwrite from an outside perspective. Always harder to underwrite stock pitches. I find it hard to underwrite stock<br /> pitches if I don&#39;t know the stock really, really well. And so I think you want to you want to invest in that part of the business.<br /> And what that investment looks like is going to be specific to your strategy.正确的？ It looks very different for a motel<br /> manager than it than it does for a smaller organization. But you can still get to that level of institutional scale as a smaller manager<br /> if you if you make it a priority and you&#39;re thoughtful around how that looks<br /> both day one and what your communication looks like for what it should be over time. Tom, what&#39;s your big differentiator?<br /> I don&#39;t think we really have one. No, I think I was a great quote pit bull<br /> that not picking know where random sports investments. Seth Klarman. I read a great quote by him.<br /> I think it two weeks ago and he said, we&#39;re fortunate to be unconstrained by a<br /> specific investment strategy from the group directly. That&#39;s so beautiful, right? Because what are you paying outposts<br /> for? You&#39;re paying them to go out and find great investments where there&#39;s downside protection.<br /> So the way that we present what we do is that we can invest anywhere in the world, really in anything but everything we do.<br /> We take a credit approach, too, which is we have an extreme focus on capital preservation and we try to structure for the best possible return.<br /> Sometimes it&#39;s an equity return or linked return or convertible or warrants so we can gain an equity return. But that&#39;s really the approach.<br /> So every investment that we pursue, we take that approach with the investment that we made in the in the football team in the UK was structured as a as a<br /> secured loan with, you know, the ability to eventually, you know, gain full<br />控制。 You know, a lot of the investing that we&#39;ve pursued. Has been structured in that way, and I<br /> think that&#39;s a differentiator because it&#39;s it&#39;s a little different than investing in somebody that&#39;s going to go trade high yield bonds or do public<br /> distrust. And I think the second thing is, at least from my core business, which we started as a distressed debt fund.<br /> The distress that funds just went off the rails. The last 15 years that the way that they operate is they they look at it a<br /> business as a carcass and then approach it to fight over the carcass.正确的。 We look at a business that might be a<br /> carcass and say, can we revive that thing?正确的。 Because if you can, the the pie that<br /> you&#39;re fighting over grows. And that&#39;s a lost art for a lot of investors in turnarounds like different many real turnaround experts anymore.<br /> And that is how you make tons of money, at least in my subsector.<br /> And so I think we&#39;ve done that pretty well. We&#39;ve invested in a few businesses the last few years where we had control that<br /> we&#39;ve turned around. Our biggest short going into the Covid was Hertz. It&#39;s now our largest long we&#39;ve ever had in the history of the firm and it was a turnaround play centered around<br /> electrification. So I think you&#39;ve got again, it goes back to, I said, the very beginning. You&#39;ve got to find what you&#39;re good at<br /> and what you love and then apply it to your strategy and do that. Like just do that. Forget all the noise.<br /> Just do what you love and what you&#39;re good at. And the rest of it should should be OK. And also having a structure that<br /> supports what you do is very advantageous. I mean, I don&#39;t want this to be lost on you. Of that, 10 billion or billion is in an insurance company.<br />是的。 And the up and you have one another for two and a half that&#39;s in drawdown, right?<br />当然。 So there&#39;s no timeline to returning capital. You some of our capital is literally insurance companies. Permanent, permanent.<br /> And then one of the drawdown funds the investor. It&#39;s really like uber wealthy family. When we draw the capital, we never have<br /> to give it back. Now, we don&#39;t get paid until we give it back. But we don&#39;t actually have to give it<br /> back in. Our fee is a sliding. Don&#39;t steal this, by the way, so we can really good idea. Took a long time to come up with this. The fee is a sliding scale based on the<br /> IRR. So there&#39;s this weird push pull because you know, sometimes you do a great investment. You compound at 40 or 35 or 30 for the first 18 months and then, you know,<br /> you&#39;re not going to continue compounding at that rate. You&#39;re probably going to slide to a lower level. Well, we have to decide, do we want to capture the higher incentive fee or we<br /> want to hold it and make a larger point. I always go for the larger, more.正确的。 But the worst thing you can do is try to<br /> live off of IRR. It&#39;s not possible you can&#39;t eat those make is what you want. So that duration of capital is hard, but<br /> the dumbest decision I ever made was pursuing long duration capital. We would be three times larger, four times larger if I had just built the<br /> Cielo business and listened to a lot of em like hired people to do right, do direct lending and do his all the things I tell you to do.<br /> No, but you were like you always had good ideas, like this is what your peers are doing. And you had very, very good advice over<br /> time that I listened to none of. And I&#39;m much poorer for it. Well, but friends at 10 million dollar fund.<br /> So there you go. No, but it&#39;s why I said you&#39;re going way back. I want permanent capital because I just<br /> said we have permanent capital. We can do whatever we want like we could by English soccer teams. Now, what I said we can do. We can make investments that really compound for a long period of time.<br /> And so we focused on doing that. Maybe it was a good decision that maybe it wasn&#39;t.时间会证明一切。<br /> But again, it went back to. That&#39;s what we love. That&#39;s what we wanted to do. But my point being, it&#39;s not just the<br /> strategy, it&#39;s also the structure. You get out for sure created a structure which is like I mean, it&#39;s almost a mini Apollo.<br />这是。 You created a structure where you just charge on Alpha Keys can get behind that. It may be long only, but you&#39;re just charging on Alpha and you&#39;re all alpha.<br /> So and you have all of the DNA from one of the greatest hedge funds in the world. You know, these are things that make<br /> each of these guys differentiated to your question and unique. And the reality is there are very few individuals that come to market with<br /> that skill set and that foresight. So so since I wrote us back that that&#39;s true. Since we brought up L P&#39;s and<br /> Allocators, I want to skip ahead to this question. What&#39;s what&#39;s the hardest question that you get asked by your limited partners<br /> or allocators? What&#39;s the most challenging question they throw at you will start with you again. Yeah, I think there are two hard questions.<br /> One is on the topic of exiting people and you know, that is mostly an<br /> objective decision, but there&#39;s a lot of subjectivity to it as well. And I think, you know, LAPD wanted to be objective and it&#39;s sometimes hard to<br /> explain. Explain some of the background to why we might keep somebody versus versus exit to them.<br /> I think the second question that they ask and we have a tough time with there&#39;s just on adapting any strategy that we have at, you know, LP is<br /> don&#39;t want you to adapt and change the business model that you promised and that and that. And I think that&#39;s. Completely fair. But there are times that are critical in<br /> a fund&#39;s life that you need to adapt or you&#39;ll die and sound money, too.例如。正确的。<br /> So, you know, whatever it may be, that that is a hard question to answer<br /> because, you know, most of the time what they want to hear is don&#39;t change your your path at all. You want to know why?<br /> I do want to. But I also want to comment on what Mike said.我愿意。这是真的。 But when you have however many years of<br /> putting up great performance and delivering exactly what you promised O PS, there is a higher receptivity I think to then whatever you see the pivot<br /> points as I&#39;ve seen this with other clients as well, that maybe started as one thing and as long as they didn&#39;t stray too far from their core DNA, I one<br /> client that is now 50 billion. He was 30 billion two years ago and he&#39;s done it through us thinking through quick other strategies and other<br /> products that are tangential but still related. And he&#39;s got credibility with his piece because of what he&#39;s delivered on<br /> turnover. OK, I just have to comment on this because, you know, like it&#39;s such a it&#39;s the bane of my existence.<br /> And I think it&#39;s one of the biggest problems in our industry. People are terrified, LPC are terrified to fire people, they think somehow it&#39;s<br /> going to reflect poorly on their ability to retain a team, their culture.<br /> Something bad&#39;s going on at the fund. You mean he&#39;s terrified of people?<br />是的。 But. But they&#39;re they&#39;re terrified.哦。 Oh, he&#39;s will think.对不起。 That&#39;s what I meant. Mm hmm.<br /> You have to be. You have to give people room to fail or to succeed, rather give them runway, give them tools, help them develop.<br /> But at a certain point, you need to graciously exit them. If they&#39;re not cutting it because the majority of you will not have a pass<br /> through model.好的。 I mean, that&#39;s just the truth. And you&#39;re gonna have a little problem called network, which is Peter over here.<br /> I&#39;m going to use just simple illustration. His ideas put up 100 hundred million of piano, piano.<br /> And Paul over here. Lost 100 million and you&#39;re zero. And what you don&#39;t want to do was Peter and Paul.<br /> You want to pay from you want to take from this guy to pay that guy. It&#39;s hard to take from this guy to pay that guy because you&#39;re going to end up<br /> losing your best people. And you also don&#39;t want your aides to feel like they&#39;re surrounded by a bunch of BS or worse yet, CS.<br /> So you need to manage people who are not cutting it and give them time to succeed. You need to manage them out.<br /> And don&#39;t worry about about your L PS because at the end of the day you&#39;re going to have a much bigger problem if your stars leave the door.<br /> They appreciate you cutting your losses. If I just want to manage talent the way you manage a portfolio, you. That&#39;s how you have to approach it.<br /> You have to be. You have to be rigorous. You have to be you know, you have to make tough decisions. You can&#39;t worry about anything else. This is the biggest problem.<br /> It&#39;s not just emerging managers, but in general that I see in our industry. And the best founders, OK, are the ones who do this really, really well.<br /> And sometimes, you know, people sort of they get a bad rap for it, but they&#39;re also the best at developing people and giving people the most runway.<br /> It&#39;s about creating an environment which attracts rock stars. On your question. Toughest question.<br /> One of the things you mentioned, Tom mentioned is I how you&#39;re going to pay<br /> for resources. So if you have a 2 percent management fee and you&#39;re in a 100 million dollar fund and you come from a fund, we&#39;re<br /> used to having tens of millions of dollars spent on research and software and data and corporate access. You have to answer the question to<br /> appease as to how you&#39;re going to fund that. You can&#39;t have you touched on this? You can&#39;t have 100 million dollar fund<br /> to meet a 2 percent management fee. And then one million dollars spent on<br /> fund expenses because that&#39;s a 3 percent drag on returns out of the gate. And it&#39;s even higher if you&#39;re if you&#39;re less.<br /> And the answer to that question really has to come back to how are you special?好的。 You don&#39;t need all these data sources.<br /> I&#39;m going to do X. I&#39;m going to do really well. And here&#39;s what I need. And be very precise about what you&#39;re<br /> bringing to the table and the resources you need to support that. The reality is you&#39;re not competing head on with these funds that spend tens of<br /> millions of dollars or even hundreds of millions of dollars on research. Brendan, what&#39;s the toughest question you get asked by potential employees?<br /> Let&#39;s say during the fundraising process, for me, the toughest is always what what your target that you&#39;re going to raise, to which my answer is I have<br /> no idea. You tell me.我们拭目以待。 I&#39;m going to launch it and we&#39;re gonna see what it is and it&#39;ll be what it is. Now, I would say that you&#39;re the hardest<br /> question. I always it&#39;s a little bit like last question. How do you how do you differentiate yourself versus other funds? Because I always inherent in that<br /> question is you have to know what that other fund is doing. And like I am a strong believer that unless you&#39;re in the walls and you&#39;re<br /> left, you understand exactly how the investment process works. It&#39;s really hard to compare yourself to another fund. And so I try to turn it back to this. Know, this is how we invest.<br /> This is how we do things. You compare that to the other people you kind of see in the market. But during the fundraising process,<br /> we&#39;re going to everyone in this room that&#39;s about to go through it. You know, the how what you what what what your target for raising.<br /> I always found somewhat amusing because I don&#39;t think anybody really knows until the last minute. Tom, how about you?<br /> I&#39;m looking for a doozy for it. I love the question. What do you see as the great opportunities over the next six months?<br /> You&#39;re literally like, really the answer to that question. I wouldn&#39;t need you as an LP to be retired, like managing my own money to<br /> someone else to be a manager in one office. I&#39;d be a professional fly fisherman, you know, like March know, 60, 20, 0 8.<br /> No one knew that. We&#39;re about to embark on the greatest run in distressed financials we&#39;ve ever seen.正确的。 September 10, 2001, no one knew there&#39;d<br /> be a huge opportunity in airlines. You know, just kind of go through history like you just don&#39;t know. So I think my answer to this question.<br />真的吗？ And playing off a little bit of the other comments is. Don&#39;t worry about what the LPC think.<br />好的。 Just say what you do, what you believe is right for generating returns. Because I&#39;ll tell you, particularly as a<br /> distressed investor. The fees are always wrong. Always like very, very rarely do we make a new investment and make people go,<br /> wow, that&#39;s great. Usually the like, oh, my God, really? Like, you really think that&#39;s a good investment?是的。 Like this.<br /> What&#39;s going to happen? Like, oh, my God, he&#39;s lost his mind. So I think you have to balance the fact that your the asset manager, you&#39;re the<br /> business builder. Just be honest.正确的。 And stick to your your strategy.<br /> But don&#39;t get swayed by what the crowd thinks. That&#39;s that&#39;s a surefire way to fail. Let&#39;s stay on that ends of the panel for<br /> this question. Tell us the biggest surprise or lesson learned over the years. What really sticks with you?<br /> I&#39;m still doing it now. I think the fact that I like it so much.是的。<br /> I came from you know, I was on a sell side trading floor with a thousand people. And it was sort of like, you know, very<br /> collegial. Lots of interpersonal reaction, interaction. Very loud, boisterous.<br /> I loved that and thrived in it. I know it&#39;s super surprising. And the you know, when you go to run your own firm and you start kicking,<br /> you&#39;re small. It&#39;s just totally different. And I wasn&#39;t sure that it would give me the same level of satisfaction that<br /> we&#39;ve that I get energized every day. It&#39;s been way better. You know, afros gone. I lost all my hair, which probably is a<br /> stress levels up, but it definitely has been a pleasure and far exceeding what I ever anticipated.<br /> Brendan, what&#39;s the biggest lesson or biggest surprise that you learned over the past few years? I think the biggest surprise and I think<br /> it&#39;s not intellectually a surprise, but it&#39;s a little bit like having kids. You don&#39;t really know what it&#39;s like until you&#39;ve got them.<br /> If you&#39;ve worked, if your background is working in other funds, working with other people, you have peers, you work with other people who appear as if<br /> something&#39;s going wrong. Complain to those peers when it&#39;s yours, it&#39;s you and the way you behave, the way you act and who you<br /> talk to in all matters because you&#39;re setting the culture of the entire organization. And that&#39;s you know, the thing Jim<br /> Parsons, who who I worked with before told me before I started with the highs are higher and lows are lower and you kind of feel it more internally<br /> in the ability to socialize it out is less there. And so it&#39;s one of those things. It&#39;s not obviously I&#39;d say that I think<br /> I run the room. But again, the. Of course it is. But until you go through it, you don&#39;t<br /> know what it&#39;s like. And again, highs or higher lows are lower. I think it nets out to being awesome.<br /> But prepare yourself for that and prepare yourself that it&#39;s different and how you behave matters. Alina, you&#39;ve seen you&#39;ve seen so much<br /> from your vantage point. Tell us, what would the biggest surprise was for you? Well, we&#39;ll save the biggest lesson for<br /> the last question. But now what what really was like, I just want to answer it this way. I mean, it nets out that it&#39;s awesome<br /> when you&#39;re successful. But the the common the most common thing I hear. I mean, I get this literally at least<br /> once a week from real managers. These aren&#39;t guys who couldn&#39;t cut it. These are guys who got to at least two, three, four hundred million.<br /> They had actually good returns even with the volatility of the last couple of<br /> years. And they are they&#39;re closing shop. And you just need to be aware of this or they&#39;re just not having fun anymore.<br /> You talked about having fun and loving it. You go into this business for you go into the idea of starting a fund.<br /> You&#39;re all emerging managers for two reasons. You believe in your strategy and you want to put it out into the<br /> world with your own imprimatur. And what you don&#39;t really realize or maybe you realize it, but yes, like the cabin having kids analogy, it&#39;s not<br /> until you&#39;re in the seat that it&#39;s really tangible. These two things, investor and entrepreneur.<br /> These two hats you need to wear are actually in conflict with each other and<br /> every moment you spend, particularly as a new manager, not investing and many of<br /> you will not be able to afford out of the gate the same infrastructure that these guys could see you&#39;re gonna get pulled into.<br /> Each are issues and legal issues and administration issues. And God, you&#39;re gonna be dealing with LP sometimes 100 percent of your time and<br /> you&#39;re going to be trying to put up great performance. And that&#39;s exhausting and it&#39;s sad, but there are many.<br /> I just have to tell the truth. There are many examples of individuals<br /> who got to a point where one might call them successful. They&#39;re running hundred million five hundred million.<br /> I have one guy who&#39;s running a billion and a half. His returns have suffered because of the distraction or they&#39;re just not having<br /> fun anymore because the thing that got them into this in the first place was a love of investing. And they find themselves actually<br /> focused on a whole host of other issues, which really are not how they want to spend their time. So if this is what you really want to do<br /> and it&#39;s an itch you want to scratch, you should go do it. But to the extent what you really want to do is have autonomy, invest, had<br /> scale out of the gate, have great resources and not that fast necessarily about all the rest of it. We should have that conversation.<br /> And if you do launch and you launch successfully, we&#39;ll have that conversation, too. Mike, what was the biggest lesson,<br /> biggest surprise to you? Yeah, you know, and Bear, you asked this question when I was on another panel with you a couple of years ago.<br /> An interesting article. Interestingly, it&#39;s the same answer. And, you know, this is a talent driven business.<br /> And what&#39;s been most surprising is the compounding effect of great talent. You always think about it in financial terms, but people who hire great people<br /> and keep the bar high, it&#39;s amazing what it does to your business. And so that&#39;s been the biggest surprise continues to be.<br /> So we&#39;re just about out of time. We don&#39;t have time for audience questions. But let me just throw one last question.<br /> Ten second response from each of you, and we&#39;ll start with Tom.<br /> One piece of advice for someone about to launch a new fund. Just as I said earlier, do you love surround yourself with people that you<br /> that you really want to work with and stay true to your initial objectives,<br /> one of which has to be to work as hard as you possibly can?正确的。 Yeah, I would. That kind of a corollary that I don&#39;t don&#39;t try to sell people on what you<br /> think that you want to hear. You have to come to market with a perspective. You have to have a strong point of view.<br /> And that either works or it doesn&#39;t. And that&#39;s the bet you have to kind of underlying make. But it won&#39;t work if you try to go if<br /> you try to shoehorn it into something that it&#39;s not. Alana, take your time. With respect to hiring people, build<br /> this on the right way. LP is would rather see a longer and slower ramp and off with respect to optimizing your investment team and your<br /> non investment team and performance. First, focus on putting up the numbers.<br /> Final word. Mike, what do you got? I have to say, in honor of the late Sam Zell who said this, go for greatness<br /> does it? Mike Rockefeller, ILana Weinstein, Tom Wagner, Brendan Diaz, thank you so much for your time and your insight and<br /> gratitude.谢谢。</p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/masters-in-business-the-emerging-manager-playbook/">Masters in Business: The Emerging Manager Playbook</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> Transcript: Ramit Sethi</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-ramit-sethi/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314561 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>﻿   The transcript from this week&#39;s, Ramit Sethi on Living Richly, is below. You can stream and download our full conversation, including any podcast extras, on Apple Podcasts, Bloomberg, Spotify, Stitcher, and YouTube. All of our earlier podcasts on your favorite pod hosts can be found here. ~~~ BARRY RITHOLTZ, HOST, MASTERS IN BUSINESS: This week…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-ramit-sethi/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-ramit-sethi/">Transcript: Ramit Sethi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ramit-sethi-on-financial-literacy-and-living-richly/id730188152?i=1000615473906" height="175" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"> <span data-mce-type="bookmark" style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" class="mce_SELRES_start">的</span></iframe></p><p></p><p>The transcript from this week&#39;s, <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/ramit-sethi" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>Ramit Sethi on Living Richly</em></a> , is below.</p><p> You can stream and download our full conversation, including any podcast extras, on <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2023-06-02/ramit-sethi-on-financial-literacy-and-living-richly-podcast" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5LGxKlY6fzXS3tGsjB23Cb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business/episode/ramit-sethi-on-financial-literacy-and-living-richly-304020349" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> , and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLe4PRejZgr0PzN7r8NikAnOqP70DHhoJ0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> . All of our earlier podcasts on your favorite pod hosts can be <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">found here</a> .</p><p style="text-align: center;"> ~~~</p><p> BARRY RITHOLTZ, HOST, MASTERS IN BUSINESS: This week on the podcast, what can I say? Ramit Sethi is a fascinating guy with really an amazing and fascinating career, starting out studying psychology and a little bit of finance at Stanford. He started a blog, which eventually became a podcast and a book, and is now a Netflix series. Depending on the platform, it&#39;s either “I Will Teach You to Be Rich,” the book, or the Netflix show “How to Get Rich.”</p><p> And it&#39;s not rich in terms of how to pile up money, but rather how to live a rich life by treating money as a tool to do the things that you want to do. That&#39;s one part financial freedom, one part prioritization of your life, and one part less stress and worries about financial matters. It&#39;s really a very thoughtful and intelligent approach to thinking about spending. And I found the conversation to be really interesting.</p><p> I&#39;ve chatted with Ramit before. I think he&#39;s really a fascinating guy, and I&#39;m glad we finally managed to get him in to the studio for a podcast. The show on Netflix is really quite interesting, and his just whole approach is intelligent and joyful and really very pleasant as opposed to the usual spending scolds who make money like a drudgery in a bore. He&#39;s not like that at all, which probably accounts for a lot of his success. He makes what is otherwise a potentially challenging subject very interesting.</p><p> I found this conversation to be delightful, and I think you will also.</p><p> So, with no further ado, my sit-down with Ramit Sethi teaching you how to live a rich life.</p><p> Ramit Sethi, Founder and CEO, I Will Teach You to Be Rich: Thanks for having me.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh, good seeing you again. Good to have you. So, before we get into the Netflix series and the book, let&#39;s talk a little bit about your background. You get a scholarship in high school, you put it in the stock market, and immediately lose half. How do you lose half of your money that quickly?</p><p> SETHI: Well, everybody thought they were a genius including me in 1999, 2000. Kind of sounds familiar to all of our crypto friends from the last few years. So, I was sitting there reading Industry Standard, remember that magazine?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Sure.</p><p> SETHI: And all these this media about how the stock market was going up 15 percent a week. So…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Forever.</p><p> SETHI: Trees grow to the sky.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> SETHI: Always, and so I said, cool, I&#39;m going to get in on this, and I took the first scholarship check which they sent to me, that&#39;s usually not how it works, they usually send it to the school.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: And you know, for a 17-year-old kid, that&#39;s a lot of money I put in the stock market, and I lost half of it within weeks. And in retrospect, that was probably one of the best lessons I ever got.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You know, if you step into a casino and the bells and lights go off and you win money, you&#39;re screwed the rest of your life.</p><p> SETHI: Cause you think you&#39;re a genius.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right, how hard is it?</p><p> SETHI: So, then I end up going to college. I had other scholarships that paid my way through, which was very fortunate. And I was learning about money, reading all the books, all the magazines, watching the shows, and I was also studying social psychology. So, I was studying human behavior, persuasion, and I was really, it reminded me of that book “The Emperor Has No Clothes” because the advice that we all get about money, for the last 30 plus years, makes no sense if you understand psychology. And that&#39;s when I started to develop my own philosophy.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And let&#39;s talk a little bit about that academic study. Stanford BA Information and Society with a minor in psychology, a master&#39;s in social psychology and interpersonal processes. It sounds like you knew exactly what you wanted to do from a fairly early period in your life.</p><p> SETHI: No, I&#39;m not so sure. I think, you remember that famous Steve Jobs commencement address?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: The speech, sure.</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Absolutely.</p><p> SETHI: That was my graduation.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Get out.</p><p> SETHI: Yes. So, he said, you often can&#39;t tell where you&#39;re going until you look backwards, and you connect the dots.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Makes sense.</p><p> SETHI: And I found that to be profoundly true for me when I was in college, I was super interested in why we do the things we do.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: For example, why do we all talk about, you know, I should probably go to the gym a little bit more, but we don&#39;t. I find that profoundly interesting because we sometimes will say it&#39;s about money, it&#39;s about time, but deep down there are deeper reasons and so being at Stanford and being able to study a science technology and society and psychology and sociology, that really allowed me to understand more of why we do what we do.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really, really interesting. I&#39;m trying to remember the date. I think it&#39;s January 19th is when the average New Year&#39;s resolution has been broken.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, there&#39;s some — you know it&#39;s interesting there&#39;s some nuance, I think, to New Year&#39;s resolutions, I used to be kind of like scornful. Ah, you know, the gym piles up and then it empties out. Now I think I&#39;ll take any opportunity where people are motivated to change. And if it is a 20-year high school reunion, if it&#39;s January 1st, doesn&#39;t matter.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Sure.</p><p> SETHI: Will most people flush out?大概。 But there&#39;s a few who will make it meaningful for them and commit to it. And for me that&#39;s a win.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, I&#39;m skipping ahead a little bit, but you write a lot about instead of focusing on goals focusing on processes, clearly psychology helps there too it&#39;s easy to make a small change in how you do things as opposed to this immense, hey I really want to be jacked for my 20th reunion.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, one of the most interesting emails I got from my newsletter subscribers was a woman who wrote me and said, you know, you talk about going for a run or going to the gym, and she goes, I have told myself that I want to go for a run five times a week for years, and I never do it, and I just wrote back to her and I said …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Go for a walk.</p><p> SETHI: … why don&#39;t you go once a week? And her response was so fascinating. She said, why would I do that, that will make no difference. I find that extremely fascinating, she would rather — yes, she would rather dream about going five times a week then actually go once a week, and so many of us do this with our money. We&#39;d rather dream about having 10 million then start investing $100 a week.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Perfect is the enemy of the good, isn&#39;t it?</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s really fascinating. So, you start the blog in 2004, more or less.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, while I&#39;m in college.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You were an early adopter, as was I. How did that evolve into a book?</p><p> SETHI: The blog was not some master genius stroke. It was my frustration because–</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Come on, tell the truth. You&#39;re like, I&#39;m going to blog for 20 years and then Netflix is going to come along.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, yes, yes, yes. Netflix, which didn&#39;t even exist.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: By then it was just DVD by mail.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, so okay, I was trying to teach my friends in college about personal finance. We&#39;d be sitting around the dining halls, someone would be complaining about their fourth overdraft fee, and I would go, hey, you should just come. I have this one-hour presentation I do on money. And they were like…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Wait, this is in college you would do this? No kidding.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, and so they would go, yes, that sounds really cool. And they would never show up.</p><p> Another fascinating peculiarity of human behavior, when it comes to money events, most people hate them because when they physically go they feel bad, and the older you get, the worse you feel, because you feel, I should have learned this earlier, my friends were 20 years old, and they already felt like they were behind imagine a 45, 55 year old at a 401k seminar, they don&#39;t want to go. So I did this for a year and a half nobody virtually nobody came like 10 people, and I finally said, I was a cocky college kid, I go, you know what the world needs to hear what I know. But they were certainly not listening. So, I started a blog.</p><p> I said, maybe these lazy college kids will read it from their dorm. And that actually turned out to be exactly right.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, was there ever an actual job out of Stanford or did the blog lead to?</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Tell us about your first gig.</p><p> SETHI: So, I had some internships in college and then when I graduated, I accepted an offer from Google actually. And they said, you should take some time. You know, you&#39;ve been in school for a long time.</p><p> I said, yes, I plan to. I&#39;ll be talking to you guys in three months. So, I took the summer off. One of my buddies said, “Hey, I&#39;m starting this thing. Why don&#39;t you start it with me?” So, I started this little collaboration company with my friend. We were co-founders. And it sort of blew up that summer. And I ended up saying to Google, “I really appreciate you guys, but I think I&#39;m going to stick with this.” And I was at that company, which was an online collaboration company, for several years, till about &#39;09.</p><p> Meanwhile, I was doing my blog on the side, and it was just getting bigger and bigger.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Whatever happened with the collab company?</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s still around, it&#39;s still around.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: There was no big exit, you didn&#39;t ring the bell and say?</p><p> SETHI: No, there was no exit, we were not here at Bloomberg. It was sort of earlier than Google Docs, and it was a Wiki, now it&#39;s sort of pivoted into B2B.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Kind of interesting, so you&#39;re working on the blog since &#39;04, somewhere along the lines there&#39;s a self-published eBook or something like that?</p><p> SETHI: Yes, around 06, 07 I said I want to see if anybody on the internet will actually pay for anything, I had not made a cent from the blog. It was just me doing it as a hobby. So, I created this eBook and I decided to sell it for $4.95 cents, and I was very terrified, it&#39;s like any artist who&#39;s ever sold something.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Sure. It&#39;s validation.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, and like what is the world going to think? I had such low confidence that I didn&#39;t even set up a distribution system I just said when the receipt comes in through PayPal, I&#39;ll manually attach it to an email because I thought 50 people would buy it, two interesting things happened first I was terrified of people calling me a sellout because back then to me selling something was sort of the antithesis of creating value and I actually did get called a sellout, I had people who had been reading me for free for years who turned and they said “Oh so it&#39;s I will teach Ramit to be rich.”</p><p> And that really hurt. When I think back to some of the most painful moments over a 20-year career, that is definitely one.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Because everything in the world is free. You should work for free. Media subscription should be free. Nobody should ever pay for anything.</p><p> SETHI: Correct. And if you do, you&#39;re trying to get one over me.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You&#39;re a sellout. I&#39;ll tell you something funny and people you know, we never quite had that accusation, but for the better part of 15 years before I started accepting capital, it was, “Hey, everybody&#39;s telling you how to manage your assets the wrong way. Here, you could do it yourself. Here&#39;s the right way to do it. You could do it. It takes a little discipline, a little time, and very little money. Manage it yourself.” And to my chagrin, people started saying, “Hey, I like the way you think, but I don&#39;t have time for this. You take my money.” “No, no, don&#39;t you understand? This is all about you can do it yourself.” “I&#39;m busy. You do it.” All right, and that&#39;s how a business was born, but I don&#39;t look at that as selling out. I don&#39;t look at what you did as selling out. $5 is not going to kill anybody.</p><p> SETHI: Exactly, and you know if they didn&#39;t like it I refunded them. That was what was fascinating.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Money-back guarantee on the, wow.</p><p> SETHI: And then the second thing that was fascinating to me was I had a small cadre of very loud vocal people who were angry. But…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: that&#39;s true on every website.</p><p> SETHI: Exactly, but the people who bought, I could see their statistics. Their open rates on my emails were quadruple the rate of everybody else. They email me saying, hey, this was great. When are you creating the next thing? I sat there looking at the data, looking at the emails, and I go, wait a minute. There&#39;s something qualitatively different about buyers and non-buyers. That led to the next three or four years of learning how to sell, how to create value, and not worry about selling out, but do it in a very ethical way. Do it my way.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And did the eBook eventually lead to “I Will Teach You to be Rich” the book?</p><p> SETHI: Yes, I think I became more comfortable. I think one of the biggest mistakes people make when thinking about writing a book is doing it too early. I waited until I had my philosophy dialed in. I treated my blog like an experimental lab. So, I tested it with different incomes, different industries, different geographies. By the time I wrote it, I knew what I was going to say.</p><p> And so that came out in March &#39;09, which actually happens to be the bottom. I&#39;m the bottom. But I remember going around, here we are in Manhattan, I remember going on book tour, and this book came out and a few months before my publishers had sort of sent me a note, are you sure that this information is still relevant because of what&#39;s going on? I go, good information has nothing to do with time. If anything, it&#39;s even more relevant because now low cost, long term investing makes sense, et cetera, et cetera.</p><p> So, I go on book tour to 13 cities and in every city, I&#39;m sitting in the green room waiting for a news director to come out and they go, we&#39;re not going to talk about investing today. I go, what? And they go, there&#39;s 10 percent unemployment. People just want to know how to get by. And I looked at them and I thought to myself, we&#39;ll talk about that. There&#39;s definitely some ways to save money.</p><p> But that also means the majority of people are employed and everybody knows that at some point the market will come back and they want to position themselves.</p><p> So, they just looked at me like I was an alien. I looked at them like, I don&#39;t really care what you say. I&#39;m going on air, I&#39;m going to say what I want. And I think that has been true since 2009 until now. Every time I do media, the predominant question is, times are tough, things are crazy, how do we get by?</p><p> And I go, I simply don&#39;t accept the premise anymore.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: I go, wait a minute, first of all, in certain areas, things are better than ever. Second, regardless of what we&#39;re talking about here, there are ways to get ahead and actually make money fun.</p><p> So, I&#39;m just not going to indulge the idea that money has to be purely a nuisance, purely an annoyance. No, let&#39;s start off by talking about how money can be amazing and joyful and create a rich life.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really love that. And I have to start out with a confession. When this book first came out, I hated the title.</p><p> (LAUGHTER)</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I thought it was just another get rich quick scheme, some sort of nonsense, and it was one of the guys I worked with that said, no, no, that&#39;s not what this book is about. You got to read it. So I started thumbing through it and I&#39;m like oh this is not about getting rich, this is about figuring out what money as a tool can do for you and how to use it properly, it&#39;s a very different headspace than most of the here&#39;s how to invest and get rich.</p><p> What led you to that sort of approach and that title?</p><p> SETHI: Well, I was sober when I chose that title, okay? I want to — I was a college kid, and I named my website I will teach you to be rich. I always have loved provocative names. I do love being ultra-clear about what I&#39;m going to promise. I have these digital programs. One of them is find your dream job. It&#39;s very clear what you&#39;re going to get.我喜欢。</p><p> But I will say that I&#39;m not offended by what you said because if you go and read it, there are people who talk about the book. I feel very fortunate that people spread the word a lot and they will almost always introduce it in the exact same way.</p><p> They&#39;ll go listen …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Ignore the title.</p><p> SETHI: They go, this book, it sounds like a scam, but “I Will Teach You to Be Rich” is actually really good and that&#39;s fine with me when you hear that title, I love a big promise, but what I love even more is over delivering on it.</p><p> So, it&#39;s not just about getting rich. It&#39;s actually about being rich, and being rich means not it means how to earn money, it means how to talk about money and even how to spend money all of those things including managing money are part of a rich life.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, let&#39;s delve deeper into the concept of a rich life. I love this quote. a rich life is lived outside the spreadsheet. explain that.</p><p> SETHI: Well, there&#39;s too many nerds probably half the people listening to this who love their spreadsheets, hey guys, do you want to do an amortization table? You want to do a Monte Carlo analysis? And they do that for 35 years tweaking numbers I go you won, you won the game. It&#39;s fine, turn the page on your life and go to the next chapter.</p><p> Once you have your asset allocation dialed in, your automatic contributions dialed in, all the basics, then you can move on. And part of that involves designing your rich life. Let&#39;s talk about that.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes, I really want to get into that because when we talk about the show, that really is a focus and you really kind of rocked some people back on their heels and make them address things they don&#39;t want to address. I&#39;m assuming that the blog and the podcast led to a lot of those interactions that ended up in the book.</p><p> SETHI: 100 percent. Yes, the blog gave me a lot of raw material because I had a chance to talk to people at different incomes, et cetera. You know, a rich life, most people expect a money book to start with a chapter on budgets. That&#39;s virtually every money book. And that is, in my opinion, a total turn off.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Buzzkill.</p><p> SETHI: Okay, some average person opens up a book. They&#39;re already feeling nervous judge. They open up the first chapter that author says, okay here&#39;s what we&#39;re going to do. We&#39;re going to get a budget. Everybody hates the word budget. I hate budgets myself. I don&#39;t keep one and now you&#39;re going to go through the last 12 months of spending which are not conveniently found anywhere, you know, you did it wrong, but I want you to go and spend the next 20 hours writing this stuff down just so you can be judged.</p><p> It&#39;s like, no thanks, I&#39;m going to put this right back on the shelf.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: So that is a lack of understanding psychology.</p><p> What I did with the book was to understand where do people want to start? Let&#39;s get them a quick win. Number one, everybody has credit cards, everybody misunderstands how to use them, and there are actually some secret perks that people have no idea about. Let&#39;s get you a quick win. You got a late fee? Read these words off the page. In fact, here&#39;s the phone number you call, and you will get your $37 fee waived. People do that, they don&#39;t believe it. And they do it, they go, oh my god it worked. And like that they realize they&#39;re on board, I can take control of my money, not let every financial company control me.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes, I was genuinely shocked and again the Netflix series is in my head. People have 18 credit cards, 20 — who has 20 bank accounts, it&#39;s you&#39;re just what you&#39;re paying in fees seems to be exorbitant.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, a lot of people who watched that show “How to Get Rich” on Netflix they told me like, I had no idea how little people know about money, but to me, I&#39;ve been talking to everyday people for the last 20 years, so it doesn&#39;t faze me to have 20 savings accounts to not know how much you&#39;re spending on fees.</p><p> Of course, you don&#39;t, that&#39;s like asking me, Ramit, do you have a carburetor in your car? I go, what the hell&#39;s a carburetor? I don&#39;t know, I turn the key it works, that&#39;s my understanding.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, let&#39;s talk about the money dial, where did the concept of that come and how do people actually use your money dial?</p><p> SETHI: When I talk about a rich life people like the term they go, rich life.那是什么？ So, you know first let&#39;s just start with that, a rich life can be traveling two months a year, a rich life can be wearing a beautiful cashmere coat, it could be picking up your kids from school every afternoon. Your rich life is yours.</p><p> And so, people they buy into that they go.哦哇。</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s not just materialism. It&#39;s not just shiny things. It sounds like it&#39;s choices and freedom and much less worry.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, but it&#39;s being very, very specific about it so freedom is when I ask people, what is your rich life? 90 percent of people say the same answer to me across the world. They go I want to do what I want when I want. They really think that they&#39;re clever.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: I go wow that&#39;s so interesting, I never heard that before.</p><p> (LAUGHTER)</p><p> SETHI: And then I go so what do you want, and they just stare at me because that is how far most of us have thought. And they&#39;ll say something like travel. I go, okay, where? They go, Europe. I go, where? I want to know what airline seat you&#39;re going to sit in, I want to know where you&#39;re going to stay, what you&#39;re going to eat, I want to know who&#39;s going with you for how long, that&#39;s a vivid and specific vision of a rich life.</p><p> So, an easy way to do this for everybody listening is let&#39;s do this quick exercise together. The first question I have for you, Barry, is what do you love spending money on?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Dining, entertainment, things like that.</p><p> SETHI: Fantastic. Dining is actually the number one response money dial, or it&#39;s what I call a money dial.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really?</p><p> SETHI: Yes, number one is eating out or dining. Number two is travel. Number three is health and wellness. Number four is my money dial, convenience. And then there&#39;s a variety of others.</p><p> So, the second question is, Barry, if you could quadruple the amount you spend on dining, what would it look and feel like for you?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That would be a terrifying number.</p><p> SETHI: Tell me.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, my wife and I also really like cooking, so we cook at home, we just redid a kitchen, we have this lovely chef&#39;s kitchen. So, I try and balance having fun and playing some music, cracking a bottle of wine and working on a recipe. That&#39;s a lot of fun. As is, you know, we just had an insane lunch at the Restoration Hardware.</p><p> SETHI: I love that place.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Just exorbitant. But, you know, as an occasion, I&#39;m like, don&#39;t even think about it. Just let&#39;s order what we want and not even think twice.</p><p> SETHI: So, you are in an unusual position because you, I&#39;m guessing, you&#39;re not really price sensitive about eating out.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, you and I have previously discussed pain points in spending. Like for me it&#39;s clothes because everything is an expensive bib eventually.</p><p> (LAUGHTER)</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And look I&#39;m wearing nice pants.</p><p> SETHI: I told Barry, my wife&#39;s a personal stylist, I said Barry let&#39;s do this.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> I mean I&#39;m wearing nice clothes today, but I can rationalize dropping a couple hundred bucks on a meal without even thinking twice about it. But you walk into certain stores, 800 bucks for a pair of shoes, 400 bucks for a shirt, it&#39;s a little more challenging because I&#39;m hard on everything. I know that the shirt will eventually have spaghetti stains on it and the sneakers the shoes will be destroyed, but that&#39;s my pain point.</p><p> SETHI: Okay.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s not cars. It&#39;s not watches. It&#39;s not food.</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s clothes.</p><p> SETHI: So, people listening, they&#39;re saying okay I eat I like to eat out or I like to travel and the second question when I ask, what would it look like if you could quadruple your spending? People smile because they go, wow, they never thought of it, most people when it comes to food. They give me the same answer, they go, wow, I probably have to watch what I eat because I&#39;d be eating up four times a week and I go…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s not bigger portions. It&#39;s going to nicer places.</p><p> SETHI: That&#39;s right. So, most of us think linearly, I go, what? Are you going to go to Chipotle four times a week?</p><p> (LAUGHTER)</p><p> SETHI: Might you go to a different caliber?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: And this is where it becomes really fascinating, a rich life is not simply more frequency, a money dial turned all the way up could be eating at a beautiful Michelin-starred restaurant for lunch, it could be going — if you turn it all the way up, you might go to Italy with your loved one, go to a farmers&#39; market with a chef and make the food together.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That sounds like fun.</p><p> SETHI: So, the point of a money dial and the point of a rich life is to really get specific about What it would look like to turn it up then you will understand what I mean when I say I want you to spend extravagantly on the things you love as long as you cut costs mercilessly on the things you don&#39;t.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And that&#39;s a really fascinating aspect to your writings and to the show because People seem to be somewhat agnostic about their spending habits regardless of whether it&#39;s important or not.</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And you know if you get — if you could get people to focus on oh, you want this big expensive trip or this nice car or whatever it happens to be, well to get there you just have to stop throwing money away on junk, you&#39;re about halfway there.</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: What&#39;s the pushback to that from clients? From people?</p><p> SETHI: Most people have simply been taught that they should cut back a little bit on everything. What a demoralizing philosophy Oh, I should cut back 5 percent on asparagus 5 percent on my car 5 percent on rent 5 percent on cable, it&#39;s like that is so ineffective, that&#39;s why there are so many folks out there who berate people about buying a…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: A spending scold.</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: if you&#39;re one latte away from your retirement being messed up you got bigger …</p><p> SETHI: Bigger problems.</p><p> And truthfully a coffee a day is not going to change your financial life in any material way but there are certain five or ten big things that make a huge difference so what I encourage you …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Let&#39;s go through those.</p><p> SETHI: All right, what I tell people is stop asking three-dollar questions, start asking $30,000 questions, those would be am I automating my savings and investments? Have I made rules for myself such that if I&#39;m saving 5 percent this year, I&#39;m going to increase it by 1 percent per year, that right there if you do that for your savings and investment is worth hundreds of thousands of dollars more than all the coffee you&#39;ll ever buy. Am I paid well? Have I learned the skills of negotiating my salary? Have I managed my asset allocation and my investment fees?</p><p> If you do these few things, you&#39;ll be light years ahead of agonizing over the price of broccoli.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right. It&#39;s whenever I read the spending scolds, they always have half the story. Never buy a sports car, never buy a sailboat, never buy a…</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s always no, no, no.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: But the right way to say that is never buy a sports car if you can&#39;t afford a sports car.</p><p> SETHI: Correct.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: But if you can afford it, go buy whatever the hell you want. And that focusing on the spending but ignoring the hey, is this a rational expenditure for someone who is earning enough to pay for that vacation, that house, that car, why not?</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s a very simple puritanical view that people in personal finance espouse, which is it&#39;s really easy to tell people no to everything. A blanket no, but it&#39;s much harder.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s lazy.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, it&#39;s intellectually lazy, but I think it&#39;s much more fascinating and nuanced to show people you can actually spend more on the things you love. For example, I just posted a picture of my car. I&#39;m not into cars, not at this phase of life, and I know you are super into it, so this is interesting. I posted my car, it&#39;s an old, of course it&#39;s a Honda Accord, all right?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s a very reasonable —</p><p> RITHOLTZ: We had a Honda Accord Cross Tour, probably the best car I&#39;ve ever had.</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s fantastic.</p><p> So, I could go buy any car, but to me, it&#39;s great. I hardly drive, I have it, it&#39;s fine. One day, I&#39;m sure I&#39;ll get a much nicer car. And so, I posted this just to show people, look, this isn&#39;t my thing, it&#39;s where I cut costs mercilessly but when I travel, I love hotels, I love clothes those are the things that are important to me and so I want people to actually have this highly dichotomous way of spending, you spend extravagantly on certain things…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: A barbell.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, a barbell and then you cut costs mercilessly on the things you don&#39;t.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I really like that concept. So, speaking of staying within your spending limits, if you&#39;re making 70 grand a year, maybe a $4,000 handbag isn&#39;t the best use of your money.</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s very likely although if they tell me, hey I pay 18 percent of gross for my rent. I would go, cool, what are you doing with the rest? They go, I love a bag. I go, how long is it going to take you to save? They go, I know my numbers, 14 months. Fantastic, but I will say you know we want to be reasonable the fact of the matter is 90 plus percent of people do not know their basic numbers.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: What are your thoughts on the early retirement fire movement?</p><p> SETHI: I like any movement that gets Americans to think about increasing their savings rate. I love that. I love a movement that gets people to be goal oriented. I love that.</p><p> However, it quickly crosses over into obsession over pure metrics and truthfully accumulating money is never the goal. That is living in the spreadsheet.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I&#39;m glad, I&#39;m glad you said that, I remember reading a blog post by someone who was in that space, and they were stressing because they had a houseguest who was taking a long hot shower.</p><p> SETHI: Come on.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I swear this is true, and the long hot shower was going to be expensive and it&#39;s like again if a hot shower, the cost of that is too much, what are you going to do when you&#39;re old if you&#39;re retired in your prime living earning spending years, it just makes no sense.</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s — that&#39;s when you&#39;ve gone too far, imagine you have a pair of eyeglasses. The primary money lens that we use in this country is cost we go to the store. We look at the cost.我得到它。</p><p> RITHOLTZ: The wrong measure.</p><p> SETHI: There are so many other lenses, so for something like black pepper, which I don&#39;t really care about I&#39;ll use cost fine, but for other things like a pair of shoes which I am going to keep for seven years or taking my parents out to a really nice restaurant, I&#39;m going to use different lenses, so there are lenses like security and safety, delight, results. That&#39;s why somebody might hire a personal trainer instead of doing it on YouTube. Even just luxury. So, what I want is for people like a symphony, you got to be able to have different instruments, not only the instrument of cost. And that&#39;s where I think people go wrong.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really, really fascinating.</p><p> I&#39;ve always thought of you as like a financial advisor, but on the show, It&#39;s almost like you&#39;re a therapist/counselor. Each of these vignettes are like interventions.</p><p> (LAUGHTER)</p><p> RITHOLTZ: How do you think of this? Am I mis-describing you? How do you think of your own work? What&#39;s your job title?</p><p> SETHI: Well, you can call me what you want. I mean, I get judged by the results of the people I work with, which I love. I think that money is so much more than just what&#39;s on the page. And ultimately, through the show and through my podcast, I&#39;ve become much more interested in the interpersonal dynamics. Couples, even individuals, they know that they should probably save more. They know that they should probably pay off debt. Why aren&#39;t they? And that to me is where we begin to peel the onion.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s more counseling than it is financial advice. And on the show, I&#39;ve seen some themes come up over and over again. So first, none of these people, they don&#39;t track their spending, there&#39;s no budget, there&#39;s not even the mental buckets of, I&#39;m going to spend this much on entertainment and this much on rent. It just is a fire hose coming in and a fire hose going out.</p><p> SETHI: That&#39;s very astute. I think that the way most people think about money is purely reactive and purely transactional. So, it goes like this. Our printer broke down. Let&#39;s buy a new printer. Our kids need soccer cleats. Let&#39;s go buy soccer cleats. Oh my gosh, we got our credit card bill. I guess we spent that much on sprinklers at Home Depot. That&#39;s basically the next 40 years of life and that&#39;s true.这是真的。 And so, I have a lot of compassion because we&#39;ve all done that in some way. It could be fitness. It could be relationships It could be anything.</p><p> You and I understand that you should probably have certain mental buckets and you should probably go on offense instead of defense and we get that after you understand this stuff, it&#39;s not that hard. If you don&#39;t even know, for example, how to decide if you can afford your car, then that is really where we&#39;re starting.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Or your house people were living in houses with HOA fees and repair costs that they seemingly never thought of.</p><p> SETHI: Well, this is the number one thing You know when I when I talk to folks the number one and number two area, they overspend on number one is their house because they have no sense of, they don&#39;t even know that 28 percent rule, they don&#39;t know 28 36. That&#39;s very technical and the second area they overspend on is their car. Now why, what is in common with both of those? First, they&#39;ve gotten more expensive recently yes, but two, there are gigantic phantom costs with each of those.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: When I show people for example that if you take a mortgage, you might as well just add on 50 percent to that mortgage to account for taxes, interest, maintenance, opportunity costs they are shocked they can&#39;t believe it. In fact, when I go further and tell them that it&#39;s actually been a better decision for me to rent than to own, It&#39;s like somebody&#39;s telling them the sky is green.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Well, the American dream has been you know, you find your little place, you buy it you own it. No one could raise your rent. You can paint the walls any color.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, and you&#39;re not throwing money away on rent, funny you never say that when you go out to a restaurant, you&#39;re throwing money away in a restaurant and then they go, oh, you&#39;re paying your landlord&#39;s mortgage. I go, are you concerned about paying your sushi restaurant owner&#39;s mortgage? No, it&#39;s a bunch of almost religious aphorisms, they lack any substance and so we simply meaninglessly repeat these phrases. I don&#39;t want to throw rent away. Easier than teaching opportunity cost and doing a buy versus rent calculation.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, let&#39;s talk about a couple of other things on the show that I was fascinated by.</p><p> Reckless spending is kind of a theme. We mentioned the $4,000 handbag for somebody who really…</p><p> SETHI: Who could not afford it.正确的？</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Or the guy who was spending hundreds and hundreds of dollars each month on video games. I mean one video game should keep you busy for a month not dozens, that was sort of a …</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: An obsession.</p><p> SETHI: So that that&#39;s really interesting, when I heard that, I really want everyone watching “How to Get Rich” to notice my reaction. When people — first of all, it is extremely intimate for people to admit all their financials to anyone, and I had all of their financials.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I saw this — by the way you walk through, here&#39;s their credit card spending, here&#39;s what&#39;s in their savings account, one of the people who&#39;s spending a ton of money literally had five dollars and change in their savings account.</p><p> SETHI: Until now you&#39;ve never been able to actually see inside people&#39;s …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s pretty horrifying.</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s fascinating to me. It&#39;s like a microscope You know, they see a spreadsheet to me when I look at someone&#39;s money, I see a family trip to Disneyland or I see a beautiful outfit or I see early retirement, and that&#39;s what I wanted to shift into.</p><p> So, when people invite me into their homes and they open up their finances to me. They are very brittle, they&#39;re expecting me to come down like a pile of bricks and say you&#39;re doing it all wrong and a lot of times I just go, that&#39;s really interesting. Why&#39;d you do that? What do you love about video games, and you can see them visibly loosen up.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You&#39;re very genteel with these people, there&#39;s no finger wagging, there&#39;s no scolding, and you very gently nudge them to that you give them I forgot which woman it was, Maybe it was the gymnast, you gave her three choices choice a, do nothing.</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Choice B, do something little.</p><p> Choice C, do something large. And nobody wants to do nothing.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, well …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: They have agency they&#39;re saying well, I&#39;m not going to do A, so now it&#39;s their decision.</p><p> SETHI: Correct? So, there&#39;s a lot of psychology into play.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> SETHI: And if you&#39;re listening and for example, you&#39;ve had a spouse maybe who&#39;s just seemingly not interested in money or your kids or anyone around you where you&#39;re or you can even bring yourself sometimes to figure out how to spend money more meaningfully, a lot of us think that the solution is found in a spreadsheet and it&#39;s not.</p><p> For every single person on the show and on my podcast, there is something much deeper going on and it&#39;s easy. In fact, it&#39;s lazy to throw a bunch of numbers, here&#39;s a compound interest chart. That&#39;s not going to change anybody&#39;s life.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: We&#39;ve all seen it; we all know what it says. But to understand, for example, what did your parents say around the dinner table? And you will always hear people repeating phrases like, we can&#39;t afford it, money doesn&#39;t grow on trees. Now imagine hearing that 10,000 times growing up.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You left the door open again, must I pay to heat Eva Lane?</p><p> SETHI: Exactly.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I heard that growing up constantly.</p><p> SETHI: Bingo. And so, a lot of the folks, whether it be on the show or on my podcast, they&#39;ll do very well. They may get a great job, accumulate money, and they can afford any lunch, they can afford a trip, but some of them agonize over it.为什么？</p><p> They think, oh, I&#39;m bad, I feel guilty buying this business class trip, but really it often traces back to what they heard from their parents.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. Let&#39;s talk about married couples that don&#39;t have a joint checking account. Two different couples with, that&#39;s unfathomable.</p><p> SETHI: Really? That surprises you?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Shocking, shocking. Because I remember when I first got married, I&#39;m married 30 years already, we had separate checking accounts and my wife is like, why do you need to hide your money from me?</p><p> I&#39;m not hiding, first of all, she was making more than me and second, I&#39;m not hiding, I have this account, you have that account, we merged everything and never looked back.</p><p> By the way, she takes care of the bills because when we were younger, when the lights went out, that&#39;s how I knew it was time to pay the electric bill.</p><p> (LAUGHTER)</p><p> SETHI: First of all, congratulations on 30 years, that&#39;s amazing. That&#39;s the ultimate part of a rich life. I&#39;m not surprised that so many couples don&#39;t have joint accounts, but I&#39;ll tell you something that might surprise you. I actually don&#39;t have a problem if couples have separate accounts, here&#39;s what&#39;s really going on the people that get into financial trouble in relationships tend to have separate accounts, but it&#39;s not the separate accounts that cause the problem, it&#39;s the fact that they simply slid into this relationship as individuals and never sat down and discussed, how do we want our money to go?</p><p> So, if they sit down and they go, you know what? I think we prefer to have separate accounts. We can combine as necessary. I say fantastic, but most people with separate accounts never had that conversation and that is the plan.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s not just the separate accounts, It&#39;s the separate spending and separate priorities where how are we going to save if you&#39;re buying X or Y or Z?</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: We&#39;ll never get out of debt. We&#39;ll never buy that house, which was one of the couples&#39; motivation.</p><p> SETHI: This is very common.</p><p> So, you know, on the podcast, I only speak to couples. And you&#39;ll get these patterns. One is an over spender; one is an under spender. I had a particularly fascinating couple; I think it was around episode 20. He wrote me in all caps, he said, Ramit, please help. My wife of 21 years is about to divorce me because I&#39;m too cheap.</p><p> I was like, click, so I immediately click and respond to him. I brought him on the show with his wife. I had reviewed all their finances and she was angry, in fact almost checked out. And she said, I don&#39;t understand why after 20 years of marriage, he doesn&#39;t trust me, our yard is the only unlandscaped yard. She said, he asked me to find mattresses for our two girls, I spent a week creating a spreadsheet. And he said, that&#39;s too expensive, the mattresses were something like 500 bucks. Their net worth, Barry, can you guess?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Five million dollars.</p><p> SETHI: It was around 13 million dollars.</p><p> And so, when you hear that —</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, 500 bucks for a mattress is just irrelevant.</p><p> SETHI: It&#39;s meaningless. It would be easy to simply say, this guy&#39;s nuts, why don&#39;t you loosen up?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: He&#39;s got issues for sure.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, and that&#39;s where I start. That&#39;s where I go, let&#39;s talk about it. Non-judgmentally, but let&#39;s talk about what&#39;s going on. Remember, she was about to divorce him. And so, you can listen to the episode, episode 20, and you can hear how that conversation evolves. It&#39;s much deeper than math.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, this raises a really interesting question, people reveal very embarrassing challenging financial habits, how did you get these folks to come clean on them?</p><p> SETHI: On the show…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> SETHI: We have casting so casting went out and found particularly interesting situations and I gave a lot of guidance as to what type of people are especially interesting, on my podcast that was the hardest thing of all is to get people to open up all of their financials.</p><p> Not only have we been able to do that, now we have them on video just like on the show. That&#39;s very intimate. I&#39;m not sure I would go on a show like that.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: What I&#39;ve learned about the psychology of people appearing on this is you have to understand that most people feel truly lost when it comes to money. They don&#39;t know who to trust. They don&#39;t even know the difference between the word financial advisor and 401k like those two, they&#39;re in different universes to us but to somebody walking on the street, those words are all jumbled up into the personal finance or confusing money cloud, and so when they hear somebody who comes and says like, hey, I&#39;m not going to judge you if you like a purse, I&#39;m not going to judge you if you like to eat out, fine, I like a couple nice things myself, that&#39;s cool, let&#39;s talk about what your rich life is and how we can use your money to get there.</p><p> They are willing to open up anything if they know that they can trust me.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really intriguing. So, let&#39;s — we were talking earlier about budgeting and you know credit scores and things like that.</p><p> Let&#39;s talk a little bit about people who have more money than they know what to do with because they&#39;ve spent their whole life working and saving and investing and suddenly, they have a hard time pivoting to, hey I could take that trip, I could buy that sailboat, I could do what I want. what sort of advice do you give to these folks to allow them to be more comfortable to make that transition?</p><p> SETHI: This is my favorite topic, Barry, because nobody really talks about it and it&#39;s very politically incorrect.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: We talk about this in the office all the time it comes up constantly partly because we have a lot of wealthy clients, but also partly because we&#39;re big believers in as you suggest, you have to use money as a tool to live your richest life, what advice do you give these folks?</p><p> SETHI: One way to think about it is you really have your prime spending years between the ages of 40 to 60, so think about that before 40 most people don&#39;t really have money after 60 there may be health issues whether it be with yourself or somebody in your family that you have to take care of, whatever, things happen.</p><p> So, if you accept the idea that your prime spending years are between 40 to 60, what does that mean for you? And suddenly, traveling to certain places becomes an urgency. Eating at a certain restaurant you&#39;ve always wanted to becomes an urgency. This requires a change. One, the idea of shifting from accumulation to de-accumulation is really hard. That&#39;s why, you know, when people retire, they start freaking out because they&#39;re not getting the income even though the interest pays more than they would have ever made.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right, they&#39;re not getting the income and they have a lot more hours in the day to go out and spend money.</p><p> SETHI: Exactly. The second thing is people often make this jump they go, well, if I go eat at that restaurant, I don&#39;t want to have to become that rich guy who&#39;s eating there. I go, you think you&#39;re going to trip and fall and eat at a Michelin starred restaurant every single night? It&#39;s like, get real, I trust myself enough to know that I can drive a car twice and not have to buy ten of them. I trust myself enough to know Barry&#39;s going, well, I don&#39;t know about that. He goes, have you been in my Porsche?</p><p> (LAUGHTER)</p><p> SETHI: Okay, maybe not. I trust myself enough to know that I can eat at a nice restaurant for an anniversary and say wow I really love that or that wasn&#39;t my thing, but it was cool and not have to do it every night.</p><p> Many of us have simply never built the skill and it is a skill of spending money, so we&#39;ve earned it, we&#39;ve managed it, but we never actually built a skill of spending it meaningfully and that&#39;s why we have to start almost like we&#39;re building a new muscle.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: How do you address the guilt that some people feel when they say I&#39;m spending my kids&#39; inheritance?</p><p> SETHI: I don&#39;t — first of all, it&#39;s lazy for people when I ask them, what&#39;s your rich life? They go, you know what? I&#39;m so simple. I&#39;m just a simple person. I really want to just provide for my kids.</p><p> I go, that sucks, that&#39;s a boring answer, and that&#39;s intellectually lazy.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: (LAUGHTER)</p><p> SETHI: So you worked your entire life. Oh and you never modeled building good spending habits.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: You literally accumulated it like Scrooge McDuck and you&#39;re handing it over to your kids without any modeling? No, that&#39;s actually unacceptable to me. I told my parents, my parents had very modest incomes growing up and we told my mom and dad I sat down with them because they were nervous about spending money because they had gone through the same thing.</p><p> And I said, let&#39;s look at the numbers I mean it very simple for them and I said, mom and dad, what are you going to do with this money if you don&#39;t start spending it? And they&#39;d never really thought about they go, we&#39;ll give it to the kids. I go, we don&#39;t want one cent, you taught us how to be educated you taught us good values, we want you to spend every last cent and maybe even more. And so, I put them on a travel budget, and I said you have to spend this much every single month, in fact they&#39;re abroad right now, which I&#39;m so happy about.</p><p> The guilt of not leaving money for your kids really is a deeply emotional response. You want to leave them money? Please do, leave them some, but more importantly leave them a model of your spending money on the things that matter to you.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Do you get the kids involved? Do you get the whole family involved when you&#39;re talking with a wealthy family that&#39;s having some issues with figuring out how to live their rich life?</p><p> SETHI: The first thing I do is work with the parents. Parents are obsessed with the question about should I give them an allowance? Should I not?</p><p> I go, listen, that&#39;s like someone saying I want to meet the person of my dreams. What kind of shoelaces should I wear? I go it&#39;s irrelevant, an allowance is not the primary issue. What I ask him is how do you talk about money at home, and they go, we don&#39;t talk about it. I go, why not? They go, because our parents never talked about it. I go, okay, we&#39;re going to start talking about it.</p><p> Second, do you ever get excited about it? Most people have never conceived that they can get excited about money, they see it as something negative something to protect their children from and so I suggest some gentle things, if their kid is very young. I say you know bring them over on your lap and say, you know mommy&#39;s going to log into the credit card, this is what allows us to buy the food that we eat can you help me push the button and then as they get older, empower them to make decisions about a vacation or a dinner out.</p><p> It&#39;s not about an allowance, you can give them an allowance or not that&#39;s not the point, the point is to model healthy relationship with money.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s really, really interesting, we in the office we set up so we&#39;ve had a robo advisor internally for six seven years already and we advise parents to set up small accounts for their kids, so they start investing at eight, twelve …</p><p> SETHI: Love it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Fourteen years old, it doesn&#39;t have to be a lot of money but they get to watch it grow.</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And it&#39;s really like oh this is something that I could continue to do on my own.</p><p> SETHI: And they talk about it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> SETHI: I had another fascinating couple they&#39;d been dating for a year, they&#39;re in their late 30s he had started a business and he was paying himself $2,000 a month. She was making $200,000 per month.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: A month?</p><p> SETHI: She was making 100 times what he makes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, she&#39;s making $2.5 million. That&#39;s a nice income.</p><p> SETHI: Very nice in her late 30s. She had more money than she would ever need and they struggled. The reason they came to me was it was about who&#39;s going to pay the check for dinner. So, believe it or not, this is a real deal. So, I took the call and what became very clear was I asked her, when did you first learn about investing? And you know what she said, Barry? She said, age five. Her parents started talking about compound interest. Age five, which is what wealthy families tend to do. Then I asked him, when did you learn about investing? He goes, I started reading your book about two weeks ago.</p><p> So, imagine a guy who has a 30-year deficit on learning about a concept as important as compound interest. We can&#39;t expect everybody to have the same knowledge. We all start at different parts in life. For me, physical fitness, I wish I learned how to deadlift when I was 16, I didn&#39;t. But if you can give your kids an advantage, and certainly your partner, it is to talk about money regularly and positively.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, before we get to our favorite questions, a quick curve ball question. Got to ask, how did the Netflix deal come about? Did they reach out to you? Did you reach out to them? Was there a third-party intermediary? How do you suddenly get a Netflix series?</p><p> SETHI: They reached out to me. I remember where I was, they emailed me and it said, would you be interested in sitting down for a meeting and also should we communicate through you, or do you have representation?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: Two things happened to me. First off, I didn&#39;t believe it was from them so I went up to the “from” and it said “@netflix.com.” I was like, wait a second.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh, you can fake that though, that&#39;s easy enough.</p><p> SETHI: So, I was like, this is crazy.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: If you hit reply, that&#39;s when you know it&#39;s real.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, that&#39;s a good tip. Well, I&#39;m glad it worked out. The second thing that occurred to me was, I don&#39;t even know what they meant by representation. I&#39;m not a Hollywood guy.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: I&#39;ve been running my business for 20 years on the internet.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You&#39;re New York based, right?</p><p> SETHI: Yes, and then LA now.</p><p> But I didn&#39;t even know, so I had to learn, how do you find an entertainment lawyer? I literally went on Google and searched entertainment lawyer, and I had to learn the entire business, which I&#39;m just, just, just starting to grasp. It was a totally fascinating journey and they had been wanting to do a money show. In fact, every network has been wanting to…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> SETHI: But money&#39;s really hard on TV. It&#39;s boring, it&#39;s often very depressing. And so, I told them point blank, I said, “Look, I&#39;m interested, but I want to do it my way. “I do not want to berate some couple, for how much they spend on Reese&#39;s Pieces cups. And they said, no, no, no, we want you to do it your way. They gave me broad creative control.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s great.</p><p> SETHI: I&#39;m very thankful.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Is there going to be a second season?</p><p> SETHI: We will see.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I mean, given that it&#39;s top 10 trending, you got to think it&#39;s interesting. What was the experience like putting this together? It&#39;s obviously, it&#39;s not writing, it&#39;s not podcasting, it&#39;s very different. You&#39;re pretty telegenic. Did you did you find the transition to video challenging at all?</p><p> SETHI: Definitely Well, you know, I got a lot of nice comments from people around the world and I thought to myself, wow so all it takes for me to look good is to throw up a multi-million-dollar crew with the best cameras in the world and makeup and I said, wow. Okay, I&#39;ll take it I&#39;ll take whatever it takes, you know, what was challenging most of all was the intimacy of going into people&#39;s houses.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> SETHI: like in the first scene you see me visiting Matt and Amani. I meet their family their children, that is as intimate as it gets to be in someone&#39;s living room talking about money.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Looking at their — looking literally at their…</p><p> SETHI: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Their statements, their credit card spending.</p><p> SETHI: And watching fights happen in front of me, which I do love a good fight I mean, I love reality TV myself, but you have to remember …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh no, it gets uncomfortable.</p><p> SETHI: Yes, and it should, right? Money is uncomfortable.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> SETHI: And that&#39;s okay, but all this time there&#39;s a tight camera on my face and I&#39;m thinking oh my — like is this really happening so to me that&#39;s what is the magic of the show is, I don&#39;t know anything about them all I know is their name and their financials, same as you and together we go and discover what&#39;s going on.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Well, it&#39;s definitely entertaining, we&#39;ll blow through five questions really quickly starting with other than “How to Get Rich” what else are you streaming on Netflix or anything else.</p><p> SETHI: I&#39;m watching “Indian Matchmaking” just because I love it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Come on.</p><p> SETHI: My parents had an arranged marriage you know I have to watch this. It&#39;s you know, it hits home. And on the podcast side there&#39;s a couple, one is there&#39;s an interesting podcast about Rolls-Royce and it&#39;s called “Ghost Stories” it&#39;s about their Ghost and it&#39;s you know it&#39;s a little bit like markety but I just love craftsmanship, I love design, so I get to hear from the designers.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And you&#39;re not sporting a watch, I&#39;m surprised, I figure that you&#39;re a clothes guy.</p><p> SETHI: I&#39;m a hotel guy and clothes and convenience, like personal training, things like that. Watches.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Doesn&#39;t do anything for you.</p><p> SETHI: Nah.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I&#39;ll tell you a funny story about that later.</p><p> Second question, who are your mentors? Who helped shape your career?</p><p> SETHI: BJ Fogg, one of my professors at Stanford. I learned from him at the Persuasive Technology Lab. He&#39;s still a close friend of mine. Jay Abraham taught me a lot about putting my customers and clients at the center of my world. Those two were very influential and continue to be.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Let&#39;s talk about books. What are some of your favorites? What are you reading right now?</p><p> SETHI: One of my favorites is “The Color of Law.” That&#39;s a book about redlining. It&#39;s about race and real estate in this country. Most people have no idea that real estate is deeply, deeply built around race. It&#39;s racist. It&#39;s a racist institution in our country.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And has been for a long, long time.</p><p> SETHI: For decades. It is built that way.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Do you think people really don&#39;t know that?</p><p> SETHI: They do not know.不。</p><p> No, no like 100 percent …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: The inner cities and slums and the highways that will cleave the lower-income part of the town right in half.</p><p> SETHI: No, Barry, they have no idea.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right your face.</p><p> SETHI: No, you can&#39;t miss it unless you&#39;ve been radicalized to ignore it so no they do not know and they don&#39;t want to know, and that&#39;s why every time I talk about books I talk about this book “The Color Of Law” it is staggering to learn what happened in our country.</p><p> And then I&#39;m reading a book right now called “Unreasonable Hospitality” the manager of 11 Madison Park. Wow, really interesting how they took that restaurant to be …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Top-rated Michelin star-rated.</p><p> SETHI: I just love a good hospitality story.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Last two questions. What sort of advice would you give to a recent college grad who is interested in a career in either financial counseling or investing?</p><p> SETHI: Gosh, I would say first off talk to people who are in the industry and were in the industry and left, talk to at least 15 people and find out what&#39;s their lifestyle like, do they get to travel do they enjoy it what do they like what are they not like? Find out if it&#39;s for you and then the second thing I would say is if you are interested in financial counseling, therapy, et cetera, you&#39;re going to learn the technical skills but the skill that I think is underrepresented when it comes to money is understanding people. So psychology is absolutely critical and that will set you apart.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Our final question, what do you know about the world of advice and financial planning and counseling that you wish you knew 20 years or so ago when you were first getting started?</p><p> SETHI: Education alone is not the answer.</p><p> I often get people saying, “Ramit, we should teach your book in high school.” and I actually disagree. Education alone doesn&#39;t solve the problems we have, it helps, but there are structural changes that need to be made such as building more housing, there are also ways of communicating about money which is why I did this Netflix show and my podcast to show people that money can actually be fun and joyful and not simply something that you need to do like flossing your teeth.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It doesn&#39;t have to be a drag.</p><p> Tell people where they can find you, your website the name of the show and the book and everything else.</p><p> SETHI: The name of the show on Netflix is “How to Get Rich” My suggestion is watch the first three minutes and notice the differences in how we talk about money.</p><p> My podcast where I speak to couples from all over the economic spectrum is “I Will Teach You to Be Rich” and my book is also called “I Will Teach You to Be Rich.”</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Ramit, thank you so much for coming in today. This was a blast.</p><p> If you enjoyed this conversation, well, be sure and check any of the previous 500 we&#39;ve done. You can find those at YouTube, iTunes, Spotify, wherever you find your favorite podcasts.</p><p> You can sign up for my daily reading list at ritholtz.com. Follow me on Twitter @Ritholtz. Follow all of the fine family of Bloomberg podcasts @podcast. I would be remiss if I did not thank the crack team that helps put these conversations together each week. Samantha Danziger is my audio engineer. Atika Valbrun is my project manager. Paris Wald is my producer. Sean Russo is my researcher.</p><p> I&#39;m Barry Ritholtz. You&#39;ve been listening to Masters in Business on Bloomberg Radio.</p><p> END</p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"> ~~~ </p><p></p><p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-ramit-sethi/">Transcript: Ramit Sethi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Tuesday AM Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-tuesday-am-reads-430/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:30:38 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314608 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> My gone to Europe / last reads for 10 days / see you later! morning reads: • The Stock Market Will Pick the Winners For You: Index funds ride the winners. And while they don&#39;t completely discard the losers right away, the stocks that are coming up pick up the slack for the eventual underperformers. (A…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-tuesday-am-reads-430/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-tuesday-am-reads-430/">10 Tuesday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> My <em>gone to Europe / last reads for 10 days / see you later!</em> morning reads:</p><blockquote><p> • <strong>The Stock Market Will Pick the Winners For You</strong> : Index funds ride the winners. And while they don&#39;t completely discard the losers right away, the stocks that are coming up pick up the slack for the eventual underperformers. ( <a href="https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/06/the-stock-market-will-pick-the-winners-for-you/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A Wealth of Common Sense</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>Why Should I Hold Stocks?</strong> And yet here we are, halfway through the year with the S&amp;P 500 up 10%. The Nasdaq-100 is up 31%, one of the best first half of a year ever. ( <a href="https://theirrelevantinvestor.com/2023/06/02/why-should-i-hold-stocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Irrelevant Investor</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Will Franklin Templeton&#39;s Deal With Putnam Change Their Fortunes?</strong> The legacy US fund businesses at Franklin Templeton and Putnam Investments have struggled for most of the last decade. ( <a href="https://www.institutionalinvestor.com/article/b8yzhng3wzgfrl/Will-Franklin-Templeton-s-Deal-With-Putnam-Change-Their-Fortunes" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Institutional Investor</a> )</p><p> • <strong>It&#39;s Not Just AI. 5 Trends That Will Change How You Invest</strong> . In the future we&#39;ll be thirsty, and artificial intelligence will do our jobs, but we&#39;ll all be svelte. ( <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-india-water-shortage-biotech-b13dbe26" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barron&#39;s</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The world is finally spending more on solar than oil production</strong> : The International Energy Agency just released its annual investment report. Here&#39;s where the money is going. ( <a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2023/06/01/1073799/the-world-is-finally-spending-more-on-solar-than-oil-production/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MIT Technology Review</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Five globally successful Chinese companies you&#39;ve never heard of</strong> : TikTok and Shein are household names, but ShareIt and Yalla aren&#39;t far behind. ( <a href="https://restofworld.org/2023/chinese-apps-succeeding-overseas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rest Of World</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Real estate is China&#39;s economic Achilles heel</strong> : It&#39;s the country&#39;s biggest engine of growth an employment, financial asset, and source of government revenue ( <a href="https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/real-estate-is-chinas-economic-achilles" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Noahpinion</a> )</p><p> • <strong>A $1.5 Trillion Backstop for Homebuyers Props Up Banks Instead</strong> : The Federal Home Loan Bank system provides billions to banks curtailing mortgage lending, and millions to its executives. ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-06-04/us-effort-to-help-homebuyers-get-affordable-loans-mainly-benefits-banks-instead" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Businessweek</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Your Dog Is a Secret Weapon in the Fight Against Cancer</strong> : Every year, thousands of pets develop tumors very similar to those found in people. Find drugs that work for canines, and human treatments should follow. ( <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/dog-cancer-treatments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wired</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Chris Christie is not in it to win it. His task is more important</strong> . If Christie can raise enough money to stay on the air with ads and on the debate stage (with or without Trump), he will be well-equipped to make three arguments that might sway some GOP voters — and certainly be persuasive in the general election. ( <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2023/06/01/chris-christie-2024-candidate-defeat/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Washington Post</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Wine-tasting: it&#39;s junk science</strong> . Experiments have shown that people can&#39;t tell plonk from grand cru. Now one US winemaker claims that even experts can&#39;t judge wine accurately. What&#39;s the science behind the taste? ( <a href="http://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2013/jun/23/wine-tasting-junk-science-analysis" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Guardian</a> )</p></blockquote><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> next week with <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.iwillteachyoutoberich.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ramit Sethi</a> writes about money, business, and psychology. He is the author of NYT bestseller <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1523505745/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>I Will Teach You to Be Rich</em></a> and the host of the popular Netflix series “ <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81410436" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>How to Get Rich</em></a> .”</p><p></p><p> <strong>The Cost of Buying vs Renting In America</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/buyingvrenting.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-314605" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/buyingvrenting.jpeg" alt="" width="700" height="577" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/buyingvrenting.jpeg 1179w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/buyingvrenting-300x247.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/buyingvrenting-1024x844.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/buyingvrenting-768x633.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/buyingvrenting-250x206.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></a><br /> Source: <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Wallstreetbetsnew/comments/13t7s4i/the_cost_of_buying_vs_renting_in_america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Reddit</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>Sign up for our reads-only mailing list here</em></a> .</p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/10-tuesday-am-reads-430/">10 Tuesday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> RWM is Austin Bound — Last Call!</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/last-call-rwm-austin/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[RWM]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314594 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> RWM is coming to Austin, TX June 12th-14th‼️ @Downtown with more details⬇️Email us at info@ritholtzwealth.com subject line “Austin” to reserve a meeting slot! pic.twitter.com/9iSdG4HFf3 — Ritholtz Wealth (@RitholtzWealth) May 19, 2023   Hey Y&#39;all! We&#39;re coming to Texas to celebrate the opening of RWM Austin! We only have a few slots left to meet…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/last-call-rwm-austin/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/last-call-rwm-austin/">RWM is Austin Bound — Last Call!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p dir="ltr" lang="en"> RWM is coming to Austin, TX June 12th-14th <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/203c.png" alt="‼" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p><p> <a href="https://twitter.com/Downtown?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Downtown</a> with more details <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b07.png" alt="⬇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Email us at info@ritholtzwealth.com subject line “Austin” to reserve a meeting slot! <a href="https://t.co/9iSdG4HFf3">pic.twitter.com/9iSdG4HFf3</a></p><p> — Ritholtz Wealth (@RitholtzWealth) <a href="https://twitter.com/RitholtzWealth/status/1659562556032184322?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 19, 2023</a> </p></blockquote><p><script src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" async="" charset="utf-8"></script></p><p></p><p> <em>Hey Y&#39;all</em> ! We&#39;re coming to Texas to celebrate the opening of RWM Austin!</p><section class="entry-content clearfix"> We only have a few slots left to meet with prospective clients — if you would like to learn more about being a client of Ritholtz Wealth Management, this is your chance. We will be in town next week to kick off our local Austin office. Meet my partners Joshg Brown, Kris Venne, and our new firm president Jay Tini, along with eight superstar financial planners and client service reps into town.</p><blockquote><p> <strong>To get on the calendar: info@ritholtzwealth.com subject line: Austin.</strong></p></blockquote><p> Or, just call 212.625.1200 with any questions you may have.</p><p> Similarly, if you&#39;re a financial advisor in Texas and you&#39;re looking to learn more about how we can take your career to the next level, <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://ritholtzwealth.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">be sure to get in touch</a> .</p><p></p></section><section class="entry-content clearfix"> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BarryToast-1024x704-1.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-313994" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BarryToast-1024x704-1.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="413" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BarryToast-1024x704-1.jpg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BarryToast-1024x704-1-300x206.jpg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BarryToast-1024x704-1-768x528.jpg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BarryToast-1024x704-1-250x172.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a></section><section class="entry-content clearfix"> <em><br />(Here we are in 2019 raising a glass at the firm&#39;s first offsite. Austinites will easily recognize this as the indoor / outdoor dining room at Lamberts on 2nd Street.)</em> If you&#39;d like to speak with us about your situation but you&#39;re not from Texas, that&#39;s cool too, we&#39;re standing by: <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://ritholtzwealth.com/contact/request-more-info/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ritholtzwealth.com</a></section><div class="disclaimer"></div><div></div><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/last-call-rwm-austin/">RWM is Austin Bound — Last Call!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Monday AM Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/monday-am-reads-55/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 10:30:11 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314342 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> My leaving-on-vacation, morning plane reads (see you in 10 days!): • There&#39;s No Easy Exit for Companies Backed by PE and VC: Verdad Advisers&#39; Dan Rasmussen argues that rising debt costs, compressed margins, and negative cash flow make for a “pretty scary” picture of the health of private companies. (Institutional Investor) • Hedge Funds at…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/monday-am-reads-55/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/monday-am-reads-55/">10 Monday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> My <em>leaving-on-vacation</em> , morning plane reads (see you in 10 days!):</p><blockquote><p> • <strong>There&#39;s No Easy Exit for Companies Backed by PE and VC</strong> : Verdad Advisers&#39; Dan Rasmussen argues that rising debt costs, compressed margins, and negative cash flow make for a “pretty scary” picture of the health of private companies. ( <a href="https://www.institutionalinvestor.com/article/b8yzgybyxxrcmn/There-s-No-Easy-Exit-for-Companies-Backed-by-PE-and-VC" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Institutional Investor</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Hedge Funds at War for Top Traders Dangle $120 Million Payouts</strong> : Paid sabbaticals, huge signing bonuses are among tools being used, as clients foot the bill in chase for steady returns. ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-01/top-traders-see-120-million-paydays-as-hedge-funds-fight-for-talent" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Why Your Steak Is Getting Pricier</strong> : Ranchers are shrinking cattle herds because of drought and high costs, cutting down the nation&#39;s supply of beef. That threatens to push prices for steaks and burgers to records. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/beef-prices-high-summer-barbecue-12a08905" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>A Brief History of Dollar Hatred</strong> : The current wave of animosity towards the USD is not the first – and it will not be the last. ( <a href="https://moneyinsideout.exantedata.com/p/a-brief-history-of-dollar-hatred" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Money: Inside and Out</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How Managers of Pension Funds, OCIOs Are Approaching Risk</strong> : Whether aiming to transfer or reduce risk or looking to diversify, managers are considering a wide range of options, including private credit. ( <a href="https://www.ai-cio.com/in-focus/market-drilldown/how-managers-of-pension-funds-ocios-are-approaching-risk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chief Investment Officer</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Unpacking an economic titan</strong> : Hayek was not, and always insisted that he was not, a laissez-faire economist. ( <a href="https://thecritic.co.uk/issues/june-2023/unpacking-an-economic-titan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Critic</a> )</p><p> • <strong>In Defense of the Lawn</strong> : Two-thirds of United States homes are occupied by people who own them (or are paying off a loan in order to be able to own them). Both the numbers and the eyeball evidence indicate that people of all political orientations and racial backgrounds, in both red and blue states, continue to seek ownership of homes and yards, and to take an interest in maintaining them, despite their increasing unaffordability and the various problems associated with them. ( <a href="https://slate.com/business/2023/05/in-defense-of-the-lawn.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Slate</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Saturn&#39;s Rings Could Be Younger Than Flowers</strong> : We&#39;re lucky that a relatively recent catastrophe created the gas-giant spectacle. ( <a href="https://nautil.us/saturns-rings-could-be-younger-than-flowers-308228/?_sp=8054383d-ff09-4968-af02-a58c2f71c447.1685621250756" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nautilus</a> )</p><p> • <strong>&#39;I was the Spotify of the 1980s!&#39; The Italian pirate mixtape empire that brought pop to the people</strong> : Started from an illegal market stall, Mixed By Erry became Italy&#39;s third biggest record label – until police cracked down. A new film asks whether the founders were heroes or criminals. ( <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2023/mar/08/i-was-the-spotify-of-the-1980s-the-italian-pirate-mixtape-empire-that-brought-pop-to-the-people" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Guardian</a> )</p><p> • <strong>He&#39;s the Best Player in the NBA. He&#39;s Also the Bloodiest</strong> . The Denver Nuggets&#39; Nikola Jokic has long been near the top of the leaderboard in points, assists and rebounds. He leads the league in flesh wounds, too. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/sports/basketball/nikola-jokic-nuggets-nba-finals-bf5901ba" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p></blockquote><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> next week with <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.iwillteachyoutoberich.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ramit Sethi</a> writes about money, business, and psychology. He is the author of NYT bestseller <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1523505745/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>I Will Teach You to Be Rich</em></a> and the host of the popular Netflix series “ <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81410436" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>How to Get Rich</em></a> .”</p><p></p><p> <strong>The Great Resignation is over, quit rates return to pre-pandemic levels<br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/axiosquitboom.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-314603" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/axiosquitboom.png" alt="" width="600" height="562" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/axiosquitboom.png 1136w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/axiosquitboom-300x281.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/axiosquitboom-1024x959.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/axiosquitboom-768x719.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/axiosquitboom-250x234.png 250w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><br /></strong> Source: <a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/05/31/great-resignation-quitting-boom" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Axios</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>Sign up for our reads-only mailing list here</em></a> .</p><p></p><p> <em>Ritholtz Reads will be on vacation next week, and will return June 15th.</em></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/monday-am-reads-55/">10 Monday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Sunday Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/sunday-reads-327/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jun 2023 10:15:09 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=313881 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> Avert your eyes! My Sunday morning look at incompetency, corruption and policy failures: • 5 winners and 5 losers from the debt ceiling deal: Biden and McCarthy win. The Freedom Caucus loses. (Vox) • Inside the Meltdown at CNN: CEO Chris Licht felt he was on a mission to restore the network&#39;s reputation for serious journalism. How…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/sunday-reads-327/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/sunday-reads-327/">10 Sunday Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Avert your eyes! My <em>Sunday morning</em> look at incompetency, corruption and policy failures:</p><blockquote><p> • <strong>5 winners and 5 losers from the debt ceiling deal</strong> : Biden and McCarthy win. The Freedom Caucus loses. ( <a href="https://www.vox.com/politics/2023/6/1/23743797/debt-ceiling-biden-mccarthy-winners-losers" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vox</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Inside the Meltdown at CNN</strong> : CEO Chris Licht felt he was on a mission to restore the network&#39;s reputation for serious journalism. How did it all go wrong? ( <a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2023/06/cnn-ratings-chris-licht-trump/674255/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Atlantic</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>Missteps and Miscalculations: Inside Fox&#39;s Legal and Business Debacle</strong> : Fox&#39;s handling of the defamation suit brought by Dominion Voting Systems, which settled for $787.5 million, left many unanswered questions. ( <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/27/business/media/fox-news-dominion-voting.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York Times</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The One Thing Holding Back Electric Vehicles in America</strong> : The biggest hurdle to mass adoption of electric cars is not the cars themselves. ( <a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2023/05/where-are-the-ev-charging-stations/674241/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Atlantic</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Company Insiders Made Billions Before SPAC Bust</strong> : Executives and early investors sold shares worth $22 billion. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/company-insiders-made-billions-before-spac-bust-4607a869" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Right-wing hatemongers count on the cowardice of companies such as Target</strong> : If there&#39;s a company in America you&#39;d expect to have the gumption and spirit to see off a stupid and specious attack on the selling of LGBTQ+-themed merchandise for Pride Month in June, it would be Target. ( <a href="https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2023-06-01/right-wing-hatemongers-count-on-the-cowardice-of-companies-such-as-target" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Los Angeles Times</a> )</p><p> • <strong>What Really Caused the Destruction of Tulsa&#39;s &#39;Black Wall Street&#39;</strong> A new book looks beyond the Tulsa race massacre to understand the demise of the historic Greenwood neighborhood, once known as a hub for Black wealth. ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-30/in-built-from-the-fire-victor-luckerson-explores-tulsa-race-massacre-aftermath" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CityLab</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Manufacturing Dissent</strong> : Activists and opinion-formers on the Left and Right have been persuaded that living under anything besides the kind of governance they want means they&#39;ve been cheated. ( <a href="https://quillette.com/2023/05/29/manufacturing-dissent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Quillette</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How Summer Camp Became Such a Hot Mess for Parents</strong> : You know who&#39;s not having fun? The people paying the bills. ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-06-01/rising-2023-summer-camp-costs-show-waitlists-have-usurped-fun" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Businessweek</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Clarence Thomas should resign from the supreme court, for the good of the court</strong> : By acting as if Thomas has done nothing wrong, chief justice John Roberts looks pathetic and enabling of unethical behavior. ( <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2023/may/24/clarence-thomas-should-resign-from-the-supreme-court-for-the-good-of-the-court" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Guardian</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The 400-Year-Old Tragedy That Captures Our Chaos</strong> : Pop culture is finding new currency in the tale of a king beset by madness. ( <a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2023/05/king-lear-shakespeare-succession-logan-roy/674205/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Atlantic</a> )<b>  </b></p></blockquote><p>Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> next week with <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.iwillteachyoutoberich.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ramit Sethi</a> writes about money, business, and psychology. He is the author of NYT bestseller <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1523505745/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>I Will Teach You to Be Rich</em></a> and the host of the popular Netflix series “ <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81410436" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>How to Get Rich</em></a> .”</p><p></p><p> <strong>The wider House Oversight&#39;s net, the more often it catches Trump</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/weboftrump.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-313578" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/weboftrump.png" alt="" width="600" height="676" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/weboftrump.png 1065w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/weboftrump-266x300.png 266w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/weboftrump-909x1024.png 909w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/weboftrump-768x865.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/weboftrump-250x282.png 250w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><br /> Source: <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/05/10/wider-house-oversights-net-more-often-they-catch-trump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Washington Post</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>Sign up for our reads-only mailing list here</em></a> .</p><p> ~~~</p><p></p><p> <em>Ritholtz Reads is taking a vacation, and will return June 15th.</em></p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/sunday-reads-327/">10 Sunday Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> Ramit Sethi on Living Richly</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/ramit-sethi/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jun 2023 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Consumer Spending]]></category><category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=314560 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>﻿   This week, we speak with entrepreneur Ramit Sethi, who is the founder and chief executive officer of the online education platform I Will Teach You to Be Rich (IWT), which attracts more than 1 million readers a month. Sethi is also the host of the Netflix series “How To Get Rich,” which is…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/ramit-sethi/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/ramit-sethi/">Ramit Sethi on Living Richly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ramit-sethi-on-financial-literacy-and-living-richly/id730188152?i=1000615473906" height="175" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"> <span data-mce-type="bookmark" style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" class="mce_SELRES_start">的</span></iframe></p><p></p><p>This week, we speak with entrepreneur Ramit Sethi, who is the founder and chief executive officer of the online education platform <a href="https://www.iwillteachyoutoberich.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">I Will Teach You to Be Rich (IWT</a> ), which attracts more than 1 million readers a month. Sethi is also the host of the Netflix series “ <a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81410436" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>How To Get Rich</em></a> ,” which is based on his New York Times bestselling book “ <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1523505745/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>I Will Teach You to Be Rich</em></a> “; he also hosts a podcast of the same name. His interest in the subject started in 2004, when he was studying technology and psychology at Stanford University.</p><p> He explains how he began a blog in college out of frustration with his fellow student&#39;s inability to manage their own finances. That blog eventually became a short e-book, the success of which led him to write a full-length book.</p><p> We discuss how Netflix reached out to him about turning the book into a <a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81410436" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>TV series</em></a> , which has been a top 10 trending show since its launch last month.</p><p> A list of his favorite books <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/ramit-sethi/#more-314560" target="_blank" rel="noopener">is here</a> ; A transcript of our conversation is <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/transcript-ramit-sethi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">available here</a> Tuesday.</p><p> You can stream and download our full conversation, including any podcast extras, on <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2023-06-02/ramit-sethi-on-financial-literacy-and-living-richly-podcast" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5LGxKlY6fzXS3tGsjB23Cb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business/episode/ramit-sethi-on-financial-literacy-and-living-richly-304020349" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> , and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLe4PRejZgr0PzN7r8NikAnOqP70DHhoJ0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> . All of our earlier podcasts on your favorite pod hosts can be <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">found here</a> .</p><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> next week with Mathieu Chabran, Tikehau Capital A global alternative asset manager with $40B in assets. The firm is headquartered in Paris, and has offices in 13 countries, but primarily is run out of money centers in New York, London, and Singapore. He cofounded Tikehau in 2004 with Antoine Flamarion, a colleague at Deutsche Bank, and runs the US division. Chabran was named <strong><em>Chevalier de l&#39;Ordre de la Légion d&#39;Honneur</em></strong> by decree of the President of the French Republic in January 2022.</p><p></p><p><span id="more-314560"></span></p><p></p><h3> Ramit Sethi Authored Book</h3><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1523505745/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">I Will Teach You to Be Rich: No Guilt. No Excuses. Just a 6-Week Program That Works</a></strong> by Ramit Sethi<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1523505745/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-314528" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ramit.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="376" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ramit.jpg 332w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ramit-200x300.jpg 200w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ramit-250x376.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p></p><h3> Ramit Sethi Favorite Books</h3><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1631494538/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Color of Law: A Forgotten History of How Our Government Segregated America</a></strong> by Richard Rothstein<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1631494538/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-314529" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coloroflaw.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="394" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coloroflaw.jpg 317w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coloroflaw-191x300.jpg 191w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coloroflaw-250x394.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0593418573/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Unreasonable Hospitality: The Remarkable Power of Giving People More Than They Expect</a></strong> by Will Guidara<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0593418573/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-314530" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unreasonable.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="377" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unreasonable.jpg 331w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unreasonable-199x300.jpg 199w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unreasonable-250x377.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/06/ramit-sethi/">Ramit Sethi on Living Richly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>