<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>大局观</title><atom:link href="https://ritholtz.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://ritholtz.com<description>资本市场、经济、地缘政治、科技、数字媒体的宏观视角</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 7 月 12 日星期三 11:05:36 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title> 10 周三上午阅读</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-wednesday-am-reads-338/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 10:50:52 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=315981 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>我的周中早班火车 WFH 中写道： • 以不同的方式衡量，通胀已经过去：那些认为潜在通胀正在下降但速度不足以让美联储满意的投资者应该会受到另一种价格上涨衡量标准的困扰。以欧洲的方式衡量美国的价格变化，通货膨胀在五月份就已经存在了……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-wednesday-am-reads-338/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-wednesday-am-reads-338/">周三上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>我的周中早晨<del>火车</del>WFH 内容如下：</p><blockquote><p> •<strong>采用不同的衡量标准，通胀已成为过去</strong>：如果投资者认为潜在通胀正在下降，但对于美联储来说速度还不够快，那么他们应该会因价格上涨的替代衡量标准而感到困扰。以欧洲的方式衡量美国的物价变化，通货膨胀在五月份就已经出现了。按照美国的做法来衡量它们，周三经济学家预测的新数据显示核心通胀率要高得多，6 月份为 5%。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/measure-it-differently-and-inflation-is-behind-us-6a6a89c1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>不存在“滚动衰退”这样的事情：</strong>您预测了衰退，但它没有发生？您即将接受 CNBC 采访吗？不用担心，您随时可以声称已经出现了“滚动衰退”。这就像一张出狱卡。除了 。 。 。滚动衰退并不存在。如果整体经济持续繁荣，房地产市场疲软之后制造业疲软以及科技行业的一些裁员这一事实并不意味着什么。滚动衰退的说法仅仅被用作错误模型导致的宏观经济预测失败的借口。 （ <a href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/theres-no-such-thing-as-rolling-recessions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">金钱错觉</a>）</p><p> •<strong>保险公司向资金管理者寻求房地产、私人信贷市场的机会</strong>：近期住宅建设的激增让保险公司将目光投向单户和多户住宅领域的投资机会。 （ <a href="https://www.ai-cio.com/news/insurers-tap-money-managers-for-opportunities-in-real-estate-private-credit-markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">首席投资官</a>）</p><p> •<strong>市政当局不会推动美国经济增长，但他们也不会阻碍美国经济增长</strong>：州和地方政府的经济非常重要。他们的支出约占美国国内生产总值的十分之一。根据劳工统计局的数据，各市政府雇用了近 2000 万美国人，而联邦政府的雇员人数约为 300 万（其中包括邮政服务）。 （ <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/bf294a55-1886-4906-97ac-3bc7ca2e4765" target="_blank" rel="noopener">金融时报阿尔法维尔</a>）</p><p> •<strong>谁雇用您的医生？越来越多的私募股权公司</strong>。一项新研究发现，私募股权公司拥有美国某些市场一半以上的专家。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/10/upshot/private-equity-doctors-offices.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">结果</a>）</p><p> • <strong>Chris Miller，历史学家和《芯片战争》一书的作者，</strong>在这本书中我就半导体行业的控制权之战咨询了一位专家。 （ <a href="https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/interview-chris-miller-historian" target="_blank" rel="noopener">诺阿平宁</a>）</p><p> •<strong>为什么Threads 的早期成功可能会变成现实</strong>：马克·扎克伯格利用Meta 的力量推动Threads 快速启动——但这可能只能在一定程度上发挥作用。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/11/technology/threads-zuckerberg-meta-google-plus.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>被排除在数字生活之外是很糟糕的。以下是如何避免它</strong>。通过使用多种形式的验证来防止锁定。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/dont-panic-set-up-two-factor-authentication-so-you-dont-get-locked-out-20dd2b82" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>夏天来了。萤火虫在哪里？</strong>萤火虫专家在最近的一项综合评估中估计，美国和加拿大近三分之一的萤火虫物种可能面临灭绝的威胁。国外的调查显示，从马来西亚的红树林到英国的草原，土地面积都在减少。新的研究揭示了这些空灵的昆虫是如何在我们围绕它们建造的明亮世界中努力繁衍生息的。而且这个问题比单一类型的错误更严重。 “萤火虫是告诉你栖息地遇到麻烦的标志。” （ <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/interactive/2023/firefly-summer-extinction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华盛顿邮报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>菲比·沃勒-布里奇的《夺宝奇兵》大冒险</strong>：从《伦敦生活》到詹姆斯·邦德、《夺宝奇兵》和《古墓丽影》并不是最合乎逻辑的 A 到 B 行动。那么，您认为这些项目背后的人认为您为他们带来了什么？这与您认为自己带来的东西相符吗？ （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/07/02/magazine/phoebe-waller-bridge-indiana-jones-interview.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报</a>）</p></blockquote><p>请务必在本周末与富兰克林邓普顿首席执行官 Jenny Johnson 一起学习我们的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士课程</a>，该公司管理着 1.5 万亿美元的客户资产。她自 1988 年以来一直在 FT 工作，并在投资管理、分销、技术、运营和高净值客户方面担任领导职务。富兰克林邓普顿管理着 9000 多名员工和 1300 名投资专业人士。约翰逊名列最有权势的女性名单（《巴伦周刊》、《福布斯》、《美国银行家》等）。她于 2020 年 2 月出任首席执行官。</p><p> <strong><br />Meta的山寨机</strong><br /><a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316356" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat.png" alt="" width="600" height="464" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat.png 1552w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat-300x232.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat-1024x792.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat-768x594.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat-250x193.png 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/copycat-1536x1188.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><br />来源： <a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/07/06/metas-copycat-machine-threads" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Axios</a></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-wednesday-am-reads-338/">周三上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title>文字记录：珍妮·约翰逊、富兰克林邓普顿</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/transcript-jenny-johnson/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mutual Funds]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=316152 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>﻿ 本周 MiB 的文字记录：富兰克林邓普顿首席执行官珍妮·约翰逊 (Jenny Johnson) 如下。您可以在 Apple Podcasts、Spotify、Stitcher、Google、YouTube 和 Bloomberg 上流式传输和下载我们的完整对话，包括任何播客附加内容。您可以在此处找到您最喜欢的播客主机上的所有早期播客。 ~~~ 播音员：这是大师赛……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/transcript-jenny-johnson/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/transcript-jenny-johnson/">后记：富兰克林邓普顿珍妮·约翰逊 (Jenny Johnson)</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">《大图片》(The Big Picture)</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm/id730188152?i=1000619921102" height="175" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"> <span data-mce-type="bookmark" style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span></iframe></p><p></p><p>本周<a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/mib-jenny-johnson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>MiB：富兰克林邓普顿首席执行官珍妮·约翰逊 (Jenny Johnson)</em></a>的文字记录如下。</p><p>您可以在<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm/id730188152?i=1000619921102" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Podcasts</a> 、 <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5LGxKlY6fzXS3tGsjB23Cb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> 、 <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business/episode/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm-305087344" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> 、 <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvZTczYzk5OGUtNmU2MC00MzJmLTg2MTAtYWUyMTAxNDBjNWIxLzRlNGNkOTEwLTQwYTEtNDYxOS1hNWYzLWFlMmIwMDEyZmZmZi81ODczYTNjYi0yOThmLTQwYmMtYjcxZi1hZTJiMDAxMzAwMGQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> 、 <a href="https://youtu.be/jO_CfgjAQak" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a>和<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2023-07-07/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm-podcast" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a>上流式传输和下载我们的完整对话，包括任何播客附加内容。您可以<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">在此处找到</a>您最喜欢的播客主机上的所有早期播客。</p><p style="text-align: center;"> ~~~</p><p>播音员：这是彭博电台巴里·里索尔茨 (Barry Ritholtz) 主持的商业硕士节目。</p><p> BARRY RITHOLTZ，商科硕士主持人：本周，在播客中，我再次迎来了一位额外的特别嘉宾。珍妮·约翰逊是投资巨头富兰克林邓普顿的首席执行官。他们的资产约为 1.5 万亿美元。她自 2020 年 2 月起担任首席执行官。她已在公司工作数十年。这是一场令人难以置信、富有洞察力的对话，内容涉及如何建立一家公司、如何通过收购实现增长、如何确保团队中的每个人都了解自己的角色、受到赞赏，并以最高水平行事和表现。</p><p>我发现这次谈话不仅富有洞察力、内容丰富，而且令人愉快，我想你也会的。</p><p>话不多说，我与富兰克林邓普顿首席执行官珍妮·约翰逊 (Jenny Johnson) 进行了对话。</p><p>珍妮·约翰逊，欢迎来到彭博社。</p><p>富兰克林邓普顿总裁兼首席执行官珍妮·约翰逊：谢谢巴里，很高兴来到这里。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：很高兴有你。我对此期待已久。我来来回回了一段时间，然后我们遭遇了大流行。</p><p>让我们谈谈您的背景。您于 1988 年加入富兰克林邓普顿。家族成员帮助创建了这个农场，并经营了很长时间。那时是弗兰克，现在是富兰克林邓普顿吗？</p><p>约翰逊：是富兰克林。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这就是富兰克林。</p><p> JOHNSON：我们于 1992 年收购了 Templeton。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：我花了一年的时间，我父亲对我说，“听着，如果你打算从事金融服务行业，你可能应该在纽约工作。”因此，我在德崇证券工作了一年。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：顺便说一句，对于习惯了阳光和好天气的西海岸女孩来说，这很难，对吧？</p><p>约翰逊：虽然我出生在新泽西州。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：好的，泽西岛哪里？</p><p>约翰逊：我出生在蒙特克莱尔。</p><p>里索兹：好的。</p><p>约翰逊：所以，我在新泽西州一直住到九岁左右。所以我回来住在泽西城......</p><p> RITHOLTZ：是的，现在我记得我们为什么搬到加利福尼亚了。</p><p>约翰逊：嘿，泽西岛有一些美丽的地方。</p><p>里索兹：有。天气确实是个大问题。至少可以说，每年 300 天的阳光是无与伦比的。既然我们谈论的是天气，那么除了天气之外，文化差异是什么，尤其是在金融方面？因为加州的金融在文化上与纽约的金融非常不同。</p><p>约翰逊：当然，我的意思是我认为——我认为，富兰克林的总部位于硅谷。事实上，我认为现在对它影响最大的是西海岸正在发生的科技文化。这很有趣，如果你，现在你在纽约看到它，但如果你穿着外套和领带出现在会议上，在互联网时代结束后进入更近的时代，你就会被视为就像旧经济一样。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：现在我们看到每个人，在纽约市走来走去，几乎没有人打领带。背心是新制服。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我认为背心已经是……</p><p>约翰逊：他们让我摆姿势……</p><p>里索兹：对吗？它有点转移到 Lululemon 裤子和纽扣衬衫上，就像人们过去穿的那样。</p><p>约翰逊：所以我认为没有人期望西海岸在文化和服装方面领先于东海岸，但我认为这在科技方面已经发生了一些。否则，在西海岸，如果你从事金融服务行业，那生活会很艰难。你在办公室里，很多人起床......</p><p> RITHOLTZ：上午 9 点午餐。</p><p>约翰逊：是的，完全正确。</p><p>里索兹：对吗？我曾经笑过。但好消息是，你完成了一门课程，你就可以出去冲浪了。</p><p>约翰逊：是的，就这样。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这一直是一件事。你在纽约的德雷塞尔大学待了一年。你回到富兰克林邓普顿。您在《金融时报》的第一个职位是什么？</p><p>约翰逊：天哪，现在我很尴尬。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：或者仍然是富兰克林？前进。</p><p>约翰逊：我是一名执行行政协调员。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：所以我在特殊项目上为首席运营官工作。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：然后我搬进去，当时我们有一家银行，我开始管理银行的一部分。我必须告诉你，我们随后剥离了汽车融资业务。作为今天的首席执行官，我不得不说，经营汽车金融业务的那段时期可能是我职业生涯中最重要的时期。当时我还经营信用卡业务。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这两项业务都很困难，所以并不容易。</p><p>约翰逊：学习如何作为首席执行官做事。一是我们将汽车贷款中的资产证券化并将其出售给其他资产管理公司，因为我们自己无法购买它们。我记得我在电话里想，当项目经理询问有关现金流和其他事情的问题时，我在想，你问了关于这个投资组合是否会表现的所有错误问题，因为它是诸如首付之类的问题。有信用评分、平均信用评分，所有的东西……</p><p> RITHOLTZ：是的，什么是风险，而不是……</p><p>约翰逊：对，完全正确。</p><p>因此，学习这方面的业务真的很好。当然，作为首席执行官，无论公司规模有多大，你总是在谈论将资本分配到哪里。您应该在营销或产品系列中添加更多内容，对吧？对于大公司和小公司来说，这些都是同样的问题。所以我一直觉得这是很棒的学习经历。</p><p>然后是 90 年代末或 90 年代初信用卡业务中最重要的事情，那些擅长数据和数据分析的人主导了该行业，并基本上将其他人排除在外。因此，我成为了数据及其预测能力的忠实粉丝。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：出于所有显而易见的原因，对吗？如果您在数据方面拥有优势，那么您在整个业务领域都具有优势。</p><p>约翰逊：当然。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：富兰克林显然剥离了银行业务、信用卡业务和汽车融资业务。是什么导致了这个决定？你们刚才是不是说我们真的要做纯粹的投资管理？</p><p>约翰逊：嗯，我认为部分原因是监管。资产管理公司对银行的要求太高了，这对我们来说有点限制。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：储贷危机发生后，情况变得更加艰难。</p><p>约翰逊：是的，完全正确。老实说，我认为我们在金融危机后撤资了。所以一旦规则改变了，是的，我们就保留了很长一段时间。但一旦规则开始改变，诸如注入新资金之类的事情就变得困难了。一年之内，你所占的份额不能超过该基金的 10%。嗯，这在我们的行业很难做到，因为人们寻找业绩记录。</p><p>里索兹：当然。</p><p>约翰逊：所以你播种并获得记录。我们只是看着它并说，它还不够重要，因为它会给我们的资产管理业务带来复杂性。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：听起来，摆脱这种束缚是一个简单的决定。</p><p>约翰逊：是的，除了我们确实有信托，这是一项高净值业务。当您拥有高净值业务时，拥有贷款部门总是好的。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：好吧，我们稍后会讨论收购，但从你刚开始担任行政组织助理时开始。</p><p>约翰逊：首席洗瓶工。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：对，对，请给我拿点咖啡，虽然我想你仍然知道，但你不是图腾柱的底部，因为人们显然知道你是谁，也知道你的家人是谁，但是从你刚开始担任“让我先迈一步”的角色开始，富兰克林在接下来的几十年里发生了怎样的变化？</p><p>约翰逊：好吧，我不得不说，当你说你知道自己是对的时，你不知道你在一个创始人仍然参与的企业中，而你是一个家庭成员，你会受到一些不同的对待，但我父亲总是坚持认为你必须比其他人更努力地工作，因为人们会看到你工作有多努力，然后工作得少一点，就像他们不会觉得自己必须做更多的事情一样。我记得我的第一份工作是暑期工作，我接替了当时 21 岁的姐姐，而我，我不知道，15 岁还是 16 岁，他每小时付给她 5 美元，他每小时付给我 2.50 美元。</p><p>我对他说：“听着，我想我工作更努力了，我想我应该每小时拿 5 美元。”他说：“好吧，你总是可以在其他地方找到工作。” （笑声） 这就是我学到的。好吧，有一定的标准……</p><p> RITHOLTZ：你爸爸可不是胡说八道的。</p><p>约翰逊：废话不多说。</p><p>里索兹：他是认真的。</p><p>约翰逊：100%。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：你不喜欢这里？敲砖头。</p><p>约翰逊：没错。</p><p>里索兹：好的。这真的很有趣，但顺便说一句，这是非常敏锐的观察，人们会看看你会付出多大的努力——你正在工作，他们认为我可以工作得不那么努力。</p><p>约翰逊：是的。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我认为他们会比你更努力地工作，所以没有人指责他们偷懒，但也许这是一代人的事情。谁知道？我们并没有那么远，我想我们的年龄差不多，我总是被教导，嘿，找到最难最快的人，然后比他多做一点。</p><p>所以你不想处于底层......</p><p>约翰逊：当然。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：你将会通过这个。</p><p>约翰逊：当然。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：那么你们在早期是共同基金还是 SMA，你们在做什么？</p><p>约翰逊：嗯，这实际上只是共同基金，我的意思是，这就是选择的工具，你知道，它随着时间的推移演变成了 SMA 和 ETF 以及集体投资信托等两种东西，现在你必须能够提供所有这些作为你投资能力的渠道，我认为发生了很多变化。这种情况已经开始发生，但在全球金融危机之后加速，监管机构要求提高分销费用的透明度。</p><p>所以你看到了这种转变，从共同基金工具中嵌入的费用到客户声明中的外部费用，然后顾问想要 ETF 和 SMA 等东西，因为客户看到他们每个月都向顾问付款。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：所以情况发生了变化，我认为我们使用的车辆类型在行业中发生了巨大的变化。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我一直认为市场会自行解决这个问题。几十年来我一直错误地认为这一点。我一直假设人们会看到，哦，C 股的预付金额为 5%，或者年度预付金额为 2 1/2%。我以为人们会看到这一点并避开。但这种情况似乎直到金融危机才真正发生。这似乎是索引真正起飞的地方，也是人们对价格更加敏感的地方。</p><p>约翰逊：嗯，我认为你看到了向 C 股的重大转变，你有更大的后端跟踪和更小的前期跟踪。所以这种情况确实发生了。看，我坚信其中一些类型的佣金产品仍然很重要。我们看看英国，那里有一种叫做 RDR 的东西。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：所以他们不允许任何形式的基于佣金的销售，所以一切都变成了收费，而且有很大比例的人无法得到建议，因为从本质上讲，顾问说，“啊，这太糟糕了。”一个小帐户。这不值得我花时间。”然而，如果他们获得了预付佣金，他们就会花时间去做这件事。关键在于人们早期投资的差异。</p><p>因此，如果您从 25 岁到 35 岁投资 10 年，例如每年 5,000 美元，或者等到 35 岁并以每年 5,000 美元的价格投资 30 年，那么在这 10 年期间您将有更多资金用于这些投资，因为复合。因此，让人们尽早投资真的非常重要，你不希望有机制、监管环境，这样会阻止他们尽早获得建议。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这很有趣，尽管在当今的数字世界中，正如你们所知，有很多没有最低费用的投资方式，而且很多人，尤其是年轻一代，非常喜欢 DIY 者，而不是自己动手的人。并不是说罗宾汉一定是他们应该投资的方式，但是嘿，它让他们对金融感兴趣，让他们思考金钱。这并不是什么可怕的事情。</p><p>约翰逊：不，这并不是一件可怕的事情。它实际上很棒，特别是因为你可以做一些基本的资产配置模型，所以机器人顾问......</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：……对于财务状况不复杂的人来说可能非常棒。</p><p>你倾向于看到的是，随着人们的收入越来越多，储蓄越来越多，有人对我说，如果你的收入有相当于三年的储蓄，那就是你开始寻求建议的时候。因为你意识到，你知道吗，这更复杂。我宁愿有人全职专注于此，而不是让我兼职管理我的资金。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我只是想分享一个有趣的故事。我们刚刚度假回来，时间不是很长，但是八九天，你回来看到所有这些邮件，哦，这是国税局的状态，传递，我必须把它转发给会计师，哦，这是关于我们拥有的这只基金的披露，然后是即将发布的季度报告，突然间，我匆忙地想通了，哦，这就是为什么人们要付费请某人为他们提供建议。我不想处理它。</p><p>约翰逊：是的。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：我度假回来了，我很放松。我最不想做的就是开始考虑纽约州 PTET 通过。把这个取下来吧。费用是多少？太好了，把这个从我的盘子里拿走。我不想处理它。</p><p>约翰逊：嗯，我想很多人，当 TurboTax 出现时，他们说，“哦，这将是注册会计师的终结。” TurboTax 的第一大用户是谁？这是注册会计师。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：注册会计师，是的。</p><p>约翰逊：因为最后，人们坐在那里说：“等一下，实际上，人们拥有的钱越多，他们就越有选择做其他事情。”</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：他们认为花时间尝试管理这些事情的机会成本是不值得的。</p><p>里索兹：是时候了。时间到了。时间至关重要。另外，规则每年都会变化。谁愿意跟上这一点？我发现这就像，你知道吗，这很有趣，这就像是晚年的认识。当你还年轻，有大把的时间，却没有很多钱时，我就能明白这一点。我可以自己报税。当你老了，就会觉得，无论付出什么代价。</p><p>约翰逊：就这么做吧。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：把这些垃圾从我身边拿开。</p><p>约翰逊：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：那么让我们来谈谈富兰克林邓普顿的收购历史。大约 30 年前，富兰克林收购了 Templeton、Galbraith 和 Hansberger。公司的新名称成为富兰克林邓普顿。富兰克林和共同基金先驱约翰·邓普顿爵士就是这样。 92 年发生这件事时，你在公司还很年轻。你还记得当时那笔相当大的、价值十亿美元的收购并不是什么都没有。</p><p>约翰逊：不，它很大。</p><p>这很有趣，因为对于很多人来说，我们作为潜在收购者之一进入得比较晚。所以，我们基本上认为，富兰克林在固定收益、国内股票方面非常强大，而邓普顿所做的是开放这种国际投资，这确实是相当新的……</p><p>里索兹：对。早期的。</p><p>约翰逊：……对于大多数资产。是的，他们是新兴市场和真正的全球股票的先驱。当我们收购它时，很多人都持怀疑态度，因为资产管理收购并不总是有效。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：对，大文化……</p><p>约翰逊：看起来很贵，文化差异很大，而且很贵。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：我不得不说我父亲理解，这一直是我们在资产管理业务所有收购中的理念，你要买什么？你买的是人、他们的投资能力和他们的投资过程，所以不要因为介入和搞乱而破坏价值。因此，我们确实将其在投资方面保持独立，然后整合了公司的其他部分。效果非常好。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这与我们通常听到的方法非常不同，我们想购买一家公司的资产、收入流，也许还有一些技术或知识产权，我们会把你融入我们的文化，无论是你喜欢与否。这似乎是你父亲采取的更细致的方法。</p><p>我没有看到金融领域有很多其他的并购是如此不干涉的。也许20年前对太平洋投资管理公司（PIMCO）的大规模收购可能有点过于放任自流，但在大多数情况下，似乎每个人都把每个人都混在一起了。</p><p>约翰逊：是的，我的意思是，就我们而言，我不会说这是完全不干涉的。它对投资过程不干涉，对吗？并真正尝试整合其余部分，然后尝试找出可以增加价值的方法，因为你拥有规模，而这些公司没有。在坦普尔顿交易中，这不是一个问题，但在我们最近的收购中，这一点非常重要。</p><p>因为我们规模更大，我们能做什么来增强各个投资团队的能力？</p><p> RITHOLTZ：那么让我们来谈谈最近的一些收购。 2020年，你买了Legg Mason。我认为这是一笔全现金交易，价值 45 亿美元，对吗？</p><p>约翰逊：是的，然后我们承担了一些债务。</p><p>里索兹：是的。 Legg Mason 带来了什么是你们需要的或没有的？您的想法是什么？</p><p>约翰逊：是的，就 Legg 而言，他们拥有西方资产管理公司，这是核心加上固定收益，这是最大的类别，而我们只是在那里没有规模，而你必须有规模才能进入制度空间。另一个令我们兴奋的大公司是 Clarion Partners，现在市值 820 亿美元，我想他们当时可能是 45 岁，市值 450 亿美元的房地产经理。我们知道我们想进入替代空间。因此，将其作为 Legg 交易的一部分真是令人兴奋。</p><p>然后是令人难以置信的 ClearBridge、Martin Currie 和 Brandywine 经理。所以我们在那里获得了丰富的专业知识。他们 75% 是机构人士。我们 75% 是零售的。因此，将两家公司合并在一起，确实让我们在零售和机构方面达到了 50/50 的比例，这非常重要。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：今年您以近 10 亿美元收购了 Putnam。普特南几乎是坦普尔顿的买家，这有点有趣，每个人最终都在同一个地方。这似乎是一次非常具有战略意义的购买。请告诉我们收购 Putnam 背后的想法。</p><p>约翰逊：所以让我退后一步，谈谈我们的收购策略。所以我认为我们过去已经完成了 10 个项目，Putnam 将是我们过去三年中的第 10 个项目。如果你考虑一下该行业正在发生的大宏观趋势，他们都关注的一个问题是私募市场将继续存在。他们来这里是为了留下来，第一，获取私人信贷。正确的？全球金融危机的银行业危机使监管机构改变了对银行的资本要求，银行为最好的客户保留了资本，这为银行体系之外的私人信贷创造了机会。</p><p>老实说，随着围绕区域银行危机后更多资本要求的讨论（我对此有强烈的看法），我认为情况只会变得更糟。然后你……</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这将为填补这一空白的公司创造机会。</p><p>约翰逊：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：顺便说一句，这实际上是从 20 世纪 90 年代末 2000 年代初开始的。随着大银行向高端市场迈进，它们留下了一个空白，私人市场就介入了。</p><p>约翰逊：完全正确。</p><p>另一方面，这肯定是由低利率推动的，但事实上，私募股权公司可以更长时间地保持私有状态。你从数字中看到了这一点，对吧？ 2000 年平均公司在三年后上市，这可能是网络公司的一个反常现象。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：到 2019 年，我认为需要 9 到 10 年，到 2022 年，他们上市需要 14 到 15 年，对吗？现在的上市公司数量只有 2000 年的一半。所以你会想，为什么要上市，对吧？上市公司面临季度盈利压力。关于员工的薪酬有很多审查。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：人们对政治有期望。你将对某些政治问题发表意见。如果您是一家私营公司，则不会有任何这些压力。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：在技术取得巨大进步的时代，你需要对事物进行投资。我的意思是，我们在区块链领域所做的一些事情在七到十年内不会对公司产生实质性影响，但我们认为我们现在做的事情非常重要。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：但是如果你是一家私人公司，如果你是一家上市公司，股东会让你对这种事情感到悲伤……</p><p>约翰逊：如果这影响了你的季度收益，我们很幸运，因为我们的管理层仍然有创始人和员工，他们拥有大量股票，所以我们可以承受一些压力，但如果你的股票表现不佳，你总是可以找一个积极分子，他希望短期内获得利益，并说如果我们打破这一切，我们将变得更有价值。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这并不能建立一家长期可持续发展的公司，但这就是上市公司所面临的压力。</p><p>因此，我们相信这种趋势将会持续下去，并且我们知道我们需要添加这些功能。因此，我说我们在收购中寻找三个领域。因此，一是填补产品空白，特别是在私人市场的情况下。</p><p>第二个是，第二个大趋势是当金融危机发生时，我们提到监管机构施加压力，要求分销费用和顾问变得收费透明，这诚实地将大部分权力推给了经销商。</p><p>老实说，实际上是对直接与客户打交道的人，对财务顾问本身。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：因此，制造商的权力较小。因此，我们寻找方法来增强分销实力，成为更好的战略合作伙伴。其中一些是金融科技，就普特南而言，它正在与 Power Corp 建立更密切的关系，Power Corp 拥有 Great West Life Insurance 或对其拥有重大控制权，以及第二大退休平台 Empower ，增长最快的一个，这非常重要，因为退休渠道是共同基金仍然有增长的地方。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：是的，因为没有理由在那里放置 ETF。</p><p>约翰逊：没错，税收……</p><p> RITHOLTZ：共同基金的负面影响是幽灵税。嘿嘿，如果是一个合格的账号，那没关系，没关系。</p><p>约翰逊：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：共同基金也有优势……</p><p>约翰逊：当然。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：……在交易和管理方面，它比 ETF 更具优势，尤其是在这种环境下。</p><p>约翰逊：当然。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：所以我想谈谈 40% 和一点点与公共市场的隔离，但我会回到这一点。我得问你关于最后一笔收购的事。去年，您购买了 O&#39;Shaughnessy Investments，包括他们名为 Canvas 的直接索引产品。坦白说，我们是 Canvas 的早期用户之一。我认为我的公司 Ritholtz Wealth Management 是 Canvas 最大的客户，或者至少在你收购它时是最大的客户。我们喜欢这个产品，我们的客户发现它在管理和抵消资本利得税方面非常有用。</p><p>收购 O&#39;Shaughnessy 背后的想法是什么？Canvas 有何计划？</p><p>约翰逊：太棒了。我的意思是，作为它的用户，您可能甚至可以比我更多地谈论这一点，但我可以告诉您，我们再次认为，一个大趋势是这种直接索引。但我们喜欢 Canvas 的原因，我知道你也知道这一点，是 Canvas 是从一家量化商店发展而来的，该商店开发了管理其量化投资组合的技术。因此，最初，您只需通过税务优化进行直接索引，但我们将其视为我们认为您可以使用的工具，就像 SMA、单独管理帐户的趋势一样，您可以使用 Canvas 的技术，表达我们的那里有积极的管理策略。因此，采取共同基金策略，通过 Canvas 平台交付，叠加税务优化，甚至包括一些 ESG 叠加。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：所以，如果你的客户说，我真的很想，我女儿会说，我真的想要推动碳净零的事情。所以她希望以这种方式管理她的投资组合。您可以将这些标签放在那里，但仍然采取专业管理的策略......</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>约翰逊：并通过该技术来表达它。所以我们对此进行了研究，并表示这在未来将非常重要。 We have to be in the direct index space but more importantly we have to have great technology because we think this is just the beginning of a trend.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right. Not only is the software really good but the O&#39;Shaughnessy database that they&#39;ve been polishing up for decades. Very few things. I mean CRISPR is probably the only other one that is that focused, that dedicated, that clean.</p><p> Most databases are just problematic to do this sort of work. Jim is now retired, but I know his son Patrick took over. But it&#39;s a great product. They&#39;re a great team. I&#39;m sure you guys are going to have a lot of success with them.</p><p> Let me go over couple of more acquisitions that really kind of surprised me. Managed options capabilities, tell us about that.</p><p> JOHNSON: Well we think that&#39;s going to be important to add to the Canvas platform.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh really?</p><p> JOHNSON: Yeah so managed options are important as part of the tax optimization strategy and so the feeling is that you needed that to be included to where the technology will ultimately go for this where the strategies will ultimately go.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So when I hear managed options and capital gains I think zero cost collars and things like that is that what&#39;s along the lines here?</p><p> JOHNSON: Yes so they can include that now in like a separately managed account.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh that&#39;s really, really interesting.</p><p> And then Alcentra you acquired from BNY Mellon, Lexington Partners who&#39;s another private equity and secondary entity and then I didn&#39;t realize you guys bought AdvisorEngine. That was like a big sort of semi-robo advisor for advisors. I mean this is a long line and then Alternative Credit Manager, Benefit Street Partners and then Athena Capital. I mean you guys have been on a tear. All of these things are different products filling in holes different services, and you want to be able to offer a full rounded set of products to institutional and retail clients.</p><p> JOHNSON: Yes, we want to be the first phone call. We want to be the strategic partner where, you know, somebody&#39;s thinking, I&#39;ve got this problem. Let me think about how to solve it.</p><p> I want to talk to Franklin Templeton and talk to them about how to approach it. And so, you take Advisor Engine, it has a CRM system that was built by a financial advisor. So, you know, a lot of smaller RIA&#39;s don&#39;t have a tech team to sit there and say, how do I use Salesforce, how do I use Microsoft Dynamic? And so they want something simple. So this is a simple CRM system that&#39;s just for the business of being a financial advisor.</p><p> And if we can build that relationship with that advisor, then we feel like we can be a stickier partner.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: How important is the registered investment advisor, the RIA space to Franklin Templeton.</p><p> I always thought of you guys back in the day as mutual fund managers, perhaps selling into that vertical, I sound like a marketing guy, but how important is the RIA space to Franklin Templeton today?</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, the RIA&#39;s have been growing again as the fee-based environment and the fact that people honestly could take their book and walk in and set up their own shingle and be on a platform provider.</p><p> And so it&#39;s a really important channel for us. It&#39;s a, we are much bigger in the wire house and the independent channels, because that&#39;s kind of been our DNA historically. And those who were big in the ETF tended, RIA&#39;s have tended to lean more towards ETFs, although that&#39;s a little bit of a stereotype.</p><p> And so it&#39;s been an important area of focus for us to grow that channel.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And to be fair, the wire houses have kind of been slowly morphing into advisors. They&#39;re all hybrids these days. It&#39;s less transactional, more fee-based to the benefit of the clients.</p><p> JOHNSON: Absolutely. Couldn&#39;t agree more.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really quite fascinating. Let&#39;s talk a little bit about your experience as a woman running a corporation. You&#39;ve held leadership roles across just about every line of business in the company. What was that experience like? What did you learn from running things as diverse as investment management and technology?</p><p> It seems like totally opposite businesses.</p><p> JOHNSON: It&#39;s funny, so on the first question, people ask me, what&#39;s it like to be a woman in finance? Well, the problem is I don&#39;t know what it&#39;s like not to be one, so I don&#39;t know that …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: …I have a good answer to that, but I can say, I am so thankful today as a CEO to have having run technology because so much, I think, of decisions that we have to make and innovation that&#39;s happening requires a basic understanding of technology.</p><p> And so I look at parts of your career, you sort of move your way around and you wonder whether it&#39;s going to be relevant at some point or not. And some of the things that I think would, naturally people think wouldn&#39;t be relevant to being CEO have been the most relevant. I mentioned running the auto finance business …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: And honestly running the technology department.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You don&#39;t have a background in tech. How hard was it to ramp up running a tech division when you&#39;re not a natural geek? And it&#39;s almost a different language sometimes.</p><p> JOHNSON: So it&#39;s funny, although I&#39;m divorced now, but I was married to a guy who was a tech person. And I&#39;d always ask him all these questions. I was really curious around it. And so I always felt like he gave me a really good background in understanding technology. And then I learned to be fearless in asking the question.正确的？ Tech people are used to everybody&#39;s being so afraid of tech that they give you, they can sometimes give you a little bit of a blurred answer.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: They can steamroll you a little bit.</p><p> JOHNSON: And you&#39;re afraid to look stupid so you don&#39;t ask. Well, I learned, you know what, if you think about what technology is, it&#39;s moving this piece of data from here to here and maybe adding some new data, dumb down what you&#39;re talking about and let me just try to understand it. and things like cloud servicing, right? These are concepts that have existed in tech for a long time. The technology gets better, and we usually change the name about every decade. But once you understand what it&#39;s trying to achieve, you don&#39;t have to be a programmer. You just, you know, and I honestly, I think one of the biggest things that people don&#39;t appreciate is the quality of data. Truly garbage in, garbage out. And so having discipline around your data management is really, really important in a tech department.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s really hard also. we were talking earlier about the O&#39;Shaughnessy database. I know that they painstakingly triple check and quadruple check stuff, because you don&#39;t want an errant thing in there that will change the outcome of a backtest or a model.</p><p> JOHNSON: For sure, and I think actually, we all talk about AI and AI understanding and the models that you use and the combination of models is going to be really important, but honestly, I think the real competitive advantage is going to be, and this is why I think scale in asset management is so important, is the breadth and depth of the database.</p><p> So we have an investment data lake that is shared by our 18 individual investment teams. And so, you know, as they contribute, so maybe a team like our Global Macro team has 14 different feeds for its ESG framework. They come in, it scrubs centrally. Now that data is available to the other teams, right? And we think over time, it&#39;s going to be more about what unique data do you have that you can apply your models, it&#39;s going to be more and more important.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So let&#39;s talk a little bit about your leadership experience. Your timing was impeccable. You step into the CEO role February 2020. Thank goodness nothing was about to happen over the next three years. What was it like a month into the new gig and suddenly the world shuts down?</p><p> JOHNSON: Yeah, well, so I stepped in, I think February 11th, I think February 20th, we announced the acquisition of Legg Mason, which of course had been in the works …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: For quite a while, so we had good plans in place, and then about three weeks later, remember, we were going to flatten the curve with two weeks off …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yeah, that&#39;s right.</p><p> JOHNSON: And it turned into two years.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s just going to be — that was transitory, right?</p><p> JOHNSON: Yeah, that was transitory.</p><p> You know, you just deal with the cards that are in front of you, and the good news was, when I was running technology, I became very passionate because we had developers in India and kind of around the world, Poland and various places. And I felt like it was really important that you could see people when English was a second language. And so we pushed, I pushed the tech team to get desktop video. And so we had these devices, they were called a Tandberg device, and it sat separately on your desktop and we would do video calls. And so the company had been doing this for 20 years.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Zoom before Zoom.</p><p> JOHNSON: Yeah, exactly. And so we were comfortable. It was already part of our DNA to have meetings where inevitably somebody was on video. So it was already kind of how we operated. Now you had everybody on video.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: And I think the thing that I appreciated was actually people finally believed you can run businesses that way. And so in many ways we closed the Legg Mason deal two months early. And I think it was because we were in some ways more efficient by doing it via video, not everybody getting on an airplane and going and trying to work your calendars to go meet.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You know, the crazy unexpected benefit of the new post 9/11 rules was that everybody had to have backup systems. You couldn&#39;t just have everything in one location. I think the SEC promulgated those. And when people were suddenly forced to work from home, it was very easy to get, or relatively easy to get up and running, just an unexpected side effect of the new regulations that came in after we lost the Twin Towers.</p><p> It&#39;s who knew that the SEC can actually be so forward-looking, and hey, you know, it all worked out. We were all able to get up and running.</p><p> JOHNSON: Yes, for sure.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So were there any complications from all this remote work in your CEO transition, or you were in place when everything hit the fan and it was just a matter of tacking into the wind when the world changed?</p><p> JOHNSON: Yes, I mean, I wouldn&#39;t attribute anything in particular to that, I mean, when you do an acquisition, one of the most important things you do is assess talent and there&#39;s a bias towards your own talent and it&#39;s a missed opportunity if you don&#39;t infuse your organization with talent from the company you acquired. And so we were very focused on that. And sure, you&#39;d love to meet people in person versus doing Zoom interviews …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: But we had to do it that way. We ended up with, I think, two thirds of Legg Mason&#39;s corporate services groups came into Franklin Templeton and a big part of the distribution team became part of Franklin Templeton.</p><p> So you&#39;re trying to kind of build a best athlete. And it&#39;s not just a best athlete, it&#39;s the best team. So sometimes you&#39;re just trying to make sure the team will coalesce. And I think we did a pretty good job of that.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. You mentioned your dad. Let&#39;s talk about some leadership lessons. What did your father teach you about managing people, running a company, and getting all of the horses pulling the cart in the same direction?</p><p> JOHNSON: I mean, one of the things that my father has always said, “Take care of the client, “the business takes care of itself.” And so anytime there&#39;d be, and I still talk to him about things, you know…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Your dad is how old now?</p><p> JOHNSON: He just turned 90 in January.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And sharp as a tack, right?</p><p> JOHNSON: Absolutely.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s really, you got some good genes here that you&#39;re dealing with.</p><p> JOHNSON: Yeah, he&#39;s amazing. And so, you know, if you think about that and you overlay that in any decision, is this good for the client? Then I think that gives you a lot of clarity. It&#39;s kind of a North Star there.</p><p> And then I&#39;d say my dad is, you know, who&#39;s always incredibly fair to people, and he recognized that every person contributes to who we are as a company. When your call center employee picks up the phone and is talking to a client, they&#39;re shouldering the entire reputation of the firm on them with that client.</p><p> And my dad always understood that, and so there&#39;s just a genuine respect for everybody&#39;s contribution to the company. And I think that&#39;s part of our culture.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s really interesting.</p><p> You mentioned you took a slot from your sister when you first started at an entry level. I know one of your brothers was very involved with the firm. What&#39;s it like dealing with people that you have this familial personal relationship? How do you manage around that? I would think that&#39;s, I&#39;m just thinking about my own siblings and we would have killed each other and gone bankrupt long ago.</p><p> JOHNSON: Everybody asks me, is this succession? No, not in our family.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I wasn&#39;t even thinking about that. I&#39;m just talking about my own family and I know there would have been bloodshed, but how do you navigate that? It sounds challenging.</p><p> JOHNSON: There were definitely times where I&#39;d say to my brother, “Listen, stop. You can&#39;t treat me like your little sister in a meeting.”</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right. In front of other people.</p><p> JOHNSON: In front of other people, right. But you know what? As a family, we get along great and my brother and I get along great and he&#39;s still Executive Chairman today. And we talk about parts of the business, things that I&#39;m struggling with. I&#39;ll talk to him, I&#39;ll talk to my dad. And I got to tell you what a great privilege it is to be a CEO and have people who care so much like you do to be able to talk to about things that you&#39;re thinking about.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: You go to them for advice all the time?</p><p> JOHNSON: We&#39;ll talk about, before any acquisition is done, that&#39;s clearly part of the conversation, as well as my uncle. My uncle&#39;s still active in the firm, and so we&#39;ll have conversations about what we think. Does it make sense? And you know, it&#39;s just my father, my uncle, my brother will never say, “You have to do this.” They&#39;ll say, “Hear the thinking on it.” And my brother would say the same thing when he was CEO for 15 years. My father was a great resource, but never would tell you what to do.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting.</p><p> JOHNSON: And so it&#39;s nice to have those voices in the room, but in the end, the decision&#39;s mine as a CEO with my board and my management team. And they&#39;re just great advisors.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s great. I love the stock symbol, BEN.</p><p> JOHNSON: Yeah, me too.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I mean, so great. You talked earlier about long-termism versus short-termism. The family still owns like 40% of the outstanding shares.</p><p> JOHNSON: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Does that insulate you from the sort of short-term activist, what about this quarter&#39;s returns when you&#39;re making those long-term investments in technology? How does that affect how you navigate?</p><p> JOHNSON: Yeah, no, I mean for sure you&#39;re you the risk in asset management is that an activist comes in and says you know what why don&#39;t we spin off all these groups as we can get a bigger multiple for the alts business and you know various things and that is a short-term gain right and doesn&#39;t build a long sustainable business, so it&#39;s better to have that you know for — and I genuinely believe scale is going to be more and more important as I mentioned for things like data for asset managers and so building a long-term business is really important.</p><p> An activist doesn&#39;t take on a company that&#39;s got a 40% you know control because you can&#39;t get enough stock to be able to ultimately you know …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right there&#39;s 90% of the remaining 60, it&#39;s — so that does create a little bit of a buffer so you guys can think very long-term make acquisitions and make investments.</p><p> JOHNSON: Right.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: which other publicly traded companies might not have that luxury.</p><p> JOHNSON: Right and we are totally aligned with the shareholders because we&#39;re looking for the best outcome for the stock and again, sometimes that&#39;s making some investments today that you know pay off in a few years.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So, this is a ridiculous question but tell us about your next acquisition meaning I don&#39;t expect you to say we&#39;re going to pay X for this like what areas do you think are interesting where are you looking to say, “Hey, we can acquire some talent and some technology in this space?”</p><p> JOHNSON: So that with respect to kind of product gaps the only one that we really feel is out there as a gap is infrastructure. So if — interesting because we think there&#39;s going to be a lot of growth on the infrastructure.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: On the bond side or on the equity side?</p><p> JOHNSON: Probably equity but because we can do the on the private credit teams they can do it on the on the bond side, but it would be — that would be an area that would be interesting to us. We like local asset management. So you know we have clients in 155 countries. People tend to like home, they have a home country bias.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Sure.</p><p> JOHNSON: So you know 80% flows in India tend to go to domestic products. We were the first foreign manager in India and so we have local equity, local fixed income but we look for markets that made sense to us. We&#39;d be a buyer of a local asset management. We have them spattered throughout the world. And then as I mentioned on the distribution side, anything that builds that deeper relationship that can help us with distribution.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So I don&#39;t want to talk about politics. I want to talk about culture and environment. We&#39;re recording this. We have President Modi here in the US India seems to be like a perennial next economic powerhouse after China and it just always seems to be not catching that next bid. When you look at a region like that, and I don&#39;t want to just talk about India, but if you&#39;re looking at India, or you&#39;re looking at China, or you&#39;re looking at Taiwan, or Singapore, or Korea, or Vietnam, how do you think about building a presence in a place like that and developing a relationship, either building or acquiring a local entity?</p><p> Because how do you pick let&#39;s focus on this region over that region? It seems like it changes from week to week, month to month.</p><p> JOHNSON: It&#39;s going to matter the demographics of a country, the growth, the policies, the regulation, all those that go into the factors. I mean we were in India in 1995, we were in Taiwan in 1985, China first investments in 1988.</p><p> So you know we look at those, Asia&#39;s going to be, they say there&#39;s going to be a billion people who enter the middle class in the next decade and 87% of them are going to be in Asia. I lived in India for a little while when I was running the technology and operations group and I can tell you 56% of the population is under the age of 25. It&#39;s got a British legal system, a British education system, you know, while there&#39;s 23 different languages that are spoken and more dialects…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Everybody speaks English.</p><p> JOHNSON: You know, certainly you aspire to speak English, and so the people that you hire from colleges are all English speaking, so those are all great tailwinds for the economy. Many people say, you know, India grows at night when the government sleeps. I think Modi&#39;s been doing a really terrific job at, you know, trying to, you know, reduce the amount of kind of bureaucracy that&#39;s there.</p><p> I have to say that my observation, when I would be excited by all those statistics, Indians were the most skeptical about India. On my last trip it was a clear difference in view that in India — Indians and Indian Americans are really excited about what&#39;s going on.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: And the first time I found an optimism there that I hadn&#39;t really sensed before.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s so interesting because that&#39;s what I meant by they&#39;re perennially about to happen like they can very easily be on par with China in terms of their economic prowess, more along the lines on technology and software and other areas where clearly there&#39;s a huge, huge infrastructure there, and it just seems to like always be about to happen and never happens.</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, you know, they say there&#39;s six times the number of engineers that graduate in India every year than the US and I can tell you, you know, an Indian would prefer to go to an IIT than Harvard. They look at Harvard as a safety school.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: (LAUGHTER)</p><p> JOHNSON: I mean really and so …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: MIT though is really still very difficult.</p><p> JOHNSON: (LAUGHTER) But the IITs are pretty phenomenal, right?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And we end up, you know, importing a decent number of engineers from the best Indian schools. Is that still going on the way it used to?</p><p> JOHNSON: Well I think a lot of them are deciding that there&#39;s more opportunity even at It used to be they had to come to the US or Europe because that was going to be where the opportunity is.</p><p> RITHOLTZ:” Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: But now the domestic economy is growing so well that there&#39;s a lot of excitement. So there&#39;s less that are choosing to leave. And then I think China, a lot of discussion around China. China&#39;s, what&#39;s the US? 23% of world&#39;s GDP and China&#39;s 18%. The third is like Japan at 4.9.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: I mean, it&#39;s a big market and it&#39;s going to be important. And so, you know, we have a joint venture there, and we continue to, you know, invest in China.</p><p> But then there&#39;s other markets, you know, that you look at. There are 300 million people in Indonesia. If they get their policies right, it&#39;s going to be amazing growth. Vietnam, you know, another one. Capital markets are really tough there, but, you know, it should be a great opportunity in growth. And you see some of the supply chains people are diversifying. India is one of the beneficiaries of that. Vietnam&#39;s another beneficiary of that. Japan even in the case of semiconductors.</p><p> So I think there&#39;s just a lot going on there that is pretty interesting.</p><p> And then the Middle East is another amazing area.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes, they seem to be purposefully trying to morph their reliance away from crude oil and energy towards more modern technologies. How can you even think about making an investment in the Middle East on anything other than oil? That&#39;s no longer the case, right?</p><p> JOHNSON: Right, I mean I think what&#39;s interesting is they think like a generational family thinks, right? And so in their mind, oil runs out, I don&#39;t know, three generations, whatever it is, they want to reinvest in their economies to diversify it, to ensure that they&#39;re not out of money when that happens, right?</p><p> And I actually genuinely believe some of the greatest innovation on renewable energy is going to come out of places like Abu Dhabi and Saudi Arabia because they are investing in it and they have the balance sheet to be able to make those investments.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And keep in mind, oil isn&#39;t going to go away. It&#39;s just going to go away as an energy source, as a material science source. It&#39;s enormous. The old joke used to be, the Arab sheik says to the American businessmen, “We&#39;re selling you all this oil. We can&#39;t believe you guys burned this. You know what it&#39;s really good for. You can make it into a million different things.” And that&#39;s the future of oil, not energy, but materials. So you have confidence in what&#39;s going to take place in the Middle East. How does one invest into that region? If you&#39;re a retail investor, “Hey, I like the idea of India, I could go buy an ETF. I like the idea of Middle East, how do I invest in that?”</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, I think you got to spend a little time there and go see because I took my executive committee to the Middle East. We visited several countries there. And honestly, I think that many of them felt that we were going there to think about raising money from that region and came away thinking there are going to be investment opportunities there.</p><p> We actually acquired in 2007 a local asset management. I mentioned local asset management being important. So a local asset management team that&#39;s based, we&#39;ve been in Dubai about 20 years, and we&#39;re the largest, I think, multinational Sharia manager for Islamic finance, that came out of that local team. And so they do local GCC bonds and equity investments. So there&#39;s a lot of opportunity, I think, to invest there.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really quite fascinating.</p><p> So let&#39;s talk a little bit about what&#39;s going on in the world today. We&#39;ve seen this massive change in rate regimes. How does that affect your ability to run the firm? And how does it affect fund managers dealing with this sudden 500 basis point increase in rates.</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, I think the good news is that fixed income is now actually an asset class you want to be in and you can get returns.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Hey, look, we get yield.</p><p> JOHNSON: Isn&#39;t that exciting?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: We get yield, exactly.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Exciting.<br /> JOHNSON: And so, I think that&#39;s terrific, right? And then the other thing is volatility is good for active managers, right? It shows whether you have skill and we&#39;ve come off a decade where basically government&#39;s been pumping money into the system. If you didn&#39;t have access to private markets, you couldn&#39;t make any money in fixed income, so where&#39;d you go? You went into equities. It just exploded equities up and …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: What was that, 2010 to 2020? 14, 15% a year?</p><p> JOHNSON: Exactly.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s double normal.</p><p> JOHNSON: But it was hard. If you are an active manager, your job is to have a diversified portfolio and think about risk-adjusted returns.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: And when you have a momentum market like that and you have five companies that take 25% of the index or whatever it ended up being, a professional manager gets nervous by that type of concentration, say the S&amp;P 500. And there&#39;s not enough discussion about how the indexes, the market risk of the index changes depending on one, the day Tesla was added to the S&amp;P 500…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: It became a much riskier investment by investing the S&amp;P 500 based on volatility and concentration. And so in those types of market, It&#39;s hard for an active manager to actually beat that, but when you have volatility, that&#39;s when you start to see outperformance.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So let&#39;s talk about money market funds. Not only are you seeing some yield on fixed income products, money market funds used to yield nothing. Now you&#39;re actually seeing some returns, even though there&#39;s been some concerns about some of the regulation around money market funds the problem we had in the financial crisis.</p><p> What is Franklin Templeton doing in this space?</p><p> JOHNSON: Well first of all I don&#39;t think money market funds look anything like they did when you had problems and you just had a couple of …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Huge difference.正确的？ Huge difference.</p><p> JOHNSON: Huge difference. And so you know there&#39;s — if you have a certain amount of risk and you&#39;re a prime floating fund otherwise you&#39;re you know tied to the dollar and it&#39;s short duration and you know I think very secure and you know today you can get 5.5% percent in the money market fund, I mean that&#39;s pretty impressive.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right. Real money.</p><p> JOHNSON: And I think that we&#39;ve seen a lot of money flow into money market funds because people saw that they could get that and they weren&#39;t ready to get back into the market now. Having said that we&#39;re close to the end of the cycle you know …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Into the rate hike.</p><p> JOHNSON: The rate hike…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right, okay.</p><p> JOHNSON: You know I think the Fed is saying they&#39;re going to still raise more and I think you could see one to two more times that they raise this year.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: I think people are finally over the they&#39;re going to cut this year. I definitely don&#39;t think they&#39;re going to cut this year.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Those were the same people by the way who have been forecasting a recession for the past 18 months. So of course they think the feds going to cut. What I find fascinating about the whole Fed investor community thing is that Jay Powell keeps saying this is what I&#39;m going to do and nobody ignores him.正确的？ I mean go back 20 years you had no idea what the Fed was doing, he&#39;s telling you, nobody wants to believe him.</p><p> JOHNSON: You know why a huge percentage of fixed income managers have only lived through the time that the Fed bailed us out every time.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: Right and so they&#39;ve been in that and so they believe that that&#39;s going to be the response whereas people that have a little more experience like me, you.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> JOHNSON: we know that you can&#39;t always you know count on the Fed to bail you out and as a matter of fact, Jay Powell is trying to be very clear with it and the market keeps fighting the Fed and thinking they&#39;re going to call us bluff or something.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: (LAUGHTER)</p><p> JOHNSON: I think that the Fed is being very data-driven at this point and he&#39;s trying to make it clear that if the economy still remains pretty hot, he&#39;s going to raise rates further.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Here&#39;s a crazy stat that someone shared with me. If you were born after 1980 and you work in finance, you don&#39;t know what it was like when we had no idea what the Fed — I remember we used to look at the flow of funds report to try and tease out what might happen. Now the Fed says, “We&#39;re going to do this,” and then they go out and do it.</p><p> I&#39;m born before 1980, so this is all new to me. But imagine spending your whole career where, “Of course we&#39;re going to get bailed out by the Fed if that happens.” How do you recover from that as a professional if you&#39;ve never experienced wild market, I guess that isn&#39;t true because you have experienced wild market volatility, just the cavalry has always come to the rescue.</p><p> JOHNSON: That&#39;s right. I think that&#39;s right.</p><p> And I don&#39;t think that, you know, I don&#39;t think that the Fed is going to, as I said, I think the Fed is going to be very data-driven and right now, you know, unemployment is still, what is it, 3.7?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Very low, right, historically low levels.</p><p> JOHNSON: You&#39;re starting to see some labor participation coming back in a little bit. You know, look at, a lot of people say, is there going to be a recession or not? Look, there probably is.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Eventually.</p><p> JOHNSON: They have to, right? I mean, they have to cool it down. The question is, is it a deep recession that causes a lot of, we don&#39;t think, or at least I don&#39;t think, and by the way, we have five different fixed income teams at Franklin Templeton, so there are some different views on this, but that we&#39;ll have a deep recession.</p><p> But the Fed has definitely jammed on the brakes, and it&#39;s still been hard. The easy part was getting inflation from nine to five, four and a half, now&#39;s the real challenge.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So last PPI that came out had a three handle on it. CPI usually follows PPI. Jay Powell can put a flag in the ground, declare victory, take a long vacation. He&#39;s already won, right?</p><p> Am I oversimplifying that too much or can he just say, “All right, I&#39;m taking the summer off”?</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, I think the challenge for him is that they&#39;ve been very vocal about the 2% target.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Which is a little weird because 2% target was post-9/11, post-financial crisis, post-pandemic, rates were at zero and two percent was the upside target, maybe that target should be rethought, maybe three percent makes sense.</p><p> JOHNSON: So until we start to hear the Fed start talking about maybe they&#39;re going to change that target or lighten up on that target, I think it&#39;s tough for him to just take too long of a break. Sure, he can take the break through the summer.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yeah, take the summer off. Go fishing. They go to Jackson Hole. There&#39;s great fly fishing up there.</p><p> JOHNSON: There you go.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right? I mean, he could just chill out for a while.</p><p> All right, so I want to throw one curve ball at you.</p><p> JOHNSON: All right.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And as a West Coast girl, I got to ask you, you&#39;re on the board for the San Francisco Giants. What was that experience like?</p><p> JOHNSON: So I was, now my brother Greg is the control person at the Giants. Look at, it was a blast, I have to say. The thing that I learned, I think I know a little bit about baseball. I don&#39;t know anything about baseball. Baseball people talk about statisticians. They know every little …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: They&#39;re quants, they&#39;re all quants.</p><p> JOHNSON: This guy&#39;s going to move three feet with this pitcher who goes up. And so pretty quickly I realized I don&#39;t actually know that much about baseball. But I loved it, it was a lot of fun. And of course I was there as I teased my brother about when I was on the board we won three World Series. So what have you done?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right? What have you done, right? Exactly, that&#39;s hilarious.</p><p> JOHNSON: Meanwhile, he actually knows a lot about baseball and I don&#39;t.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s very funny. Just goes to show you that breadth of and depth knowledge doesn&#39;t necessarily help you win championships.</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, I think the key was, Jenny wasn&#39;t really involved in making too many decisions.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh, you weren&#39;t telling when to bring in the left hander? We need to switch pitchers? That wasn&#39;t part of your responsibilities?</p><p> All right, so I know I only have you for a little while. Let me jump to my favorite questions that we ask all our guests, starting with, tell us what you&#39;ve been keeping yourself entertained with. What are you watching or listening to these days?</p><p> JOHNSON: I just finished. I&#39;m always way behind on these things. So I just finished, I think it&#39;s called “Dead to Me” …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh sure.</p><p> JOHNSON: Which is a Netflix series. It&#39;s like a dark comedy …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Very good.</p><p> JOHNSON: But very good. It was funny. And I&#39;ve been watching a little bit of “Manifest.” That was one that …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I&#39;ve heard about “Manifest” I haven&#39;t seen it yet.</p><p> JOHNSON: So anyway, and then, you know, I love to watch, there&#39;s a streaming service called Curiosity Stream.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh sure.</p><p> JOHNSON: And you know, it&#39;s got great documentaries on science and history and stuff like that, so I tend to watch some things. I was trying to understand quantum computing and what it does, and quantum entanglement. And because from a tech standpoint …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Entanglement, spooky action at a distance, yeah.</p><p> JOHNSON: Exactly, and so you know, so …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Curiosity Stream has one of my favorite astronomy channels.</p><p> JOHNSON: I will check that out.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s really — they do like deep, crazy stuff and you just get lost in it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yeah, no, exactly. So I love watching that kind of thing. Huh, really interesting.</p><p> I know the answer, but I got to ask anyway. Tell us about your early mentors who helped shape your career.</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, my father is my early mentor and continues to be my greatest mentor. I feel incredibly blessed to have him and grateful. And like I said, he never tells you what to do, but he&#39;s always great if you ask. He&#39;s always great at giving you his opinion and really incredibly thoughtful.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. Let&#39;s talk about books.</p><p> JOHNSON: I have to say something about my mom for a second.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Go ahead, all right.</p><p> JOHNSON: Okay, so you got to understand, my mom had seven kids and then went back to Stanford Medical School.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Oh really?</p><p> JOHNSON: So while my dad was building Franklin, she was doing that and she&#39;s 87. They&#39;re amazing and you know, you had to be in a real partnership.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: How long did she practice for?</p><p> JOHNSON: Oh, I think she practiced probably 25 years.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Wow, after seven kids went to medical school. That&#39;s a hell of an accomplishment.</p><p> JOHNSON: I think she probably decided she needed a reason to be out of the house.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s very funny. Let&#39;s talk about books. What are some of your favorites and what are you reading right now?</p><p> JOHNSON: I am reading a book on Kissinger right now, but I think, you know …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: His book or someone else&#39;s biography?</p><p> JOHNSON: I&#39;m reading Walter Isaacson&#39;s book on Kissinger.</p><p> I loved his book on Steve Jobs.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Fascinating, really fascinating.</p><p> JOHNSON: A few of the books that he&#39;s done. So I like historical fiction and I like history books. Probably Ken Follett, I really enjoy historical fiction books. He had the ones from World War I, World War II. He&#39;s a great one called it&#39;s about the building of cathedrals. “Pillars of the Earth” I think it is.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Every one of his books could absolutely be a movie.正确的？ I mean they all are like a James Bond unwind. But by the way if you liked Isaacson&#39;s biography on Jobs, I&#39;m drawing a blank on his name is on the tip of my tongue. Did you see the book on the Wright Brothers? Oh David McCullough.</p><p> JOHNSON: Oh yeah, yeah.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So fascinating.</p><p> JOHNSON: Is it good on the Wright brothers? I haven&#39;t read that one. He&#39;s another one I&#39;m a big fan of.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right everything he writes it&#39;s just …</p><p> JOHNSON: Is amazing, yeah.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right? It&#39;s like he was there reporting on it and a hundred years forward.</p><p> JOHNSON: Exactly.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Just so much details.</p><p> JOHNSON: Yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Down to our final two questions. What sort of advice would you give to a recent college graduate who is interested in a career in either investment management or finance?</p><p> JOHNSON: You know, I feel like as an industry we don&#39;t do a good enough job at selling people and what we do. And I tell the story about, I have five kids and with my daughter, I was talking to my daughters and I said, “So are you going to join me in this industry?” And one of my daughters said, “No, mom, I want to do something that helps people.” I&#39;m like, “Are you kidding me? This industry is a great industry to help people.” You wouldn&#39;t have the vaccines that we had without the businesses that were out there that were investing and trying to find opportunities.</p><p> We help people, I say at Franklin Templeton, to achieve the most important financial goals of their life. And by the way, every goal, not every goal, most goals require some financial component.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Buy a house, retirement…</p><p> JOHNSON: Kids&#39; education, whatever.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right, down the line.</p><p> JOHNSON: So my first thing is to say this is just a great industry to be in if you want to make a difference and you want to help people. You think about some of the stuff on ESG, the kind of impact investing, those types of things. All of those things require money. And so one is it&#39;s a great industry. Two is go in and be just curious. Ask questions. Read. I always say to people, read the CEO&#39;s letter in an annual report if you want to know what&#39;s on your boss&#39;s mind, right? Because they&#39;re going to lay it out there and try to connect what you do to the bigger picture of whatever a company is.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. And our final question, what do you know about the world of investing today you wish you knew 35 years or so ago when you were first starting out?</p><p> JOHNSON: Well, I think the tenets that have always been important, which we talked about earlier, like diversification, get invested early, the value of compounding, dollar cost averaging, where you just keep committing, you know, and investing month after month after month. Those things get lost sometimes in the stories, and yet they&#39;re probably the most important things about investing.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really, really, really good stuff.</p><p> Jenny Johnson, thank you so much for being so generous with your time. This has just been delightful.</p><p> We have been speaking with Jenny Johnson. She is the CEO of Franklin Templeton.</p><p> If you enjoy this conversation, well, be sure and check out any of the 500 other such conversations we&#39;ve had over the past nine years. You can find those at iTunes, Spotify, YouTube, wherever you find your favorite podcast. You can sign up for my daily reading list at ritholtz.com. Follow me on Twitter @Ritholtz. Follow all of the Bloomberg family of podcasts on Twitter @podcast.</p><p> I would be remiss if I did not thank the crack team that helps put these conversations together. Each week, Atika Valbrun is my project manager, Justin Milliner is my audio engineer, Paris Wald is my producer, Sean Russo is my researcher.</p><p> I&#39;m Barry Ritholtz. You&#39;ve been listening to Masters in Business on Bloomberg Radio.</p><p> END</p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"> ~~~ </p><p></p><p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/transcript-jenny-johnson/">Transcript: Jenny Johnson, Franklin Templeton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Tuesday AM Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-tuesday-am-reads-433/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:30:52 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=315980 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> My-Tuesday morning train WFH reads: • When Will Interest Rates Really Start to Matter? For the longest time pundits predicted interest rates would go higher yet they did nothing but go lower year after year. Then when rates hit 0% it seemed like everyone assumed we would experience lower rates forever…just in time for rates…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-tuesday-am-reads-433/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-tuesday-am-reads-433/">10 Tuesday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> My-Tuesday morning<del>火车</del>WFH reads:</p><blockquote><p> • <strong>When Will Interest Rates Really Start to Matter?</strong> For the longest time pundits predicted interest rates would go higher yet they did nothing but go lower year after year. Then when rates hit 0% it seemed like everyone assumed we would experience lower rates forever…just in time for rates to rise higher than anyone thought was possible in such a short period of time. So it goes when it comes to the markets. ( <a href="https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/07/when-will-interest-rates-really-start-to-matter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A Wealth of Common Sense</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Five Ways the Bull Market Makes Investors</strong> : Nervous Investors can&#39;t stop looking over their shoulders for major risks looming in markets. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/five-ways-the-bull-market-makes-investors-nervous-2f0bf74c" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>Five Revealing Pictures</strong> : Professional money managers do well on their “slower”, buying decisions (actually well enough to beat benchmark portfolios!). It&#39;s on their “faster”, selling decisions that money mangers significantly underperform ( <a href="https://sapientcapital.com/insights/five-revealing-pictures/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sapient Capital</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Howard Marks on Taking the Temperature</strong> : “You know, looking back, I think my market calls have been about right.” The response: “That&#39;s because you did it 5 times in 50 years.” It struck me like an epiphany: Those five instances the markets were either crazily elevated or massively depressed, and as a result, I was able to recommend becoming more defensive or more aggressive with a good chance of being right. ( <a href="https://www.oaktreecapital.com/insights/memo/taking-the-temperature" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Oaktree Capital</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Taylor Swift Is Halfway Through Her Rerecording Project. It&#39;s Paid Off Big Time</strong> : The remaking of Swift&#39;s early discography, which includes her first six albums, has so far found success, with fans eager to listen to her new vocals, unpack its various easter eggs, and purchase new merchandise. Speak Now (Taylor&#39;s Version) is expected to debut at No. 1 on the Billboard 200 chart, which would give Swift the third-most No. 1 albums of any artist of all time, surpassing Barbra Streisand And Bruce Springsteen. ( <a href="https://time.com/6292599/taylor-swift-speak-now-rerecord-project/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Time</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How Fossil-Fuel-Owning Alts Managers Became Green-Energy Leaders</strong> : Firms like Brookfield and Carlyle are buying up polluters and promising to scrub them clean ( <a href="https://www.institutionalinvestor.com/article/2bw3keigpdk9nyf7hpts0/portfolio/how-fossil-fuel-owning-alts-managers-became-green-energy-leaders" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Institutional Investor</a> )</p><p> • <strong>2024 Rolls-Royce Spectre EV</strong> : RR introduces its first all-electric vehicle, as it plans to phase out ICE by 2030. ( <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-e/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Big Picture</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>Best Electric Vehicles of 2023 and 2024</strong> : We&#39;ve selected the best electric cars you can buy today that include a wide range of SUVs, hatchbacks, sedans, and even pickup trucks. ( <a href="https://www.caranddriver.com/features/g40322167/best-electric-cars/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Car and Driver</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Elon Musk Is Making Mark Zuckerberg Seem Cool Again</strong> : The Facebook co-founder is seizing the moment with a win after years of tumult ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/mark-zuckerberg-threads-twitter-elon-musk-ecec1eaa" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The Last Place on Earth Any Tourist Should Go: Take Antarctica off your travel bucket list</strong> . All of these attractions are getting harder to find in the rest of the world. They&#39;re disappearing in Antarctica too. The continent is melting; whole chunks are prematurely tumbling into the ocean. And more people than ever are in Antarctica because tourism is on a tear. ( <a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2023/07/antarctica-tourism-overcrowding-environmental-threat/674600/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Atlantic</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Investors Bought Nearly $1 Billion in Land Near a California Air Force Base. Officials Want to Know Who Exactly They Are</strong> . Flannery Associates&#39; purchases near Travis Air Force Base have alarmed local and federal officials . ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/investors-bought-nearly-1-billion-in-land-near-a-california-air-force-base-officials-want-to-know-who-exactly-they-are-fd868e38" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Turner Classic Movies Is a National Treasure</strong> : The channel has an astounding degree of control over a crucial part of American cinema. It should become a public resource available to all. ( <a href="https://www.newyorker.com/culture/cultural-comment/turner-classic-movies-is-a-national-treasure" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New Yorker</a> )</p></blockquote><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> this weekend with Franklin Templeton CEO Jenny Johnson, which manages $1.5 trillion dollar in client assets. She has worked at FT since 1988, and held leadership roles in investment management, distribution, technology, operations, and high-net-worth clients. Franklin Templeton oversees more than 9000 employees and 1300 investment professionals. Johnson is on the list of most powerful women (Barron&#39;s, Forbes, American Banker, and more). She has been CEO since February 2020.</p><p></p><p> <strong>There are now over 102 million Threads users</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316321" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m.png" alt="" width="700" height="268" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m.png 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m-300x115.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m-1024x392.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m-768x294.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m-250x96.png 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/100m-1536x588.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></a><br /> Source: <a href="https://www.quiverquant.com/threadstracker/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Quiverquant</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>Sign up for our reads-only mailing list here</em></a> .</p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/10-tuesday-am-reads-433/">10 Tuesday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> Ack! Twitter Account Hacked!</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/ack-twitter-account-hacked/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=316296 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> Out to dinner on a Saturday night, we come home late. I check my mail, see an email change request made to my Twitter account hours earlier (above). I click through the link to deny the request + say this isn&#39;t me, but it&#39;s too late: The e-mail associated with the account, the password,…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/ack-twitter-account-hacked/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/ack-twitter-account-hacked/">Ack! Twitter Account Hacked!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316297" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed.png" alt="" width="720" height="447" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed.png 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed-300x186.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed-1024x635.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed-768x477.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed-250x155.png 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/email-changed-1536x953.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p></p><p> Out to dinner on a Saturday night, we come home late. I check my mail, see an email change request made to my Twitter account hours earlier (above). I click through the link to deny the request + say this isn&#39;t me, but it&#39;s too late: The e-mail associated with the account, the password, and even the username have all been already changed.</p><p> I file a report, which generates a <em>Kafkaesque hellscape of automated e-mail loops</em> , none of which ever reach a human and none of which satisfactorily resolve the issue. The inquiry is closed (no action taken) and I get a lovely email asking me to rank the quality of the Twitter Support (Timeliness 8/10; Did we resolve the issue? 0/10).</p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/twtr-hack.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignright size-medium wp-image-316304" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/twtr-hack-208x300.png" alt="" width="208" height="300" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/twtr-hack-208x300.png 208w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/twtr-hack-710x1024.png 710w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/twtr-hack-768x1108.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/twtr-hack-250x361.png 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/twtr-hack.png 832w" sizes="(max-width: 208px) 100vw, 208px" /></a> I create a new account with @Barry_Ritholtz, then change it to my old Twitter handle (@Ritholtz), to make sure no one else can grab it. And I keep adding more info to the email response from Twitter Support.</p><p> So if you see this post, be aware that <a href="https://twitter.com/ritholtzwealths" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@RITHOLTZWEALTHS</a> is not me or the firm, it&#39;s the hackers, and that&#39;s not me posting racist crap or pushing shitcoins.</p><p> Over the 36 hours since the hack took place, Twitter Support has been an exercise in frustration. From the new account, I filed an impersonation report, noting that my account was hacked and the new account (@Ritholtz) is what I am using to access support. They asked for a government ID, so maybe that&#39;s a good sign.</p><p> If there is a silver lining, its that this led me to change lots of passwords, add two-factor authentication <sup>1</sup> (2FA) everywhere, and a separate digital authenticator.</p><p> I am way too addicted to Twitter as a news/research tool and need to find backups.</p><p> <em>In the meantime, if you would be so kind as to file an impersonation report for @RitholtzWealths it would be greatly appreciated . 。 。</em></p><p></p><p></p><p> __________<br /> 1. I had 2FA on Twitter until some genius thought removing it was a good marketing idea to sell monthly subscrtiptions.</p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/ack-twitter-account-hacked/">Ack! Twitter Account Hacked!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Monday AM Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/monday-am-reads-56/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=315867 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> My back-to-work morning train WFH reads: • What exactly is your problem with stock index concentration? Ever since artificial intelligence was invented eight months ago, people have been writing about the rising concentration of stock indices. The usual way to start is with an observation that the trillion-dollar IT club makes up approximately a quarter…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/monday-am-reads-56/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/monday-am-reads-56/">10 Monday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div class="pf-content"><p> My back-to-work morning<del>火车</del>WFH reads:</p></div></div><blockquote><p> • <strong>What exactly is your problem with stock index concentration?</strong> Ever since artificial intelligence was invented eight months ago, people have been writing about the rising concentration of stock indices. The usual way to start is with an observation that the trillion-dollar IT club makes up approximately a quarter of the S&amp;P 500 index by weight — because of AI hype, or possibly, the result of a rotation by investors after the same stocks sold off a year earlier. Everyone says this much concentration is bad, because obviously. But there&#39;s not much agreement as to the specific reasons for that badness. ( <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/13f34a3f-8dab-4797-8e40-e1436be9cd23" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Financial Times</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The New 1970s</strong> : The US is a confused, unsettled nation. But green shoots are quietly sprouting. ( <a href="https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/the-new-1970s" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Noahpinion</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Three Maintenance Philosophies Fought for Control of the Auto Industry</strong> : A fundamental question that will keep coming up is this: What are the best ways to design for maintenance? At the very beginning of the auto industry, no less than three radically different design-for-maintenance philosophies fought it out. One lost, but not because of maintenance issues. The other two won big by rejecting each other&#39;s approach to maintenance. ( <a href="https://books.worksinprogress.co/book/maintenance-of-everything/vehicles/three-maintenance-philosophies-fought-for-control-of-the-auto-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Works in Progress</a> )</p><p> • <strong>As Greedflation Starts to Fade, Wageflation Creeps In</strong> : Softer demand, more supply and rising labor costs all take the air out of profit margins. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-greedflation-starts-to-fade-wageflation-creeps-in-1adb7b9c" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Q and A with Robert McCauley on Manias, Panics, and Crashes: A History of Financial Crises</strong> : In 1978 Charles Kindleberger published what was to become the classic text on financial bubbles, Manias, Panics, and Crashes: A History of Financial Crises. Though Kindleberger died in 2003, his work has never seemed more relevant. Economists have described recent economic conditions as the “Everything Bubble,” where the prices of all asset classes are simultaneously overvalued. ( <a href="https://blogs.lse.ac.uk/lsereviewofbooks/2023/07/04/q-and-a-with-robert-mccauley-on-manias-panics-and-crashes-a-history-of-financial-crises/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">London School of Economics</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Meta&#39;s New Threads App Is Terrible. It Just Might Bury Twitter</strong> . It has one killer feature that&#39;s a nightmare for Elon Musk. after less than a day, a new warrior has taken the clear lead in the Twitter wars. It&#39;s Threads, the Twitter copycat from Meta. The app rolled out on Wednesday, and within seven hours, Mark Zuckerberg said it had cleared 10 million users. By Thursday morning, it was north of 30 million. (Zuckerberg and Meta are a bit more constrained than Musk in their ability to lie about the success of their initiatives because Meta is a public company and Musk&#39;s Twitter is not.) ( <a href="https://slate.com/technology/2023/07/threads-app-meta-review-twitter-musk-facebook-winner.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Slate</a> )</p><p> • <strong>As Downtowns Struggle, Businesses Learn to Love Bike Lanes</strong> : From Manhattan to San Francisco, the need to rethink the urban core is encouraging business improvement districts to change their tune on prioritizing cars. ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-07-06/in-bid-for-survival-business-districts-welcome-bikes-and-pedestrians" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CityLab</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Bitter rivals. Beloved friends. Survivors</strong> . After 50 years, Chris Evert and Martina Navratilova understand each other like no one else can. When cancer came, they knew where to turn. ( <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/interactive/2023/chris-evert-martina-navratilova-cancer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Washington Post</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Spider-Man&#39;s Pavitr Prabhakar, Based on Peter Parker, Drives India Wild</strong> : The world&#39;s most movie-crazed country is ecstatic over what&#39;s considered to be the first Indian superhero in an American blockbuster. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/spider-mans-pavitr-prabhakar-based-on-peter-parker-drives-india-wild-179508d2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The point of Shania Twain is to let her be Shania Twain</strong> : Even if her current concert tour isn&#39;t exactly what anyone might expect, the country-pop legend has defied odds for decades by doing exactly what she wants.  ( <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/arts-entertainment/2023/07/03/shania-twain-concert-tour-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Washington Post</a> )</p></blockquote><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> this weekend with <a href="https://www.franklintempleton.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Franklin Templeton</a> CEO Jenny Johnson, which manages $1.5 trillion dollar in client assets. She has worked at FT since 1988, and held leadership roles in investment management, distribution, technology, operations, and high-net-worth clients. Franklin Templeton oversees more than 9000 employees and 1300 investment professionals. Johnson is on the list of most powerful women (Barron&#39;s, Forbes, American Banker, and more). She has been CEO February 2020.</p><p> <strong>Used vehicles (2-6 years old), Weekly Wholesale + Retail Price Indexes</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wholesaleweekly.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316007" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wholesaleweekly.webp" alt="" width="600" height="367" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wholesaleweekly.webp 1400w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wholesaleweekly-300x184.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wholesaleweekly-1024x627.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wholesaleweekly-768x470.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wholesaleweekly-250x153.webp 250w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><br /> Source: <a href="https://www.blackbook.com/market-insights/market-insights-7-5-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Black Book</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>Sign up for our reads-only mailing list here</em></a> .</p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/monday-am-reads-56/">10 Monday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> Threads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/threads/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bob Lefsetz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sun, 09 Jul 2023 19:00:56 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=315961 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> Have you signed up yet? We haven&#39;t had this spirit here since 2006, when Facebook opened up to the general public. Or maybe 2010, with the launch of Instagram. Or 2017, with the launch of TikTok. Only this time it&#39;s different, we&#39;re not excited about a new platform because of the possibilities, but because of…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/threads/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/threads/">Threads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/threads-.webp"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-315965" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/threads-.webp" alt="" width="720" height="366" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/threads-.webp 1280w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/threads--300x152.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/threads--1024x520.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/threads--768x390.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/threads--250x127.webp 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a> </div><div></div><div data-test-id="message-body-container"><div class="I_ZkbNhI D_FY W_6D6F" data-test-id="message-view-body"><div></div><div class="X_6MGW"> Have you signed up yet? </div><div class="msg-body P_wpofO mq_AS" data-test-id="message-view-body-content"><div class="jb_0 X_6MGW N_6Fd5"><div id="yiv9352255008"><div><p> We haven&#39;t had this spirit here since 2006, when Facebook opened up to the general public. Or maybe 2010, with the launch of Instagram. Or 2017, with the launch of TikTok. Only this time it&#39;s different, we&#39;re not excited about a new platform because of the possibilities, but because of the hatred of the old platform, Twitter. We&#39;re seeking a refuge.It&#39;s all about community. In every vertical these days. That&#39;s the hardest lift, the biggest climb. It doesn&#39;t matter how good your idea is, it comes down to whether it spreads, whether you can build a fan/user base. It&#39;s nearly impossible to do. People are overwhelmed, they want less clutter, not more. And in a world split into narrow niches, they might not be interested in your vertical.</p><p> But we couldn&#39;t wait to sign up for Threads.我做到了。 I&#39;m eager. Because not only am I down on Elon Musk, I&#39;m down on the experience. Twitter has become less fulfilling, I don&#39;t need it as much, I&#39;m not nearly as addicted as I used to be, it&#39;s no longer the heartbeat of the world, it&#39;s been taken over by bro culture, a tiny sliver of society that most of us decry.</p><p> Elon Musk might have been good at getting ahead of the public, with PayPal and Tesla, but he&#39;s not good at actually living in the moment, with the rest of us. You see Musk&#39;s input is limited. What I mean is he doesn&#39;t have enough sources, he&#39;s living in an echo chamber. He believes the hype. He believes the problem with Twitter is freedom. He&#39;s become the hero of ignorant, alienated males, and that&#39;s a bad look. Furthermore, you fail upon launch, not when you&#39;re dealing with a mature platform. There was this insanity with check marks. You have to pay, or maybe you don&#39;t have to pay. Some people can post endless screeds. It&#39;s no longer a microblogging platform, it seems to be going backward to something like Blogger or LiveJournal. And we learned with Tumblr that you never alienate your core customers, whether it be users or advertisers, because it all depends upon community, you&#39;ve got to keep the eyeballs, otherwise you&#39;ve got nothing.</p><p> In other words, this is a maintenance mission as opposed to an innovative mission. You take what you&#39;ve got and tweak it, you don&#39;t trash it, throwing the essence overboard.</p><p> Steve Jobs believed in small teams. He thought they accomplished more than large teams. But he didn&#39;t believe in eliminating the team. It&#39;s one thing to be lean, it&#39;s another to be strapped. And in a world run by Millennial and Gen-Z values you don&#39;t want to abuse workers and not pay your bills. That&#39;s anathema to them, they hate you on principle, you&#39;ve got to assuage them first. You have to know who your customer is.</p><p> And then messing with the content… It&#39;s bad enough we have to see ads, now we don&#39;t even get to see the content we want to?</p><p> As for Zuckerberg… He&#39;s no prince, but we haven&#39;t heard anything about the metaverse in months. He seems to have pivoted, refocused, without trashing his past efforts. He&#39;s just moved on, like a band that made a bad album and now wants to recover, like Garth Brooks after he morphed into Chris Gaines.</p><p> And Facebook may have reduced head count, but the company went on a hiring spree over the last few years. The company is lean (and can we call it Facebook instead of Meta now?), but it still has enough person power to create and distribute.</p><p> Musk had nothing he could protect. Hell, you can build a microblogging platform on open source software. The lift is not that heavy. Why did he think he was immune? There&#39;s no secret code, no investment of so many dollars that no one can compete, all that Musk has is his audience, and people can abandon you on a dime. And you never really know what the public will do, but you can prepare for it.</p><p> Screw what the Supreme Court says, screw the Trumpists, most people don&#39;t want falsehoods on Twitter. They don&#39;t want conspiracy theories. They want a more pure site, they want SUPERVISION! Otherwise it&#39;s a cesspool, with a shouting match laid on top. This is kind of like gun laws. The right and the Supreme Court might want open carry of battle weapons, but most people do not. And in order for Twitter to succeed, it must appeal to most people. Or at least the people who were using it. In this case, the informed, educated elite. You went to Twitter for news, hard news, who let the nincompoops in?</p><p> So we want to get out.</p><p> That&#39;s what Threads offers.</p><p> This is why the Great Man strategy fails. Just because you&#39;re good in one thing does not mean you&#39;ll be good in another. Just because Musk can make and distribute electric cars does not mean he can run a successful app that interacts with the public at large. He&#39;s got no clue. Like we constantly hear we want businessmen in government. Well, first and foremost, we want more women, not men, and we want those experienced, who know the ropes, who are not learning on the fly. In other words, would you want a great lawyer to be your heart surgeon? Or vice versa? Never has expertise been denigrated so.</p><p> Not that the experts are not manipulative. This is what turns us off most about Twitter, Musk&#39;s manipulation, as if we can&#39;t see it. Under the banner of freedom he&#39;s limiting ours.</p><p> Turns out we need a microblogging platform. Quick, you smell smoke, is there a fire? The TV station won&#39;t tell you if there is a fire, nor will the radio station. They&#39;re further behind the curve than ever. No, for that you need the wisdom of the crowd, real time information, which is what Twitter provided, but we don&#39;t need to get it from Twitter. Assuming there are enough people contributing elsewhere.</p><p> And Twitter is not about catalog. It is not like Wikipedia, the inertia of the past locking in its power. To compete? You&#39;d have to recreate all that history, it&#39;s too much of an effort. But Tweets are essentially evanescent. It&#39;s Groundhog Day, over and over and over again. You&#39;re starting anew. What happened yesterday, even earlier this afternoon, might already be irrelevant. Almost nobody searches history on Twitter, and so much of it is just plain wrong. Twitter is where you go to see the story unfold, it&#39;s not where you go to read deep analysis after the fact.</p><p> And Zuckerberg never invented anything successful in his life. He refined Facebook. He purchased Instagram and WhatsApp, was beaten to the punch by TikTok and is now competing, poorly, with Reels.</p><p> But users don&#39;t have a problem with TikTok, they see no reason to move on. It&#39;s those not on TikTok who complain. Just like those not on Twitter complained about the cancellation of political figures and misinformation. It was all theory, in a relative vacuum, mostly horsesh*t. This is how bands built careers in the old days, not only with their music but the hatred by the oldsters and out of touch, it made them cool! You need to be cool to survive.</p><p> So Zuckerberg just copied Twitter. There&#39;s no protection of an idea. No reason he can&#39;t. Which is one of the positives of art, you can try and replicate it, but most times you cannot. You need vision, you need expertise…</p><p> The Threads story will be in the news for weeks now, maybe even months. I&#39;m betting on its success, but even if it doesn&#39;t make it another platform will arise, that&#39;s how much people are dissatisfied with Musk, maybe even hate him. All his faux pas are coming home to roost, and the limit to the number of tweets was just the cherry on top, the straw that broke the camel&#39;s back, enough already.</p><p> Let&#39;s be clear… The government is not in control of Twitter or Threads.</p><p> And if you run one of these outlets you must have a soft touch, because if you alienate the audience, you&#39;re toast.</p><p> And this is interesting because recently users have been happy with their apps, they haven&#39;t seen a need for replication. Which is why Walmart still has not toppled Amazon. Online one is enough.</p><p> Unless there&#39;s enough blowback.</p><p> My problem with Amazon is the ads, you can&#39;t find what you&#39;re looking for, and some of its business policies. If someone else had the inventory and delivery, I&#39;d switch. But it&#39;s a very heavy lift. Meanwhile, Jassy is about contracting as opposed to growing. Is now the time? When Amazon is under the microscope? We hate the company for so many reasons, it&#39;s anti-union, it disadvantages third party sellers, I could go on and on. It&#39;s like the record business, the labels thought people had no choice, then Napster came along and it turned out that people did have an option. And it took years for the labels to even see that the internet option was better for the consumer than ten tracks on an overpriced CD. In internet-land, you&#39;ve got to give the public what it wants.</p><p> This is the story of Zaslav. He too thinks he lives in a vacuum. Killing content for the tax write-off, taking the axe to TCM… The most forwarded story today is the one about the “GQ” story taken down: <a class="yiv9352255008url" href="https://wapo.st/3pE26M0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">wapo.st/3pE26M0</a> Zaslav is af*ucking out of touch idiot. Just like Musk. If Zaslav didn&#39;t think his sh*t didn&#39;t stink he&#39;d have been on the internet, would know how it works. YOU NEVER RESPOND TO BAD PRESS! BECAUSE NO ONE IS GONNA SEE IT! What was a nonstory is now a story. How come I know that and this guy making triple digit millions doesn&#39;t? Because he&#39;s out of touch, hanging with his buddies in Sun Valley instead of home on TikTok, where he can truly learn what his customers want.</p><p> Ignore the public at your peril. Take people&#39;s temperatures constantly. Don&#39;t bend to any whim, but you want to make an informed decision.</p><p> So what we&#39;ve got here now is an alienated press corps that is gonna have a field day reporting on Threads, adding to its user base and possible success. You may not care, but reporters do, they&#39;re addicted to Twitter, which means you&#39;re gonna have to hear about this Twitter/Threads battle ad infinitum.</p><p> At least we&#39;ve got a game.</p><p> We need something like this in politics.</p><p> But no, we&#39;re just supposed to believe in the aged Biden, we get no choice, no voice. But if they gave us one, someone younger who could stand up and debate and fight back, maybe people would get excited and rally around the candidate. Instead, we hate Trump and DeSantis and we&#39;re given no ammunition, we&#39;re supposed to shut up, we&#39;re told the experts know better, when they&#39;ve been wrong time and time again.</p><p> Like Elon Musk.</p><p> Turns out he wasn&#39;t an expert in social media.</p><p> GOOD RIDDANCE!</p><p>希望。</p></div><p> ~~~</p><p> Visit the <a class="gtrackexternal" href="http://lefsetz.com/wordpress/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">archive</a> :  http://lefsetz.com/wordpress/</p><div><p class="p1"> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="http://www.twitter.com/lefsetz" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@Lefsetz</a> http://www.twitter.com/lefsetz</p><p> If you would like to <a class="gtrackexternal" href="http://www.lefsetz.com/lists/?p=subscribe&amp;id=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">subscribe</a> to the LefsetzLetter</p><p></p></div></div></div></div></div></div><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/threads/">Threads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 2024 Rolls-Royce Spectre E</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-e/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sun, 09 Jul 2023 14:00:58 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Cars]]></category><category><![CDATA[Weekend]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=316045 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> The Spectre is Rolls-Royce&#39;s first all-electric car. The company has fully embraced EVs; all Rolls-Royce gasoline-powered models, including that glorious 6.75-liter V12, are being phased out, and the company says RR will be entirely electric by 2030. Car &amp; Driver called the Spectre a “Massive, Maximally Badass EV Super Coupe,” and that seems like a…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-e/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-e/">2024 Rolls-Royce Spectre E</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The <a href="https://www.rolls-roycemotorcars.com/en_US/showroom/spectre-in-detail.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spectre</a> is Rolls-Royce&#39;s first all-electric car.</p><p> The company has fully embraced EVs; all Rolls-Royce gasoline-powered models, including that glorious 6.75-liter V12, are being phased out, and the company says RR will be entirely electric by 2030. <a href="https://www.caranddriver.com/news/a41670551/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-revealed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Car &amp; Driver</a> called the Spectre a “ <em>Massive, Maximally Badass EV Super Coupe</em> ,” and that seems like a fitting description.</p><p> The Spectre&#39;s design appears based on the Rolls-Royce Wraith, which ends this model year. Design similarities include suicide doors, 4,796 LED stars in the Starlight Headliner, and a massive presence on the road (the Spectre is actually a bit larger than the Wraith). Get in, step on the brake, and the huge 5-foot door closes automatically — unlike the Wraith, which required you to push a button to close the door, like some kind of uncivilized barbarian.</p><p> Stats for the 2024 Rolls-Royce Spectre:</p><blockquote><p> <em>Powertrain</em> : Dual Separately Excited Synchronous Motors (BMW)<br /> <em>Output</em> : 584 Horsepower/664 Pound-Feet<br /> <em>Speed</em> : 0-60 MPH: 4.4 Seconds<br /> <em>Battery</em> : 102.0-kWh sourced (BMW)<br /> <em>Charge time</em> : 10% to 80% in 34 minutes (195 kW DC fast-charger)<br /> <em>Range</em> : 260 Miles<br /> <em>Drag Coefficient</em> : <a href="https://www.press.rolls-roycemotorcars.com/rolls-royce-motor-cars-pressclub/article/detail/T0366853EN/spirit-of-ecstasy-redesigned-for-most-aerodynamic-rolls-royce-ever?language=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener">0.25</a><br /> <em>Tech</em> : rear-wheel steering, automated emergency braking, lane-keeping assist, adaptive cruise control with lane-centering<br /> <em>Platform</em> : All-aluminum “Architecture of Luxury”<br /> <em>Dimensions</em> : 126.4-inch wheelbase, 215.6-inch long overall<br /> <em>Weight</em> : 6371 pounds<br /> <em>Missing</em> : 6.75-liter V12</p></blockquote><p> These go on sale in Q4 of 2023; if you wan ta Badass EV Super Coupe, better get in line — <a href="https://insideevs.com/news/632650/rolls-royce-spectre-order-intake-far-better-than-expected-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">demand</a> for these suggests that these may soon sell out. But if you want to enjoy one of these magic carpet rides, it ain&#39;t gonna be cheap: No one will be buying the base versions of these at $420,000, customized and optioned, these will end up with MSRPs north of $500k. That is a lot of moolah, but at least you won&#39;t be leaving a plume of exhaust behind as you waft along…</p><p></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316063" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="440" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2.jpeg 980w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2-300x183.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2-768x469.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2-250x153.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-2.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316064" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-2.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="441" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-2.jpeg 980w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-2-300x184.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-2-768x470.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-2-250x153.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-scaled.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316208" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-scaled.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-scaled.webp 2560w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-250x141.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/34s-2048x1152.webp 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316231" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="480" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1.jpeg 1600w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1-1024x682.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1-250x167.jpeg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-int-1-1536x1023.jpeg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-scaled.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316206" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-scaled.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-scaled.webp 2560w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-250x141.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/dash-2048x1152.webp 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-2.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316065" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-2.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="440" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-2.jpeg 980w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-2-300x183.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-2-768x469.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-2-250x153.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316229" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="480" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats.jpeg 1600w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats-1024x682.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats-250x167.jpeg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/back-seats-1536x1023.jpeg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316230" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2.jpg" alt="" width="720" height="480" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2.jpg 1600w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2-300x200.jpg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2-1024x682.jpg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2-768x512.jpg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2-250x167.jpg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rear-seats-2-1536x1023.jpg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316048" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1.webp 1920w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1-250x141.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3-1-1536x864.webp 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316051" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1.webp 1920w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1-250x141.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1-1536x864.webp 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316052" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7.webp 1920w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-250x141.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-1536x864.webp 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316054" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2.webp 1280w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-2-250x141.webp 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316055" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2.jpeg 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-250x141.jpeg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1536x864.jpeg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316056" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4.jpeg 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-250x141.jpeg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1536x864.jpeg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316057" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5.jpeg 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-250x141.jpeg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-1536x864.jpeg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316058" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6.jpeg 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-250x141.jpeg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6-1536x864.jpeg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316059" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7.jpeg 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-250x141.jpeg 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7-1536x864.jpeg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> Source: <a href="https://www.rolls-roycemotorcars.com/en_US/showroom/spectre-in-motion.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rolls-Royce</a></p><p> Additional Sources: <a href="https://insideevs.com/reviews/674936/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-first-drive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Inside EVs</a> , <a href="https://www.roadandtrack.com/reviews/a44452462/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-is-exactly-what-youd-expect-an-electric-rolls-to-be/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Road &amp; Track</a> , <a href="https://www.caranddriver.com/news/a41670551/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-revealed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Car and Driver</a> , <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-review-electrified-at-last-45414642" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> </p><p></p><p><span id="more-316045"></span></p><p></p><div class="rich-text"><div class="js-rrmc-rich-text" data-lazy-load-class="rich-text-lazy-load"><div class="rrmc-component-grid-container rrmc-rich-text rrmc-rich-text-six-col rrmc-rich-text-centre-align "><div class="rrmc-rich-text-wrapper"><div class="rrmc-rich-text-paragraph-container rrmc-rich-text-body-standard"><p> <a href="https://www.rolls-roycemotorcars.com/en_US/showroom/spectre-in-motion.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rolls-Royce</a> :</p><blockquote><p> SPECTRE&#39;S DRIVE DELIVERS THE SEEMINGLY IMPOSSIBLE</p><p> “Spectre&#39;s drive is uncompromising; it is an experience only ever realised by Rolls-Royce. Built upon the Architecture of Luxury — a custom platform that enables adaptive engineering and peerless ride quality — it combines agile performance with the marque&#39;s signature magic carpet ride. Experience a seamless blend of performance and control. </p><div class="rich-text"><div class="js-rrmc-rich-text" data-lazy-load-class="rich-text-lazy-load"><div class="rrmc-component-grid-container rrmc-rich-text rrmc-rich-text-six-col rrmc-rich-text-centre-align "><div class="rrmc-rich-text-wrapper"><div class="rrmc-rich-text-paragraph-container rrmc-rich-text-body-standard"><p> THE APEX OF ATHLETICISM AND ELEGANCE</p><p> Spectre is a hallmark of dazzling power and presence. The world&#39;s first Ultra-Luxury Electric Super Coupé is engineered with precise handling and a fast-accelerating drive. This dynamism is matched with effortless performance and spectacular comfort.</p><p> SPIRIT, ELECTRIFIED </p><div class="rich-text"><div class="js-rrmc-rich-text" data-lazy-load-class="rich-text-lazy-load"><div class="rrmc-component-grid-container rrmc-rich-text rrmc-rich-text-six-col rrmc-rich-text-centre-align "><div class="rrmc-rich-text-wrapper"><div class="rrmc-rich-text-paragraph-container rrmc-rich-text-body-standard"><p> The formidable fastback establishes electrification as the marque&#39;s perfect pairing. Combining luxurious silence with powerful poise, it is exquisite — an experience in a league of its own. </p></div></div></div></div></div><div class="spacer"></div></div></div></div></div></div><div class="spacer"></div></blockquote></div></div></div></div></div><div class="spacer"></div><p></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316060" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="479" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1.jpeg 1050w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1024x682.jpeg 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-768x511.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-250x166.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316061" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="544" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1.jpeg 980w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-300x227.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-768x580.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-250x189.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316062" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="480" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1.jpeg 980w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-250x167.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316046" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1.webp 1920w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-250x141.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-1-1536x864.webp 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316047" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1.webp" alt="" width="720" height="405" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1.webp 1920w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-250x141.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2-1-1536x864.webp 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316049" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1.webp" alt="" width="720" height="323" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1.webp 1920w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1-300x134.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1-1024x459.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1-768x344.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1-250x112.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-1-1536x688.webp 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2.webp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316050" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2.webp" alt="" width="720" height="584" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2.webp 1920w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2-300x243.webp 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2-1024x830.webp 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2-768x623.webp 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2-250x203.webp 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5-2-1536x1246.webp 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></a></p><p></p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/2024-rolls-royce-spectre-e/">2024 Rolls-Royce Spectre E</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Sunday Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/sunday-reads-331/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:30:55 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=315411 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> Avert your eyes! My Sunday morning look at incompetency, corruption and policy failures: • Lessons From the Catastrophic Failure of the Metaverse: Did the “creative class” learn anything from buying into a product that was obviously destined to flop? (The Nation) • How China Came to Dominate the World&#39;s Largest Nickel Source for Electric Cars: Chinese firms…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/sunday-reads-331/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/sunday-reads-331/">10 Sunday Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Avert your eyes! My <em>Sunday morning</em> look at incompetency, corruption and policy failures:</p><blockquote><p> • <strong>Lessons From the Catastrophic Failure of the Metaverse</strong> : Did the “creative class” learn anything from buying into a product that was obviously destined to flop? ( <a href="https://www.thenation.com/article/culture/metaverse-zuckerberg-pr-hype/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Nation</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How China Came to Dominate the World&#39;s Largest Nickel Source for Electric Cars</strong> : Chinese firms mastered a process that unlocked Indonesia&#39;s ore for use in making EV batteries. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-china-came-to-dominate-the-worlds-largest-nickel-source-for-electric-cars-4c081a12" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Those 10,000 5-star reviews are fake. Now they&#39;ll also be illegal</strong> . The FTC has proposed new rules that clarify what is and isn&#39;t a deceptive online review — and would give it the power to fine $50,000 for each fake. ( <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/06/30/fake-reviews-online-ftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Washington Post</a> )</p><p> • <strong>A Drug for Itchy Dogs Costs $1,200. Why Is the Human Equivalent $43,000?</strong> What a shot that treats pet eczema reveals about how pharma companies actually price their drugs. ( <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/drug-costs-pricing-dogs-humans-1479e10e" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barron&#39;s</a> )</p><p> • <strong>New York State Built Elon Musk a $1 Billion Factory. &#39;It Was a Bad Deal.&#39;</strong> New Tesla facility in Buffalo was supposed to house a huge solar-panel operation, but the project hasn&#39;t turned out as planned. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musk-tesla-buffalo-new-york-solar-plant-1b634b9e" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>David Zaslav kills everything he touches, including GQ:</strong> Zaslav is the man in charge of frankencorp Warner Bros. Discovery and, in an impressively short period of time, has managed to f—k up nearly everything within its considerable portfolio. Freelance writer Jason Bailey attempted to note all of those f—k-ups for posterity just this week, when he wrote an article for GQ excoriating Zaslav for his pathetic stewardship of WBD. It noted all of Zaslav&#39;s lowlights, which I will repeat here for reasons that will soon become evident. SFGATE columnist Drew Magary unpacks the latest in the saga of the HBO-slayer. ( <a href="https://www.sfgate.com/sf-culture/article/david-zaslav-gq-article-18186324.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SF Gate</a> )</p><p> • <strong>What Makes Putin and the World&#39;s Autocrats So Resilient?</strong> Regimes are cooperating more closely to withstand diplomatic pressure from the West. ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/what-makes-putin-and-the-worlds-autocrats-so-resilient-b89c19de" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • &#39; <strong>Thanks for visiting Florida&#39;: one Black family&#39;s road trip to a &#39;hostile&#39; tourist trap</strong> : The NAACP has issued a warning about the state. But being Black in America was a long-odds game well before DeSantis showed up. ( <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/jul/05/florida-naacp-black-americans-race-politics" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Guardian</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How Trump has flaunted sensitive information: A history</strong> : Donald Trump&#39;s former White House press secretary says she witnessed him showing off such information at Mar-a-Lago. Here&#39;s how the allegation fits into his long record. ( <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/07/03/trump-classified-documents-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Washington Post</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>4 revelations from the latest unsealed records in the Trump classified documents case</strong> : Security footage, unwitting lawyers, and more details in the Mar-a-Lago search warrant affidavit reveal how prosecutors built their case against Trump. ( <a href="https://www.vox.com/2023/7/6/23786135/trump-classified-documents-affidavit-security-footage" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vox</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Inside Moms for Liberty&#39;s summit</strong> : Big money and even bigger conspiracy theories Manufacturing terror to mobilize parents and take over your kids&#39; school. ( <a href="https://www.mediamatters.org/moms-liberty/inside-moms-libertys-summit-big-money-and-even-bigger-conspiracy-theories" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Media Matters</a> )</p></blockquote><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> this weekend with <a href="https://www.franklintempleton.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Franklin Templeton</a> CEO Jenny Johnson, which manages $1.5 trillion dollar in client assets. She has worked at FT since 1988, and held leadership roles in investment management, distribution, technology, operations, and high-net-worth clients. Franklin Templeton oversees more than 9000 employees and 1300 investment professionals. Johnson is on the list of most powerful women (Barron&#39;s, Forbes, American Banker, and more). She has been CEO February 2020.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Signs of Frustration With the Two-Party System</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/frustration.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-298812" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/frustration.png" alt="" width="650" height="608" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/frustration.png 840w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/frustration-300x281.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/frustration-768x719.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/frustration-250x234.png 250w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" /></a></p><p> Source: <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/politics/2022/08/09/as-partisan-hostility-grows-signs-of-frustration-with-the-two-party-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pew Research Center</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>Sign up for our reads-only mailing list here</em></a> .</p><p> ~~~</p><p> To learn how these reads are assembled each day, <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2016/08/assemble-daily-reads-3-ez-steps/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>please see this</em></a> .</p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/sunday-reads-331/">10 Sunday Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> MiB: Jenny Johnson, Franklin Templeton CEO</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/mib-jenny-johnson/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sat, 08 Jul 2023 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mutual Funds]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=316151 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>﻿   This week, for our special 500th episode of Masters in Business, I speak with Jenny Johnson, president and chief executive officer of the Franklin Templeton. Johnson joined the firm in 1988 and held leadership roles in all its major divisions before becoming CEO in February 2020. She also led the historic acquisition of…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/mib-jenny-johnson/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/mib-jenny-johnson/">MiB: Jenny Johnson, Franklin Templeton CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm/id730188152?i=1000619921102" height="175" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"> <span data-mce-type="bookmark" style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span></iframe></p><p></p><p>This week, for our special <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/500/">500th episode</a> of Masters in Business, I speak with Jenny Johnson, president and chief executive officer of the <a href="https://www.franklintempleton.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Franklin Templeton</a> . Johnson joined the firm in 1988 and held leadership roles in all its major divisions before becoming CEO in February 2020. She also led the historic acquisition of Legg Mason in 2020, and Putnam in 2023, with the organization now managing more than $1.5 trillion globally. Among many other accolades, she has been named to Barron&#39;s list of the 100 most influential women in US finance for three consecutive years, most recently in 2022.</p><p> She began at Drexel Burnam, getting her feet wet learning operations as a very junior employee. When she returned to Franklin Templeton, she rotated through various divisions, including investment management, distribution, technology, operations, and high-net-worth.</p><p> There is a history of acquisitions at FT, going back to the October 1992 acquisition of <em>Templeton, Galbraith &amp; Hansberger</em> for $913 million. (This led to the firm&#39;s current name from its prior “Franklin”). Bringing on mutual fund pioneers Sir John Templeton + John Galbraith led to a critical mass at the firm.</p><p> Johnson has since led multiple acquisitions, including the 2020 all-cash deal for Legg Mason valued at $4.5 billion; Last year, FT purchased O&#39;Shaugnessy Asset management, including its breakout direct indexing product Canvas, for an undisclosed amount; this year, FT purchased Putnam for $925 million. Each of the acquisitions filled in a hole in Franklin&#39;s suite of products. The firm continues to expand, looking abroad for more growth, including India and the Middle East.</p><p> We also discussed active management versus indexing:</p><blockquote><p> “If you are an active manager, your job is to have a diversified portfolio and think about risk-adjusted returns. When you have a momentum market [like now] and you have five companies that take their 25% of the index, a professional manager gets nervous by that type of concentration, say the S&amp;P 500. There&#39;s not enough discussion about how the market risk of the index changes depending on [a few stocks]. The day Tesla was added to the S&amp;P 500, it became a much riskier investment based on volatility and concentration. In those types of markets, it&#39;s hard for an active manager.”</p></blockquote><p> A list of her favorite books <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/mib-jenny-johnson/#more-316151">is here</a> ; A transcript of our conversation is <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/transcript-jenny-johnson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">available here</a> Tuesday.</p><p> You can stream and download our full conversation, including any podcast extras, on <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm/id730188152?i=1000619921102" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5LGxKlY6fzXS3tGsjB23Cb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business/episode/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm-305087344" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> , <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvZTczYzk5OGUtNmU2MC00MzJmLTg2MTAtYWUyMTAxNDBjNWIxLzRlNGNkOTEwLTQwYTEtNDYxOS1hNWYzLWFlMmIwMDEyZmZmZi81ODczYTNjYi0yOThmLTQwYmMtYjcxZi1hZTJiMDAxMzAwMGQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> , <a href="https://youtu.be/jO_CfgjAQak" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> , and <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2023-07-07/jenny-johnson-on-managing-a-trillion-dollar-firm-podcast" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a> . All of our earlier podcasts on your favorite pod hosts can be <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">found here</a> .</p><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> next week with Tom Wagner, Co-Portfolio Manager at <a href="https://www.knighthead.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Knighthead Capital</a> . The $10 billion event-driven is a deep value-focused investor specializing in companies that need financial and operational restructuring. He is a co-investor with football legend Tom Brady in several sports assets, including a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-12/why-a-hedge-fund-manager-is-betting-on-pickleball-with-tom-brady#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pickleball team</a> , <a href="https://theathletic.com/4498330/2023/05/08/tom-wagner-birmingham-city/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Birmingham City FC</a> in the English Football League, and an endurance auto racing team. Wagner began his career doing hedge fund accounting at Ernst &amp; Young.</p><p></p><p><span id="more-316151"></span></p><p></p><h3> Jenny Johnson Current Reading</h3><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0743286979/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kissinger: A Biography</a></strong> by Walter Isaacson<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0743286979/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316011" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kissinger.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="377" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kissinger.jpg 331w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kissinger-199x300.jpg 199w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kissinger-250x377.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1451648537/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Steve Jobs</a></strong> by Walter Isaacson<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1451648537/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316012" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/stevejobs.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="380" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/stevejobs.jpg 328w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/stevejobs-197x300.jpg 197w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/stevejobs-250x380.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/9526529030/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ken Follett Century Trilogy War Stories Collection 3 Books Set (Fall of Giants, Winter of the World , Edge of Eternity)</a></strong> by Ken Follett<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/9526529030/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316013" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/follett.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="360" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/follett.jpeg 347w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/follett-209x300.jpeg 209w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/follett-250x360.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0451488334/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Pillars of the Earth</a></strong> by Ken Follett<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0451488334/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316014" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pillars.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="377" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pillars.jpg 331w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pillars-199x300.jpg 199w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pillars-250x377.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/mib-jenny-johnson/">MiB: Jenny Johnson, Franklin Templeton CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Weekend Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/weekend-reads-571/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sat, 08 Jul 2023 10:30:17 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=315352 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> The weekend is here! Pour yourself a mug of  coffee, grab a seat outside, and get ready for our longer-form weekend reads: • The Physics of Kaizen: Why Somebody Should Get Credit for Fixing Problems That Never Happened: Toyota&#39;s culture of Kaizen: continuous improvement. It is an obvious statement: companies should be continually improving. Companies…</p><p> <a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/weekend-reads-571/">Read More<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/weekend-reads-571/">10 Weekend Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The weekend is here! Pour yourself a mug of  coffee, grab a seat outside, and get ready for our longer-form weekend reads:</p><blockquote><p> • <strong>The Physics of Kaizen: Why Somebody Should Get Credit for Fixing Problems That Never Happened</strong> : Toyota&#39;s culture of Kaizen: continuous improvement. It is an obvious statement: companies should be continually improving. Companies that are able to successfully adopt a culture and practice of Kaizen have the ability to establish a dominant position in their market. ( <a href="https://taylorpearson.me/kaizen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Taylor Pearson</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The $100 billion bet that a postindustrial US city can reinvent itself as a high-tech hub</strong> : Can a massive infusion of money for making computer chips transform the economy of Syracuse and show us how to rebuild the nation&#39;s industrial base? ( <a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2023/07/06/1075817/micron-syracuse-chips-economic-development-technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MIT Technology Review</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How to Do Great Work</strong> : If you collected lists of techniques for doing great work in a lot of different fields, what would the intersection look like? I decided to find out by making it. Partly my goal was to create a guide that could be used by someone working in any field. But I was also curious about the shape of the intersection. And one thing this exercise shows is that it does have a definite shape; it&#39;s not just a point labelled “work hard.” The following recipe assumes you&#39;re very ambitious. ( <a href="http://paulgraham.com/greatwork.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Paul Graham</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How to Make Money by Losing $300,000 a Year on Slot Machines</strong> : Millions of people tune in to see others tackle the casino mainstay. &#39;It&#39;s fun to watch somebody else play with their money while you&#39;re sitting on your couch drinking a beer.&#39; ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/gambling-watching-slot-machines-online-9bfc1345" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Inside the AI Factory</strong> : As the technology becomes ubiquitous, a vast tasker underclass is emerging — and not going anywhere. ( <a href="https://www.theverge.com/features/23764584/ai-artificial-intelligence-data-notation-labor-scale-surge-remotasks-openai-chatbots" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Verge</a> )</p><p> • <strong>How Tom Brady&#39;s Crypto Ambitions Collided With Reality</strong> : The superstar quarterback is among the celebrities dealing with the fallout from the crypto crash. Others, like Taylor Swift, escaped. ( <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/06/technology/tom-brady-crypto-ftx.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York Times</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Walmart Is Quietly Growing Into an E-Retail Tech Titan</strong> . The world&#39;s biggest retailer stumbled in the early innings of the e-commerce revolution. Now that Walmart has found its footing, it&#39;s poised for big profits. The Stock Is a Buy. ( <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/buy-walmart-stock-price-pick-b2f6a90f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barron&#39;s</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The Big Penis War</strong> : The inventor of the world&#39;s first cosmetic penile implant says a group of Houston doctors is trying to steal his ideas. Inside the multimillion-dollar feud. ( <a href="https://www.texasmonthly.com/news-politics/penis-implant-lawsuit-penuma/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Texas Monthly</a> )</p><p> • <strong>A New Map of the Universe, Painted With Cosmic Neutrinos</strong> : Physicists finally know where at least some of these high-energy particles come from, which helps make the neutrinos useful for exploring fundamental physics. ( <a href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/a-new-map-of-the-universe-painted-with-cosmic-neutrinos-20230629/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Quanta Magazine</a> )</p><p> • <b>Shattered Nerves, Sleepless Nights: Pickleball Noise Is Driving Everyone Nuts</b> : The incessant pop-pop-pop of the fast-growing sport has brought on a nationwide scourge of unneighborly clashes, petitions, calls to the police and lawsuits, with no solution in sight. ( <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/06/30/sports/pickleball-noise-complaints-lawsuits.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York Times</a> )</p></blockquote><p> Be sure to check out our <a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">Masters in Business</a> this weekend with <a href="https://www.franklintempleton.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Franklin Templeton</a> CEO Jenny Johnson, which manages $1.5 trillion dollar in client assets. She has worked at FT since 1988, and held leadership roles in investment management, distribution, technology, operations, and high-net-worth clients. Franklin Templeton oversees more than 9000 employees and 1300 investment professionals. Johnson is on the list of most powerful women (Barron&#39;s, Forbes, American Banker, and more). She has been CEO February 2020.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Imploding breadth is historically ultra-bullish</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-315926" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding.png" alt="" width="700" height="394" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding.png 1800w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding-300x169.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding-1024x576.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding-768x432.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding-250x141.png 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/imploding-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></a><br /> Source: <a href="https://nypost.com/2023/07/02/bad-breadth-is-the-latest-ridiculous-reason-naysayers-insist-stocks-are-doomed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York Post</a></p><p></p><p></p><div><div class="pf-content"><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>Sign up for our reads-only mailing list here</em></a> .</p><p> ~~~</p><p> To learn how these reads are assembled each day, <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2016/08/assemble-daily-reads-3-ez-steps/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>please see this</em></a> .</p></div></div><p></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/07/weekend-reads-571/">10 Weekend Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>