<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>大局观</title><atom:link href="https://ritholtz.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://ritholtz.com<description>资本市场、经济、地缘政治、科技、数字媒体的宏观视角</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 8 月 30 日星期三 02:38:44 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title> 10 周三上午阅读</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-wednesday-am-reads-345/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 10:30:06 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318845 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>我周中早上的火车上写着： • 习近平让中国破产了吗？终于可以想象一个后共产主义政权了。 (UnHerd) • 疫情以非常不同的方式改变了美国最大的市中心：虽然公交客流量和市中心餐饮全面受到重创，但美国各地新的通勤模式和零售支出差异很大……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-wednesday-am-reads-345/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-wednesday-am-reads-345/">周三上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>我周中早上的火车上写着：</p><blockquote><p> •<strong>习近平让中国破产了吗？</strong>终于可以想象一个后共产主义政权了。 （ <a href="https://unherd.com/2023/08/has-xi-jinping-bankrupted-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">取消群聚</a>）</p><p> •<strong>疫情以截然不同的方式改变了美国最大的市中心</strong>：虽然公交客流量和市中心餐饮全面受到重创，但美国各地新的通勤模式和零售支出差异很大。 （ <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-08-28/covid-19-transformed-america-s-downtowns-and-public-transit" target="_blank" rel="noopener">城市实验室</a>）</p><p> • <strong>Larry Summers 对 2013-23 年通货膨胀与 1966-76 年通货膨胀的比较是无知的疯狂</strong>：Larry Summers 关于通货膨胀的错误有多么令人难以置信？ 2022年6月，他表示“我们需要5年失业率高于5%才能遏制通胀，2年失业率达到7.5%，或者5年失业率达到6%，或者1年失业率达到10%”，这只是为了遏制通胀，而不是降低通胀率。它。但当时CPI年通胀率为9.7%，现在为2.7%。 （ <a href="https://www.cato.org/blog/larry-summers-comparison-2013-23-inflation-1966-76-uninformed-madness-6" target="_blank" rel="noopener">卡托研究所</a>）</p><p> •<strong>退休的演变</strong>：没有人确切知道未来几十年要存多少钱。没有人知道金融市场的回报、利率或通货膨胀将会如何。没有人知道他们的消费习惯、生活方式或收入在职业生涯中会发生怎样的变化。没有人知道生活什么时候总会给他们带来一个曲线球。 （ <a href="https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/08/the-evolution-of-retirement/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">丰富的常识</a>）</p><p> •<strong>最后一次总是发生在现在</strong>：您总是知道什么时候是第一次做某事，但您几乎永远不知道什么时候是最后一次做某事。 （ <a href="https://www.raptitude.com/2021/09/the-last-time-always-happens-now/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">狂喜</a>）</p><p> •<strong>雅虎如何在新东家的带领下实现复兴</strong>：雅虎在 2021 年被 Verizon 出售给阿波罗全球管理公司时，差点就死掉了。在新东家的领导下，这家成立于 1994 年 1 月的公司获得了一次难得的重塑自我的机会。 （ <a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/08/29/yahoo-apollo-renaissance-jim-lanzone" target="_blank" rel="noopener">阿克西奥斯</a>）</p><p> •<strong>人工智能革命即将到来。但并不像某些人想象的那么快</strong>。从蒸汽动力到互联网，各行业和经济的技术发明和采用之间一直存在滞后。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/08/29/technology/ai-revolution-time.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>由于气候变化，年轻人感觉自己没有未来；我们需要改变这种说法</strong>：超过一半的年轻人认为，由于气候变化，“人类注定要灭亡”。我们需要重新构建叙事，从厄运和牺牲转向机遇。 （<a href="https://hannahritchie.substack.com/p/young-climate-anxiety" target="_blank" rel="noopener">数字中的可持续性</a>）</p><p> •<strong>乌克兰战争如何将网球变成了战场</strong>：对于乌克兰球员以及来自俄罗斯及其盟国的球员来说，国内持续不断的冲突已经渗透到了比赛中。现在他们将在美国公开赛上交锋。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/08/29/magazine/ukraine-war-tennis.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">《纽约时报》</a> ）<em>另请参阅</em><strong>《他们如何试图杀掉我</strong>》：2022 年，n+1 发表了俄罗斯记者埃琳娜·科斯尤琴科 (Elena Kostyuchenko) 撰写的有关乌克兰战争的四篇报道（1、2、3、4）。在接下来的文章中，科斯尤琴科首次描述了她逃离乌克兰的原因，并透露她去年秋天在慕尼黑中毒。 ( <a href="https://www.nplusonemag.com/online-only/online-only/how-they-tried-to-kill-me/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">N+1</a> )</p><p> •<strong>詹妮弗·安妮斯顿 (Jennifer Aniston) 如何从情景喜剧明星成为好莱坞巨星</strong>：这位演员、制片人和企业家在好莱坞开辟了自己的道路——从《老友记》到《早间秀》。就是这样。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/style/jennifer-aniston-morning-show-season-3-59413d2f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p></blockquote><p>请务必查看本周末我们对先锋集团首席投资官格雷格·戴维斯的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士</a><a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" data-web-url="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2">采访</a>。戴维斯负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。他还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。</p><p></p><p> <strong>91% 的美国抵押贷款借款人的抵押贷款利率低于 5.01%</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/below5pct.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-318910" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/below5pct.jpeg" alt="" width="600" height="434" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/below5pct.jpeg 733w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/below5pct-300x217.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/below5pct-250x181.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><br />资料来源：<a href="https://twitter.com/NewsLambert/status/1693650460895273186" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@NewsLambert</a></p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p></p><p></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-wednesday-am-reads-345/">周三上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title>文字记录：Greg Davis，CIO Vanguard</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/transcript-greg-davis/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Index/ETFs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Investing]]></category><category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318920 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>﻿﻿ 本周 MiB 的文字记录：Greg Davis，CIO Vanguard，如下。您可以在 Apple Podcasts、Spotify、Stitcher、Google、YouTube 和 Bloomberg 上流式传输和下载我们的完整对话，包括任何播客附加内容。您可以在此处找到您最喜欢的播客主机上的所有早期播客。 ~~~ 播音员：这个……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/transcript-greg-davis/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p>帖子<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/transcript-greg-davis/">记录：Greg Davis，CIO Vanguard</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/greg-davis-on-vanguard-portfolio-management/id730188152?i=1000625684276" height="175" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"></iframe></p><p></p><p></p><p>本周<a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/mib-greg-davis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>MiB：CIO Vanguard 的 Greg Davis 的</em></a>文字记录如下。</p><p>您可以在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/greg-davis-on-vanguard-portfolio-management/id730188152?i=1000625684276" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Podcasts</a> 、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/2bo96GOdIjlVEodoCm7zvn" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> 、 <a href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> 、 <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvZTczYzk5OGUtNmU2MC00MzJmLTg2MTAtYWUyMTAxNDBjNWIxLzRlNGNkOTEwLTQwYTEtNDYxOS1hNWYzLWFlMmIwMDEyZmZmZi81ODczYTNjYi0yOThmLTQwYmMtYjcxZi1hZTJiMDAxMzAwMGQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> 、 <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLe4PRejZgr0PzN7r8NikAnOqP70DHhoJ0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a>和<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2023-08-25/greg-davis-on-vanguard-portfolio-management-podcast" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a>上流式传输和下载我们的完整对话，包括任何播客附加内容。您可以<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">在此处找到</a>您最喜欢的播客主机上的所有早期播客。</p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"> ~~~</p><p></p><p>播音员：这是彭博电台巴里·里索尔茨 (Barry Ritholtz) 主持的商业硕士节目。</p><p> BARRY RITHOLTZ，主持人，商业硕士：本周的播客中，我有一位特别的嘉宾。格雷格·戴维斯（Greg Davis）是一家名为先锋集团（Vanguard Group）的小公司的首席投资官，该公司管理着 8 万亿美元的资产。他只负责其中的 7.3 万亿美元，真是个懒鬼。</p><p>我发现这次谈话绝对是一堂大师课，讲述了如何思考投资风险，如何思考回报从何而来，什么样的行为问题会导致不良结果，以及我们在这次谈话中学到的所有常见知识距离先锋集团的成功已经有好几年了。</p><p>很少有人比先锋首席信息官更能了解投资领域的动态，无论是机构投资还是零售投资。格雷格·戴维斯做得非常出色。我认为这是一次非常有趣的谈话。我想你也会的。</p><p>话不多说，下面是我对 Vanguard 首席信息官 Greg Davis 的采访。</p><p>格雷格·戴维斯，欢迎来到彭博社。</p><p>格雷格·戴维斯，先锋集团首席投资官：谢谢，巴里。很高兴和你在一起。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：很高兴有你。</p><p>那么让我们来谈谈你的背景吧，这很有趣。本科生，您将获得宾夕法尼亚州立大学的保险学士学位。是什么引发了对保险的兴趣？</p><p>戴维斯：说来话长，但我最初是学工程学的。到了学校，我意识到我不太擅长机械制图，而机械制图是航空航天工程课程的重要组成部分。所以我开始寻找其他机会，主要是商业领域的机会。</p><p>因此，开始研究金融、房地产和保险领域的机会。宾夕法尼亚州立大学是少数几所真正设有保险专业的学校之一。为了在大学毕业后真正获得有酬就业的目标，我想，嘿，拥有一些独特的背景会有所帮助。</p><p>结果很成功，并获得了来自多家不同保险公司的多份工作机会。在我决定回到学校攻读 MBA 之前，我有机会担任几年的承销商。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：您是如何在 20 世纪 90 年代加入美林证券的？</p><p>戴维斯：所以我最终完成了沃顿商学院的课程。夏天我在花旗银行证券公司实习，负责固定收益销售和交易。在街对面有几个不同的工作机会。但我去美林的原因是因为他们有独特的全球债务轮换计划，允许你在固定收益、销售和交易等几个不同的业务部门之间轮换。我知道我想从事交易。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：你当时在市中心吗？世界……</p><p>戴维斯：世界金融中心。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：顺便说一句，这可能是最令人惊奇的交易台。我去过那里几次。在 20 世纪 90 年代，当你走进股票市场时，你会被一堵声音和能量墙击中。我在其他地方从未见过或经历过类似的事情。</p><p>戴维斯：固定收益楼层的规模相同，只是位于不同的楼层，但环境类型也相似。但这是研究生毕业后开始职业生涯的一个非常有趣的地方。但这段经历被缩短了，因为就在我上课的时候，正值亚洲金融危机的尾声，俄罗斯卢布贬值</p><p>里索兹：97 还是 98？</p><p>戴维斯：98年。我从98年9月开始，那发生在97年。但亚洲金融危机、俄罗斯卢布贬值，以及长期资本管理的失败。</p><p>里索兹：对。</p><p>戴维斯：因此，街对面发生了很多裁员方面的变化，我们的计划被缩短，最终被安排在非贸易职位，并决定寻找外面的其他机会，并遇到了这个伟大的机会24 年前有机会在先锋集团从事交易。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：那么我们来谈谈这个吧。您的简历解释了您是如何被招募到先锋集团的。我认为这是一个非常有趣的故事。告诉我们一些是什么让您来到先锋集团的。</p><p>戴维斯：所以这很有趣，因为我非常热衷于留在纽约。我建立了很多关系，并在纽约市找到了另一份工作。但和我一起长大的最好的朋友之一实际上在先锋集团的人力资源部门工作。她说，“你应该下来和先锋集团的一些人谈谈。”</p><p>起初我有点不以为然，但她非常坚持。所以我下来，会见了我们的投资组合审查部门的负责人，该部门负责监督我们的外部经理，会见了我们的经纪业务负责人，然后会见了绑定索引的负责人，他当时是肯·沃尔珀特。我和他立刻就产生了联系。所以肯是我来到先锋集团的主要原因。 Vanguard 已经享有很高的声誉，当时我们的规模要小得多，但 Ken 拥有将新人引入团队、培养他们并随着时间的推移看到他们从事更大工作的记录。</p><p>作为这个行业相对较新的人，这就是我正在寻找的导师和老板。所以，肯最终成为我职业生涯中遇到过的最好的老板之一。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：稍后我们将讨论领导力和团队发展。这确实是一个令人着迷的话题，但您最终担任了 Vanguard 澳大利亚和亚太地区的总监以及该地区的首席信息官。请告诉我们一些 2000 年代的经历。我的意思是，90 年代是它自己独特的动物，但 2000 年代当然并不无聊。</p><p>戴维斯：不，所以我和我的家人搬到了澳大利亚墨尔本，我们的办公室就在那里。</p><p>无论是在职业还是个人方面，这都是一次美妙的经历，只是有机会在不同的国家工作，拥抱澳大利亚文化，但作为亚太地区的一部分，因为当时我们在香港设有办事处我们就是在那里开始我们的 ETF 业务的。</p><p>但这是一次巨大的经历，因为我从债券交易开始，进入投资组合管理并管理债券指数团队多年，然后我被要求承担这一职责，范围要广泛得多。</p><p>因此，我对债券指数的主题很深入，但现在我有机会领导一个股票指数小组、整个固定收益团队、我们的投资策略团队，该团队为我们的客户围绕投资组合构建进行研究，这些类型的事物。</p><p>但另一个重要部分是有机会加入实际经营该业务的澳大利亚高管团队。因此，从更广泛的角度来看，我是一名投资人，但这是一个真正了解业务的机会，了解先锋澳大利亚如何在生态系统中运作，我们如何尝试营销我们的产品和服务，我们如何参与与监管机构、媒体、整个九个院子一起工作，然后也是董事会的一部分，所以从更广泛的角度来看，这种经历令人难以置信。</p><p>所以我珍惜​​在那里的每一分钟，不幸的是，或者幸运的是，这取决于你如何看待它，三到四年的任务最终只有 13 个月。但正如你提到的，我有一个很好的机会回来管理固定收益部门，但在澳大利亚的时光对我自己、我的妻子和孩子们来说都是美妙的。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：你知道，真正有趣的是每个人都倾向于从投资方面来考虑华尔街以及投资和金融。但商业方面确实很有趣。商业模式有无数种，看看人们如何运作它，这确实是一种教育，我认为很多刚从学校出来的人都没有考虑过这种教育，因为你会考虑性感的事情。 “嘿，我想做风险投资。我想做这个，我想做那个。”商业方面确实非常令人着迷，但有些被忽视了。</p><p>戴维斯：这是非常非常正确的。但这也是你在从事某项工作一段时间之前不一定会欣赏的事情之一。所以，如果你对我说，你知道，当我第一次从研究生院毕业时，你对我说，嘿，我希望你去商业领域，你知道，我会说，不，谢谢，我真的很想做交易和投资组合管理。但当你在职业生涯中达到某个阶段时，你会觉得，嘿，你学到了很多东西，你已经组建了一个团队，你正在寻找新的挑战和机会来拓展自己、成长和学习。这正是这个机会所提供的。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：所以现在你最终得到了，你进入固定收益，然后你被提升为整个 Van 集团的首席投资官。带我们了解先锋首席信息官一天或一周的生活。</p><p>戴维斯：嗯，很多。我的意思是，有大量的会议，按照我的描述，巴里，这是一个混合体。它与客户相关，就像我们今天所做的那样。它也是管理 Vanguard、Vanguard 业务的高级团队的一部分，对吗？因此，从客户策略、营销角度，然后监督投资团队。所以各种风险会议，各种经济会议。因此，任何一天都可能略有不同，但随着时间的推移，它通常会捕获这些类别。因此，市场和业务中总是有很多事情发生，让我们非常忙碌。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：您在 Vanguard 工作已近 25 年了。</p><p>戴维斯：11 月 24 日。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：所以距离一个重要的里程碑还有一年的时间。</p><p>那个时期很大程度上涵盖了先锋集团从一个公认的成功但不是巨大的实体，直到我认为 2000 年代，尤其是金融危机，改变了人们对管理资产、指数、咨询与交易的看法，先锋集团和贝莱德一起，改变了人们对管理资产、指数、咨询与交易的看法。是其中最大的受益者之一。告诉我们一些你在这 24 年里经历过的事情，当公司发展壮大时，你确实在场，然后他们发现了另一个齿轮，然后爆炸了。</p><p>戴维斯：是的，你说得完全正确，巴里。我的意思是，市场对投资者投资方式的看法发生了很大变化，对吧？你是对的。所以你回想一下30年前，有很多人专注于个人证券选择，挑选个股。</p><p>现实情况是，我们知道这很难做到，也很难跑赢大盘。因此，人们大力推动以高度多元化、低成本的方式获得适当水平的资产配置。 ETF，即 ETF 包装器，允许人们以低廉的价格获得该风险敞口，并将其保存在经纪账户中。</p><p>因此，它确实为索引领域提供这些产品的人们提供了良好的推动力。从个股选择转向广泛的指数投资，先锋集团是最大的受益者之一。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：至少可以这么说。</p><p>因此，让我们讨论一下领导力以及如何培养船员以及识别和培养其他人的领导技能。</p><p>戴维斯：是的，巴里，这是一个很好的问题。我们试图关注的事情之一是，作为面试过程的一部分，始终尝试评估和衡量人们除了技术能力之外发展领导能力的意愿和兴趣。因此，当我们想到我们的投资专业人士时，显然他们必须拥有敏锐的技术。他们必须学习这些技能才能完成日常工作。</p><p>但如果他们也想成为交易部门的负责人并领导我们集团或更广泛的先锋集团内的主要职能，他们还必须真正善于识别人才、培养人才、维持真正牢固的关系、成为战略思想家，并且那种性质的东西。因此，我们有很多项目来帮助我们评估人们在领导力之旅中的进展情况。我们帮助人们一路走上领导力之旅，但评估过程也让我们能够找出人们可能存在的差距，以及需要有机会回去复习的地方。</p><p>因此，我们一直非常积极地参与我们的投资专业人士的整个过程。它得到了回报，它确实得到了回报，它帮助我们确保我们正在招聘合适的人才，它帮助我们留住人才。因为当你为一位伟大的老板工作时，你就会有动力留在那家公司。因为我们知道有时很难与老板建立牢固的联系，而且先锋集团拥有出色的领导者，我们感觉，嘿，我们有一些最酷的工作可供人们选择，你加上出色的领导力，我的意思是，这是我们组织长期成功的双赢公式。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这真的很有趣。</p><p>许多金融界人士表示，在这种环境下很难找到人才。先锋集团正在采取哪些措施来保持席位充足，并确保有源源不断的人才来到宾夕法尼亚州？</p><p>戴维斯：是的，所以我们非常积极地参与其中。具体来说，在我们的团队中，我们有投资管理发展计划，每年我们都会有一批暑期实习生以及刚刚完成本科学习的全职人员，他们通过轮换计划来到我们这里，让他们有机会接触对于股票、固定收益和风险的各个点以及我们的投资组合审查部门来说，这是人们探索和了解他们真正想做的事情的一个很好的切入点。</p><p>因此，我们刚刚有一名干部在本周早些时候开始了他们的最终安置。因此，有七个人涉足从风险到高收益交易再到投资级研究的各个领域。这是一个很好的人才管道。最棒的是，我们今天看到的人才比 20 年前吸引的人才要多得多。</p><p>因此，这些人今天所带来的意识水平、对市场的理解以及从 IT 和数据科学角度来看的技术技能都是相当惊人的。这确实是我们的管道。然后，如果出现人员流动，而我们的替补席上没有人准备好进入更大的席位，或者如果我们正在尝试建立新的能力，例如我们过去做过。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：真的令人印象深刻。</p><p>我们来谈谈先锋总市场指数。这已成为世界上最大的基金。管理如此规模且对先锋集团如此重要的基金需要什么？</p><p>戴维斯：我的意思是，这实际上是从人开始的。只是确保我们拥有令人难以置信的才华横溢的专业人士，他们真正致力于日常管理这些指数基金。从我们的角度来看，我们的项目经理同时也是交易员，因此他们日复一日地密切合作，确保总股票市场指数基金和我们所有其他股票指数基金最大限度地减少跟踪误差。</p><p>我们还努力确保在市场上进行交易时最大限度地降低交易成本。还要认识到贸易活动的税务影响。然后还寻求通过机会主义想法以及通过再平衡、公司行动、新问题和类似性质的事情来增加边际价值，试图蚕食边际费用率。但同样，是以高度、高度风险控制的方式。</p><p>最棒的是，我们拥有一支几十年来一直从事这方面工作的团队，他们在行业中是无与伦比的，因为他们致力于索引编制。你会发现很多公司的员工都是从索引开始，然后转向其他领域。在先锋集团，这是许多人的职业目的地，他们热爱自己工作的每一分钟。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：所以很多索引器都会跟踪其他人的索引。 Vanguard总市场指数是Vanguard自己创建的。有一个单独的索引组，并且设置了一大堆技术方法。股票会员资格的变更涉及哪些内容？告诉我们一些关于这个过程是什么样的。</p><p>戴维斯：对于整个股票市场指数基金来说，这是一个由芝加哥大学运营的 CRSP 基金。他们创造了基准。我们帮助他们识别和创建围绕如何构建索引的参数。最重要的事情主要是当有公司行动时，就会有首次公开募股。这些通常是推动变革的因素，因为这又代表了整个市场。所以你有小盘股、中盘股、大盘股。你在那里有成长、价值和融入。因此，营业额主要由公司行为和首次公开募股驱动。然后团队花费大量时间来确保他们确实非常好地处理这些问题，以最大限度地降低成本，并确保跟踪误差保持相对较小。</p><p>该团队所做的另一件事是，我们有一个证券借贷团队，他们也花了很多时间来确保我们从所需的证券中获得价值。证券借贷收入的收益在扣除运营该集团的成本后将直接返回该基金。</p><p>因此，只要对我们拥有的某些证券有大量需求，我们的股东就会受益。因此，这也是影响这些基金业绩的另一个因素。</p><p>里索兹：对。这是一个性能增强器。</p><p>戴维斯：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：最终导致能够降低该基金的成本。</p><p>戴维斯：嗯，它降低了交易成本带来的最终阻力。确切地。</p><p>里索尔兹：是的。那么 Vanguard 多久创建一个新索引呢？那么这个过程是怎样的呢？</p><p>戴维斯：我们倾向于不创建索引。这是一个外包流程。所以这真的取决于我们的阵容是否有空缺？因此，我们从各个业务部门获取意见，无论是我们的零售部门、我们的机构部门还是我们的财务顾问服务部门，是否存在我们认为的差距，嘿，我们没有提供所需的相关产品我们的客户？</p><p>然后我们发现，我们进行研究，投资组合审查部门进行研究，以确定谁将是此类任务的最佳和装备最齐全的指数提供商。然后我们的团队在尽职调查过程中与他们密切合作，并确保该指数以我们满意的方式构建，并采取适当的控制水平。</p><p>然后，您知道，一旦设置完毕，团队就准备好开始根据新定义的索引进行管理。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：当你说你的阵容中存在差距时，你并不是在谈论流行的东西，比如“嘿，我们没有虚拟宇宙索引。”或者，“看，我们没有人工智能指数。”它总是更广泛、更持久，如果这是我正在寻找的正确的词，或者是持久的。</p><p>戴维斯：是的，同样，这些需要具有持久的长期投资价值。这是我们推出基金之前的关键定义原则之一。这种投资策略有真正的长期价值吗？你是完全正确的。 Vanguard 不是那种会推出专注于主题的产品的公司，无论是人工智能、水还是其他什么。这不是先锋集团所做的。我们正在寻找长期持久的投资解决方案和产品，为我们的投资者提供真正为他们服务的长期机会。</p><p>因此，几年前，我写了一篇专栏，介绍 Vanguard 的这个令人震惊的小方面，我认为没有人理解，这就是 Vanguard 在管理共同基金税收的方式上拥有的专利，这使得您的共同基金的行为更像 ETF ，并且通常没有税收转嫁。</p><p>这让我想到了一个问题。当你达到先锋集团的规模时，你如何平衡一方面的纪律与创造力的需要以及偶尔的跳出框框的思考？你可能会认为他们可能会发生争执。那是什么样子的？</p><p>戴维斯：是的，最重要的是，巴里，这是一个很好的问题。最重要的是，持久的理念是什么以及我们试图为客户实现什么？归根结底，他们来找我们是为了尝试长期接触某一细分市场。我们希望以尽可能最好的方式做到这一点，确保他们获得市场回报，减去费用比率，我们将再次尝试用证券借贷收入和深思熟虑的再平衡策略来抵消这一点。</p><p>但归根结底，这实际上归结为我们的客户以低成本、多元化的方式进行广泛的投资，我们认为这最终将在他们构建投资组合时为他们服务。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：大多数人首先认为先锋集团是被动的。告诉我们一些关于首席投资官在投资业务的被动方面所做的事情。</p><p>戴维斯：其中很大一部分实际上是在发生更复杂的企业行为并带来一定程度的风险时。我们与风险管理部门进行了对话，以确保我们对基金中产生的风险敞口感到满意。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：当你说公司行为时，我们指的是并购、首次公开募股、破产，以及任何在你的决策过程之外的人退出或进入市场的情况。</p><p>戴维斯：是的，完全正确。因此，当发生这样的重大交易时，你总是可以选择，“嘿，你能在进入基准时准确地做到这一点吗？您需要提前做一些事情吗？您是否需要事后做一些事情来使整个过程顺利进行？”这是您必须做出的风险决定。当发生重大活动时，会有多少流动性？与等到二级市场开始交易相比，立即定价是否更具吸引力？这些是我们与风险团队和股票方面的高级投资专业人士进行的考虑和对话。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：学术研究中已经明确认为，从长远来看，股票方面的被动投资胜过主动投资，但在固定收益方面却并非如此。固定收益的主动型往往是被动型的，因为固定收益的选择比股票的选择要多得多。请告诉我们一些您作为 CIO 在债券方面所做的工作。</p><p>戴维斯：所以在债券方面，我们两者都有。因此，我们以高度多元化的方式进行债券指数化，跨越各个细分市场，包括国债，包括政府、企业、抵押贷款以及类似性质的东西，全球投资组合为您提供了对冲美元的巨大多元化，这以高度多元化的方式是获得债券敞口的好方法。</p><p>就主动固定收益而言，我们确实拥有一个非常庞大的主动固定收益团队，该团队在长期增值方面非常成功。因此，当你看一些结果时，其中很大一部分来自我们团队内部的信用研究能力，包括投资级别、新兴市场以及高收益，但我们 92% 的主动债券基金做得更好高于利珀特集团五年内平均基金的平均水平。我们 87% 的主动型固定收益基金在三年内的表现优于其基准。</p><p>然后，如果你看一下五年的时间范围，就会发现这个比例是 77%。</p><p>因此，我们的活跃团队已经成功超越了他们的基准。其中很大一部分是，您是否有可以进行尽职调查的信贷团队？因为信用是我们认为可以通过信用研究增加最大价值的地方。我们在市政债券方面也看到了这一点，我们拥有非常活跃的市政债券特许经营权。信用研究使该团队能够持续增加相对于其基准的价值，从而为我们的客户提供更好的长期结果。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：在股票方面，这确实非常令人着迷，2% 或 3% 的股票是所有价值创造的地方。在固定收益方面，似乎消除风险或久期最差的 10%、20%、30% 的股票是所有 alpha 产生的地方。</p><p>戴维斯：是的，我的意思是，在固定收益领域，因为它往往是一种防御性资产类别，你想要做的是尽量避免失败者，对吗？你知道，投资债券有什么好处吗？</p><p> RITHOLTZ：嘿，你把钱拿回来了。</p><p>戴维斯：你可以拿回你的钱。您知道，您会在到期时按时获得息票付款和本金。缺点是您的损失为零，因为该公司申请破产并且没有恢复价值。因此，您知道，对于防御性资产类别，我们一直认为您希望限制投资组合中本应平衡的风险量。我们能够实现这一目标的方式是，因为我们拥有如此大的规模和能力，为了在先锋集团保持较低的成本，最终我们的主动固定收益经理不需要采取同样的水平与我们的一些竞争对手一样存在风险，仅仅是因为他们没有同样程度的逆风。我们的费用比率较低。</p><p>因此，当市场上的东西看起来价格不具吸引力时，您不需要一直坐在那里并试图克服高昂的费用比率。我们可以耐心等待。我们可以等待。我们可以等到市场更具吸引力，当我们觉得我们的冒险得到了回报时。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：Vanguard 的低成本方面有一点乘数效应，因为你不必在每个球上挥杆。有能力说：“不，不，我们对此很擅长。 “我们会等到机会看起来更有吸引力。”我不明白很多金融界人士的这种感觉。他们每个月都会受到评判，每个季度都会受到评判，他们觉得，老笑话是什么？切勿将活动误认为进步？</p><p>戴维斯：没错。</p><p> RITHOLTZ：这在华尔街似乎很常见。</p><p>戴维斯：是的，我的意思是，对于我们的团队，我们活跃的团队，他们的表现是按三年评估的。所以你知道-</p><p>里索兹：三年？</p><p>戴维斯：是的，所以——</p><p>里索兹：太棒了。</p><p>戴维斯：所以当我们考虑如何评估这些团队时，这是一个三年的数字。那么你的表现如何呢？ Because in any given quarter, any given year, you know, you could have winners and losers in terms of strategies, but what you&#39;re trying to do is you&#39;re trying to string good periods together and over a three-year period, we feel like there&#39;s enough opportunities for teams if they&#39;re good at what they do to add value. And that&#39;s what we&#39;ve been able to demonstrate over time.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s so fascinating because I would assume that intellectually, everybody understands that&#39;s true, but emotionally, two bad quarters, and it&#39;s like, we know we told you three years, but we&#39;re getting pressure from investors and we have to make a change. Like to stay with that is really challenging.</p><p> DAVIS: Well, you know, it&#39;s a great point, Barry, but the reality is like when you&#39;re running portfolios in a highly risk-controlled way, you&#39;re trying to manage the downside, right? So when you have three years, you have three years, again, because you&#39;re trying to make sure people have an opportunity for their strategies to play out over time, but you&#39;re also making sure that you&#39;re constraining the risk, that even if you do have a bad year, it&#39;s not going to be so bad that investors start running for the hills.</p><p> Again, we want investors to stay in each product long-term because we think they provide good, long-term, enduring value for our clients.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And Vanguard famously during the financial crisis, not only did you not see outflows, you actually saw inflows. I got to imagine a year like 2022 wasn&#39;t horrible for Vanguard&#39;s asset growth.</p><p> DAVIS: It&#39;s interesting. I mean, there&#39;s certain segments of markets that did quite well, certain segments of the business, but you also have a period of time when there&#39;s repricing that happens in the fixed income space, like we saw, and it was pretty rapid last year.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Sure.</p><p> DAVIS: And you had-</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Hey, 500 basis points of rate increases, we&#39;ll do that.</p><p> DAVIS: That&#39;s exactly it. And when you saw the US Ag down 13% last year, for folks, again, who are investing for retirement and in their 529 plans, they&#39;re not concerned about it. But when you translate that to folks who might have a heavy municipal bond portfolio, and those folks who are in retirement, and they don&#39;t like principal losses. They like tax-free income, but they also don&#39;t like principal losses. So when you have a big backup like that, you tend to see outflows in that segment of the market more than you would see in a taxable market, which tends to be, in our case, more long-term, retirement-oriented, and things of that nature. So you will see some pressure on munis in those types of interest rate environments.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting.</p><p> So let&#39;s talk a little bit about last year, where all I heard was the 60 portfolio is dead. Discuss.</p><p> DAVIS: It&#39;s interesting. I mean, we&#39;ve heard that over and over again. It was a tough year for investors in terms of both stocks and bonds being down where stocks were down about 20%, the US AG was down 13%.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: When was the last time we saw stocks and bonds down double digits, like 81, something like that?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Somewhere in that type of horizon, yes, exactly. So it&#39;s not something that many investors have been accustomed to or have seen in their lifetimes, but the reality is, the reality is, when you think about the components in the terms of long-term investing, the bond portion of the equation provides that balance and diversification. Now again, in any one given year, you will have a 60, you can have a 60/40 portfolio that underperforms and both sides of the equation go down, but for a long-term investor who&#39;s saving for retirement, that balance and diversification has proved and delivered really good long-term returns.</p><p> So when you go back to 1926, if you were an investor since then, a 60/40 portfolio has returned 8.8% on average over that time horizon…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> DAVIS: Which is impressive.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> DAVIS: Because again, it provides you diversification, it reduces some of the volatility, but there will be periods of time where, again, that type of portfolio when, we were in an environment where interest rates were held down to historically low levels.</p><p> So when they reprice, it&#39;s not surprising that you see losses on the bond side of the equation. But if you go back to the period before 2022, from 2019 to 2021, a 60/40 portfolio actually produced 14% returns over that time horizon, which is above the long-term average.</p><p> So, in the grand scheme of things, it&#39;s not surprising that there&#39;s periods of outperformance and that ultimately will lead to periods of underperformance.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s right. And I&#39;m glad you mentioned the period before that. Go to the decade before 2022, the equity side was something like 13%. And then whatever you got from bonds was just a bonus on top of that.</p><p> DAVIS: That&#39;s exactly right.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: People forget that when they see a single year like 2022, and they really forget that in a year like 2023, where everything is going up, I mean, other than gold, what hasn&#39;t been going up this year? How do you deal with the opposite of last year with the first half like this year?</p><p> DAVIS: Well, look, clearly the equity market has been on a tremendous tear so far this year, up 18%, 19% year to date. But the key thing there is, again, investors have to keep in mind that that&#39;s probably not sustainable long term. And so again, the importance of having a diversified portfolio is critically important. And just think about fixed income and money markets as an asset class.</p><p> You know, for a decade, you weren&#39;t earning anything in a money market fund because interest rates by the Federal Reserve were pegged at zero. And you had to take on significant duration risk and credit risk just to earn a couple percentage points. And now, you&#39;re in an environment where money market funds are yielding 5-1/4%. You have the US Ag that&#39;s yielding somewhere close to 5%, so 4.5%, 5%. So in the grand scheme of things, investors are actually being rewarded for having exposure to money markets and bond funds.</p><p> And so if people are truly concerned about a 60/40 portfolio, they should have been concerned about it for 10 years. Now&#39;s not the time when you&#39;re back to an environment where you&#39;re actually getting a real yield when it comes to the bond market.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I&#39;m glad you brought up money markets because it&#39;s this overlooked area that when you have rates at ultra-low levels, it kind of gets forgotten about. But is it fair to say that this year and perhaps last year, you saw a big shift of client cash assets into money markets?</p><p> DAVIS: We definitely saw a number of clients who started embracing money markets. And the reality is for a lot of investors, it truly is free money, right? So when you think about what people are earning in their deposit accounts at their banks, and banks have historically been very slow to raise, very slow in terms of raising deposit rates because those deposits tend to be very sticky.</p><p> And I&#39;ve had people stop me, even at Vanguard, in the hallway and say, “Wow, I didn&#39;t realize that I&#39;ve been leaving this much money on the table by keeping a sizable amount of deposits at my bank.”</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Yes.</p><p> DAVIS: “I moved it to a money market, now I&#39;m getting a five and a quarter percent type yield, which is amazing when some folks are still getting less than half a percent” in many cases, in the bank.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It&#39;s shocking that this has gone on, how much inertia there is in finance that even if you&#39;re just getting your December bonus that you&#39;re going to pay Uncle Sam in April, leaving that money in a savings account for a third of the year, you&#39;re leaving a chunk of change on the table.</p><p> DAVIS: It&#39;s free money.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Free money, right.</p><p> DAVIS: It&#39;s free money.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Quite interesting.</p><p> So at what point do you think high yields become a headwind for stocks, or is it just overall part of the 60/40 portfolio? And hey, we&#39;ll either take it on the equity half or the bond half, we don&#39;t care.</p><p> DAVIS: Well, I think if you look at what our return expectations are for the global balance portfolio, we&#39;re expecting that over the next decade or so, somewhere in the neighborhood of about 5.5% for a global balance portfolio. So combination of equities, bonds, US and international stocks. And the reality is, our return expectations for the US equity market is a bit more muted. We&#39;re expecting US equity market returns to hover somewhere around 5% or so…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> DAVIS: Where international equities, because of valuations, probably 7% to 7.5%.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So let&#39;s talk about that, because that gap in valuation has persisted for a long time. Certainly for a few years after the financial crisis, it seemed like US stocks were pricey, forward return expectations were low and the opposite was true overseas, but the US seemed to be the only place to be.</p><p> How durable is that shift, given how large that gap has gotten in valuation between US stocks and the rest of the developed world?</p><p> DAVIS: Yes, so I mean, if you were to take a look at what&#39;s happened over the last 10 years, looking at the S&amp;P 500 index versus, you know, like the FTSE Global All Cap ex-US, there was a seven percentage point difference per year by being–</p><p> RITHOLTZ: 700 basis.</p><p> DAVIS: 700 basis points–</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s monstrous.</p><p> DAVIS: Of outperformance by the US market relative to the international markets. But, you know, so if you were to take a look at where PE ratios are today, between ES and P, which has an earning yield of about 5%, and you look at the FTSE Global All Cap ex-US, it has an earning yield of 8.3%, right? And so–</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Not insubstantial–</p><p> DAVIS: There&#39;s a substantial difference. Now, there are sector differences. So, you know, and we could talk about that to some degree as well, but the reality, even if you adjust for sector differences, there&#39;s still a big gap. There&#39;s still a big gap in terms of the PE ratios across the US market relative to the rest of the world.</p><p> And so, unless we expect earnings for US companies to vastly outpace what&#39;s happening in the international markets, and it might, but there&#39;s a lot of great news already priced into the marketplace. And when you think about translating the S&amp;P 500 PE to an implied equity risk premium by looking at the 10 year treasury yield, you&#39;re 200 basis points below what it&#39;s been for the last 10 years.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So let&#39;s do a little comparison because I&#39;m always skeptical when people focus on a single metric like price to earnings. I want to make that more three-dimensional. So if Europe is at an 8.3 earnings yield and we&#39;re at about a 5%, what&#39;s the growth rate difference between the two, meaning are people willing to give up a little bit of earnings in order to accept a faster growth rate that certainly we&#39;ve seen on the tech side, I can&#39;t speak across every sector.</p><p> DAVIS: Well, I think there&#39;s a couple of things there, Barry. I mean, one of it is, do you expect the earnings growth to live up to the expectations that are already priced into the US market? And if so, that&#39;s fine for where we are, but that&#39;s not necessarily going to lead to multiple expansion, right? And a big driver of the outperformance over the last decade of US stocks relative to the international valuation expansion.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right. And that&#39;s all sentiment.</p><p> DAVIS: That&#39;s exactly it. And a lot of, we would say a lot of that&#39;s probably already baked into the marketplace and has run its course. Could it go further? Of course it could. But at some point, there is a tipping point where people start saying, “Well, in the US, I have alternatives. I have alternatives because I can go out and buy a money market fund at five and a quarter percent and I don&#39;t have to take a lot of risk.” And if, again, based on our forecast for US equity markets, they&#39;re somewhat muted because valuations are stretched in our view relative to our fair value model.</p><p> And so I think a lot of investors have alternatives. They can buy money markets, they can buy bond funds where there was no alternative for the last 10 years because we didn&#39;t get any real yield when it came to the fixed income or the money market space. But there&#39;s really alternatives today for investors, either in fixed income money markets, or international stocks.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right. The 2010s were certainly the TINA decade. It&#39;s funny you mentioned multiple expansion. When you look at the 82 to 2000 bull market, something like 75% of those gains came not from earnings growth, but from multiple expansion.</p><p> I&#39;m curious if that&#39;s kind of repeating now and the 2020 pandemic fiscal stimulus, which was massive under two presidents. What does that do in terms of resetting the cycle? And can we stay pricey, forget higher for longer, can we stay pricey for longer given all the stimulus that&#39;s coursing through the system?</p><p> DAVIS: Well, I think there&#39;s a couple of things. One, it becomes a factor. Yes, the economy can clearly keep roaring along, which we&#39;ve seen. The fiscal stimulus that we&#39;ve seen, there&#39;s over $2 trillion that was saved. Our reports show, and some of the data out in the marketplace shows that about a trillion dollars of that has already been spent down. So investors and savers are definitely eating into that safety net, which over time as that continues to decline should slow the economy down to some degree. So I think that&#39;s going to be a big factor.</p><p> But then when you think about the broader equity markets, again, the biggest thing that would be concerning if you start seeing a continued rise in interest rates and that has to put pressure on equity valuations. I mean equities are a ultra-long duration asset.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> DAVIS: And if you&#39;re discounting those future cash flows at higher interest rates, that means you get a lower present value. And at some point that will bite. Who knows when that&#39;s going to be? Nobody knows when you could see that kind of return to normal. But you would definitely expect that higher interest rates will put continued pressure on the equity market and get valuations back to something that&#39;s more normalized over time. Because you do expect, if you&#39;re investing in equities, to earn an equity risk premium.</p><p> And the fact that it&#39;s so much lower than what we&#39;ve seen historically, it starts to beg the question, how much exposure, if I&#39;m a shorter term investor, how much exposure do I want in that space? For long term investors, it doesn&#39;t matter.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So let&#39;s stay with interest rates for a moment. Interest rates are much higher than they&#39;ve been over the past decade. But let&#39;s look at the past 50 or 75 years, interest rates today are clearly above where they were, but they&#39;re not especially high by historical standards. I think a lot of people confuse those two.</p><p> DAVIS: Yes, I think a lot of investors end up succumbing to recency bias, right? So the fact that we&#39;ve been in an environment where interest rates …</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Hey, it ain&#39;t zero anymore.</p><p> DAVIS: That&#39;s exactly it. So people think that that&#39;s the end. I think what you have to look at, and our team has done work on this, you have to look at what do you think is the appropriate level for Fed funds in the neutral state where it&#39;s not stimulative or contracting the marketplace. And so some of the research our team has done, it says that, look, long-term Fed funds could be higher than what the market is pricing in.</p><p> The market and the Fed have said, probably in the neighborhood, R-star is 50 basis points or half a percent. You add 2% inflation on top of that, that gives you a long-term Fed funds of 2.5%.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right.</p><p> DAVIS: You know, our investment strategy group, through their analysis, they estimate that R-star is probably closer to 1.5%. So that brings you to a longer term Fed funds target of closer to 3.5% if they&#39;re successful at bringing rates back down to 2%, inflation back down to 2%, I should say. And then if you build a normal term structure on top of that, between three month treasury bills and 10 year bonds of about 100 basis points, that brings you to a 10 year that&#39;s probably fair around 4.5%.</p><p> And so — but it all depends on what happens from an inflation perspective, economic growth perspective, and how aggressive the Fed will have to be going down the path here but again, we think that there is some risk that rates will have to go a bit higher here, just given everything that&#39;s going on in the economy and the marketplace.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: And the 10-year is not all that far away from four and a half percent.</p><p> DAVIS: It is not.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: That&#39;s something that end of year is not unthinkable.</p><p> DAVIS: That&#39;s right.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting.</p><p> So everybody seems kind of shocked by what&#39;s taking place in 2023, although to be fair, everybody seemed shocked at what took place in 2022. What are your thoughts about how Wall Street plays this forecasting game where everybody&#39;s thrown a dart, someone randomly gets it right, but it just seems like it&#39;s a weird game to be playing with people&#39;s serious money?</p><p> DAVIS: Yes, we try not to be in the short-term forecasting game. Forecasting&#39;s really hard, and it&#39;s even harder to the extent you&#39;re doing it for the short-term. And so, when we think about the Vanguard Capital Markets model, which drives a lot of our advice engines and the recommendations that we provide the client, the truly not point forecast in the narrow sense of how people tend to do forecast, it&#39;s really the median results of a large simulation that shows a probabilistic determination of results.</p><p> And it runs a scale. And the median is just basically that midpoint of all those observations. And so we have a distribution around that. And so again, there&#39;s going to be periods of time when you&#39;re in the tail, both positively and negatively. But again, what we try to say to our clients, you have no control about how volatile the market&#39;s going to be. What you can control at the end of the day is how diversified you are, how cognizant you are to the cost that you&#39;re paying for the funds that you&#39;re investing in. And doing that in a highly diversified, low-cost way, we think is going to provide investors the best chance for their investment success long-term versus focusing on daily news announcements, what&#39;s happening.</p><p> Those are the types of things that create trading activity, but don&#39;t tend to add value for long-term investors.</p><p> So you recently came out and criticized some of the market timing that&#39;s been going on. What I found shocking about that was we really have to warn people about the dangers of market timing and overtrading. Isn&#39;t that an issue that the academics have long ago resolved? Yes, but it is, it is, Barry. I mean, the data will show that it is not fruitful. It is not helpful to long-term investors to engage in that type of activity, but we don&#39;t have to look too far past with the meme stocks and things of that nature where for a variety of reasons, things pop on the headline and there&#39;s a lot of momentum and folks get involved and people get caught up and believe it&#39;s easy money and it&#39;s free money.</p><p> And the reality is that&#39;s speculation and not investing. And so speculating is, that&#39;s a very risky strategy. And when we think about investing, that&#39;s not the way you construct an investment portfolio. If you want to do that from a speculative standpoint, that&#39;s fine. Do that with a very small portion of your portfolio, but the majority of it should be investing in long-term strategies that will add value and are enduring.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: My favorite part of TikTok were the TikTok speculative traders. “Hey, investing is easy. Just buy stocks that are going up. And when they stop going up, you sell them. What could be an easier way to support your lifestyle?”</p><p> And as that was happening in real time during 2020, I&#39;m sure you felt the same thing I felt like I&#39;ve seen this movie, I know exactly how this is going to end.</p><p> DAVIS: That&#39;s exactly right, Barry. I mean, I&#39;ve been in this industry long enough. I started my career in finance in 1998 and very familiar with the dot-com era and what happened there. And it was very, very reminiscent of that period of time where during that period, anything with a dot com behind it, ran to the moon, and you couldn&#39;t go wrong. Well, that works until it doesn&#39;t.</p><p> And then one day you realize that these companies actually, they have to be real companies that make money, produce earnings, and are viable businesses. And in a speculative fever, people lose sight that having cash flow, having earnings matters in the long run, and sometimes people have to learn a hard, hard lesson that, again, that&#39;s not investing, and that&#39;s really speculative.</p><p> And it&#39;s a lesson to learn earlier on in your career when you don&#39;t have a lot of money versus later on in your career where you start to accumulate some assets. You definitely want to be more of an investor versus a speculator.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right, make your mistakes early. You know, there&#39;s a chapter in, I want to say it&#39;s Adam Smith&#39;s “The Money Game” from the 1960s, where he talks about a fund manager running a bunch of young run-and-gun managers. “Why do you have these young kids working for you?” “Oh, because they&#39;ll buy all the stuff that I won&#39;t buy and we&#39;ll make money in it. And when it blows up, I&#39;ll sell early and fire them all and go on to the next group.” I was reminded of that last time.</p><p> But it seems shocking, I guess like the market timing argument. We&#39;re still in a debate between meme stock pickers and indexers. It&#39;s fascinating that every new generation has to learn the hard lessons over and over again.</p><p> DAVIS: Yes, I mean, you just have to look at history, but some people have to learn the hard way using real money to do that. But eventually, most people find religion and start thinking about, “Hey, how do I actually construct a portfolio that&#39;s durable, that will provide the type of economic return that&#39;s required to meet their retirement needs, college saving needs, or buying that new house, or whatever the case may be.”</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Right. So let&#39;s talk about some adult decision-making around a durable portfolio. Internally, we&#39;ve been having discussions about extending duration. If you tightened up duration in &#39;21 or even &#39;22, you did better than the index. At what point do you say, “Hey, I&#39;m not getting paid to take risk short-term because of the possibility of those rates dropping, whether it&#39;s &#39;24 or &#39;25.”</p><p> Where do you start thinking about going back out on the duration curve for fixed income?</p><p> DAVIS: I think you have to get to a place where you feel like the Fed is done and inflation is starting to be — you&#39;re convinced that inflation is under control and path towards the Fed&#39;s 2% target. So we think there&#39;s still some ways for that to go. And again, if you go back to what I was saying earlier about R-star and the neutral Fed funds rate, if we believe that&#39;s 3.5% with a normal shape yield curve of 4.5%, we&#39;re not far from that, but it&#39;s also, that&#39;s far from neutral, right?</p><p> If we think 4.5% is fair value, we&#39;re not at fair value yet. So that means it also means that, hey, it&#39;s not cheap. So you don&#39;t want to dive in with both feet. When you&#39;re approaching fair value, you want things to actually be cheap before you do that. So the risk is that rates back up more. And so I think you still want to be somewhat conservative when it comes to duration positioning in a portfolio.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So I always have a question about that 2% inflation target. Not to be flippant, but it seems like a made up number. I hunted for some academic research that said, here&#39;s why. And I came up with something, the former Fed vice chair wrote a paper that said, oh, it&#39;s a thing from New Zealand in 1980s.</p><p> It&#39;s kind of a made up round number and everybody adopted it. Can it be that simple? We&#39;re using a Fed inflation target that&#39;s just a made up number?</p><p> DAVIS: Well, that&#39;s what the market is gravitating towards. That is what the Fed is operating off of. And until they decide to communicate a different message, that&#39;s what the market is going to continue to follow. And their behavior says that, hey, they want to see inflation coming down. It&#39;s also difficult to be changing the strategy when you&#39;re falling behind your current strategy. Because if you say, “Hey, I&#39;m going from a 2% target to 3%, well, you&#39;re at 3% because you couldn&#39;t hit 2%. Well, is 3% the right number?”</p><p> And so…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Well, if you&#39;re going to make up a number, make up one you can reach as opposed to one you can&#39;t.</p><p> DAVIS: But we have to be realistic too, right, Barry? I mean, the reality is for 10 years, we couldn&#39;t hit 2% inflation. We were on the other side.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: We were on the downside.</p><p> DAVIS: We were underneath that 2%. They were working really hard to try to get to 2% and they couldn&#39;t achieve it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: So in an era of low monetary policy and almost non-existent fiscal stimulus, upside target of 2% doesn&#39;t seem to make a lot of sense. Fast forward to the 2020s, now we&#39;re in an era of massive fiscal stimulus, not nearly as much monetary stimulus. Does it make sense to have the same target when you&#39;re coming from 5% above it as opposed to 0% under it?</p><p> DAVIS: Well, the thing is, it&#39;s supposed to be a long-term target and it&#39;s supposed to be an average target over time. So, I haven&#39;t heard anything that would say that they&#39;re in the process of deciding to switch it to a higher number. I think that&#39;s something that&#39;d be debated once you get back to close to your target. And that gives you greater credibility over time.</p><p> What you don&#39;t want to do is you don&#39;t want to change, you don&#39;t want to change the mile post while the car is still in motion and you&#39;re running the race. You want to basically say, “Hey, we&#39;re anchored to this.我们相信这一点。 And ultimately we think this is going to allow us to pursue a level of economic growth that continues to give us full employment, moderate price increases.”</p><p> Again, it&#39;s debatable whether or not 2% is the right number or 3%. All I would say is that it took us a long time to get north of 2%. We finally got it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: It took $6 trillion in fiscal stimulus, but that raises the question, “Hey, you know, when it gets icy out, you got to slow down.”</p><p> DAVIS: You do have to slow down, but the reality is that stimulus is starting to wear off. Those savings are starting to be consumed. You&#39;re starting to see the Fed reduce its balance sheet slowly, but it&#39;s starting to happen. And you&#39;ve seen the Federal Reserve clearly raise interest rates dramatically, 525 basis points in 15 months. They&#39;re definitely trying to slow the economy down.</p><p> And so we&#39;ll have to wait and see if that&#39;s enough. But again, we have to remember, we can&#39;t be blindsided by the fact that inflation has been well above their target because of all this stimulus. This stimulus was slowly ebbing out of the system and we&#39;re gradually going back to, we&#39;re going in the right direction. The question is how long will it take for us to get there?</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. I&#39;m going to throw you a curve ball question which I did not disclose in advance because I wanted to surprise you. You&#39;re born in Germany, raised in a military family, and you speak fluent German with your mom and English with your dad. Tell us a little bit about your experience growing up overseas as a military brat?</p><p> DAVIS: It was a phenomenal, phenomenal experience. I mean, I had the privilege of growing up in a bilingual household. And my maternal grandmother was also home, and she spoke primarily German to me. So what was challenging for me was like, actually, when we moved to the US when I was seven years old, I was always good with math, but my English was below average. And my wife is an English, as she taught English at the college level, she said, “You dummy, English was a second language for you.”</p><p> RITHOLTZ: (LAUGHTER)</p><p> DAVIS: And it really was. I didn&#39;t know it even, I went to a US Department of Defense school in Germany, but my primary language that was spoken by my grandmother, who I spent most of my time with, was German. So, that was interesting.</p><p> And I loved the experience of living over in Germany, and I had the benefit as a kid, during my teenage years, going back to visit family members and friends over the years going back to Germany, which is also a very rewarding and memorable part of my childhood.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting.</p><p> So I only have you for a few more minutes. Let&#39;s jump to our favorite questions that we ask all of our guests that are a little bit revealing of who they are.</p><p> Tell us a little bit about what you&#39;ve been streaming, what&#39;s been keeping you entertained these days.</p><p> DAVIS: So from a streaming standpoint, there was a series, went through the first season that ended, they&#39;re going to start a new one in 2024, it was called “Night Agent.” Which was really interesting. There was an FBI agent who was manning a telephone in the basement of the White House.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I saw the first episode of that.</p><p> DAVIS: Yes, it&#39;s actually a really good series and the good news is it got picked up and I think they&#39;re coming out with new episodes in 2024. But it was a really, really interesting…</p><p> RITHOLTZ: He kind of gets the crap beat out of him in the first episode.</p><p> DAVIS: Yes, yes, yes.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: I saw that, it was very fun.</p><p> DAVIS: It was a really interesting show.这就是其中之一。 And then because of my kids also been, big fans of All American and Bel Air, which are also really cool series that we&#39;ve been watching. So those were a couple.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Tell us a little bit about your early mentors who helped to shape your career.</p><p> DAVIS: I had a number and I&#39;ll go back to the first two I had when I started in this industry. Darrell Thomas was leading investment grade capital market at Citibank. He actually helped me get my internship. I met him at a career fair. He helped me get my first internship on Wall Street with somebody I kept in contact with over the years. And he helped me, you know, him and there was another individual Carmine Urciuoli, who also worked at Citi at the time.</p><p> Those two individuals gave me a lot of perspective when I was thinking about moving from Wall Street to the buy side. And thanks to some of the words of wisdom from Carmine, he said to me when I was thinking about making a change, he said, “If you could join a well-regarded, well-respected asset manager, you&#39;re going to have a much longer and more fruitful career than if you stay on the sell side.”</p><p> And that was advice he gave me back in 1999.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Good advice and good timing.</p><p> DAVIS: I send Carmine chats every once in a few years saying thank you for the advice and I appreciated it.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting.</p><p> DAVIS: And then along the way, Ken Volpert who hired me, huge, huge mentor. He hired me to trade treasuries and mortgages on the team, big mentor, advocate, sponsor and friend, and of course Tim Buckley who gave me the opportunity to go to Australia and then ultimately lead the fixed income group and then put me in the seat that I&#39;m in today. I&#39;ve only had two bosses at Vanguard in 24 years and they&#39;ve both been phenomenal.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Wow, really, really interesting.</p><p> Let&#39;s talk about books. What are some of your favorites and what are you reading right now?</p><p> DAVIS: Right now I&#39;m reading “Plunder” by Brendan Ballou. It talks about the private equity world. I have a daughter who wants to do private equity investing, so I&#39;m doing some due diligence. And the book is actually an interesting read, but it talks a bit about the dark side of private equity versus some of the favorable things that come out of that space as well.</p><p> And then there was another book that I read previously that I thought was really interesting. It&#39;s not market related, but it talks a lot about history in the US, it is called “From Here to Equality” by William Darity and Kirsten Mullen. And it really examines a lot of American history that isn&#39;t covered in school.</p><p> You know, it&#39;s a deep look at some of the, you know, really pivotal points in the nation&#39;s history that, you know, where we had a number of opportunities to create a more and equal and just society where we chose to go left instead of right. And, you know, we&#39;re still dealing with some of those ramifications in today&#39;s modern age. So I thought it was a really, really interesting book about American history.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really interesting. What sort of advice would you give a recent college grad who is interested in a career in either asset management or finance?</p><p> DAVIS: I would say a couple of things. One is be a continual learner. Master your craft. So spend the time and energy and the effort to learn and become an expert. And the key thing is continuous learning. And there&#39;s opportunities to learn from everybody that you interact from and interact with.</p><p> And so the other thing I would say is, for young people, you have to remember a career is a marathon and not a sprint. The problem that people face is that they&#39;re constantly comparing themselves with somebody else who started at the same time or one of their peers who is working at a different firm. And what I always say to the younger joiners to our firm is run your own race. Judge your success by how you&#39;re doing. Are you getting better than where you were a year before? Are you continuing to learn? Are you being developed? And if you focus on yourself about getting better every day, you&#39;re going to have a much more fruitful and long living career than somebody who&#39;s constantly comparing themselves to somebody else.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really good advice.</p><p> And our final question, what do you know about the world of investing today you wish you knew 30 or so years ago when you were really first getting started?</p><p> DAVIS: I would say the power of compounding is such a beautiful thing. I just, I wish I would have learned that lesson earlier on. And you know, what we were speaking about before, the idea of investing versus speculating.</p><p> As a youngster, it&#39;s always interesting to, you think about an industry or a company and you&#39;re like, oh, it&#39;d be a great investment, but what you&#39;re doing is speculating and you should be investing and let that investment compound over 30, 40, 50 years, and you can see that even small amounts of money will grow into a rather large sum if you do it on a consistent basis.</p><p> So I wish I would&#39;ve learned those lessons earlier and earlier in my lifetime.</p><p> RITHOLTZ: Really great stuff.</p><p> We have been speaking with Greg Davis. He is the Chief Investment Officer at the Vanguard Group.</p><p> If you enjoy this conversation, please check out any of the 500 previous interviews we&#39;ve done over the past eight years. You can find those at iTunes, Spotify, YouTube, wherever you find your favorite podcasts. Sign up for my daily reading list at ritholtz.com. Follow me on Twitter @barry_ritholtz until I get back my hacked Twitter account @ritholtz. Follow all of the Bloomberg family of podcasts on Twitter @podcast.</p><p> I would be remiss if I did not thank the crack team who helps put these conversations together each week. Paris Wald is my producer. Atika Valbrun is my project manager. Justin Milner is my audio engineer. Sean Russo is my researcher. I&#39;m Barry Ritholtz. You&#39;ve been listening to Masters in Business on Bloomberg Radio.</p><p>结尾</p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;">~~~ </p><p></p><p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></p><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/transcript-greg-davis/">Transcript: Greg Davis, CIO Vanguard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 Tuesday AM Reads</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-tuesday-am-reads-440/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 10:30:20 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318842 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p> My Two-for-Tuesday morning train WFH reads: • Stock Pickers Never Had a Chance Against Hard Math of the Market: In years like this one, when just a few big companies outperform, it&#39;s hard to assemble a winning portfolio. (Businessweek) but see With cash earning 5%, why risk money on the stock market? Savings rates have…</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-tuesday-am-reads-440/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-tuesday-am-reads-440/">10 Tuesday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> My Two-for-Tuesday morning<del>火车</del>WFH 内容如下：</p><blockquote><p> • <strong>Stock Pickers Never Had a Chance Against Hard Math of the Market</strong> : In years like this one, when just a few big companies outperform, it&#39;s hard to assemble a winning portfolio. ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-25/even-best-stock-pickers-face-an-uphill-battle-beating-the-market" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Businessweek</a> ) <em>but see</em> <strong>With cash earning 5%, why risk money on the stock market?</strong> Savings rates have rocketed and UK savers can earn over 5% on deposits. So doesn&#39;t it make sense to cut risk and stick to the safety of cash? ( <a href="https://www.schroders.com/en-gb/uk/intermediary/insights/with-cash-earning-5-why-risk-money-on-the-stock-market-/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Schroders</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The Exact Age When You Make Your Best Financial Decisions</strong> There&#39;s a magic number for when your expertise and cognitive powers align. （ <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.wsj.com/personal-finance/the-exact-age-when-you-make-your-best-financial-decisions-2a8163bb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> • <strong>Why Are Mortgage Rates So High?</strong> With the 10 year at 4.2% and inflation at 3.2%, mortgage rates should be lower…right? Mortgage rates typically trade a spread to the 10 year Treasury yield. If we were at 1990s spread levels we would be looking at mortgage rates of 5.7%. Even if we were at the average for the 2020s so far they would be at a more reasonable 6.4%. So why are spreads so high right now? ( <a href="https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/08/why-are-mortgage-rates-so-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A Wealth of Common Sense</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>The Great and Awful Thing About These Interest Rates</strong> : The era of low interest rates is over. In the blink of an eye, the Fed went from punishing savers to punishing borrowers. If you&#39;re depending on income to fund your retirement, 5% rates are a blessing.但如果你需要信贷，当前的利率就是一个诅咒。 （ <a href="https://theirrelevantinvestor.com/2023/08/23/the-great-and-awful-thing-about-these-interest-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">无关投资者</a>）</p><p> • <strong>How To Be Lucky: What we get wrong about getting what we want</strong> : There are two contrasting ways of pursuing wealth, power and success. The approach that works the best is also the one most people ignore. ( <a href="https://sapientcapital.com/insights/how-to-be-lucky/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sapient Capital</a> )</p><p> • <strong>If the US economy is doing well, why do so many Americans say it&#39;s terrible?</strong> The leading economic indicators show the US economy is performing well, but most Americans still believe economic conditions are extremely poor — as if the country was mired in a deep recession. What explains this discrepancy? (<a href="https://popular.info/p/if-the-us-economy-is-doing-well-why" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Popular Information</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>Is Partisanship Driving Consumer Sentiment?</strong> Does it make sense that current sentiment readings are worse than: 1. 1980-82 Double Dip Recession 2. 1987 Crash 3. 1990 Recession 4. 9/11 Terrorist Attacks 5. 2000-2003 Dotcom implosion 6. 2007-09 Great Financial Crisis 7. 2020 Pandemic Panic ?!? ( <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2022/08/partisan-sentiment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Big Picture</a> )</p><p> • <strong>The Last Lyme Shot Failed. Can a New One Succeed?</strong> There&#39;s been explosive growth in the number of cases of the disease since Lymerix was pulled from the market more than two decades ago. How much enthusiasm will there be for its replacement? ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-08-24/dogs-have-a-lyme-disease-vaccine-now-pfizer-is-making-one-for-people" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Businessweek</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Businesses Want Remote Work, Just Not as Much</strong> : The enormous increase in remote work that occurred during the pandemic was a response to a temporary public health crisis.现在疫情已经过去，远程工作的持续程度到底有多少，企业可以接受多少？ ( <a href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2023/08/businesses-want-remote-work-just-not-as-much/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Liberty Street Economics</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>Office Tenants Are Renewing Leases—but for Far Less Space</strong> : A record 217 million square feet of sublease space is also weighing down office values. （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/real-estate/commercial/office-tenants-are-renewing-leasesbut-for-far-less-space-b27d5b7e" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> • <strong>The diaries of Amy Winehouse</strong> : &#39;I&#39;m the nutter of the class – loud and mouthing off!&#39; Using family photographs, journals, letters and handwritten lyrics, a new book sheds fresh light on the great singer&#39;s life – while hinting at the tragedy to come. We publish exclusive images from the often heartbreaking work ( <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2023/aug/28/diaries-amy-winehouse-tragedy" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Guardian</a> )</p><p> • <strong>What Your Insurer Is Trying to Tell You About Climate Change</strong> : Insurers are trying to send a message. The government is trying to suppress it. ( <a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2023/08/home-insurance-costs-wildfires-floods-weather/675141/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Atlantic</a> ) <em>see also</em> <strong>Rising Insurance Costs Start to Hit Home Sales</strong> : Vulnerable areas on coasts are first to feel impact of higher premiums ( <a href="https://www.wsj.com/real-estate/rising-insurance-costs-start-to-hit-home-sales-d8787f0f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> )</p><p> • <strong>Michael Jordan Is the Richest Basketball Player Ever With $3.5 Billion Fortune</strong> : The NBA legend&#39;s wildly successful deal with Nike forms the cornerstone of his wealth, which has grown through endorsements and the sale of his majority stake in the Charlotte Hornets. （ <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-24/michael-jordan-s-hornets-sale-sets-3-5b-net-worth-richest-nba-player-status" target="_blank" rel="noopener">彭博社</a>）</p></blockquote><p>请务必查看本周末我们对先锋集团首席投资官格雷格·戴维斯的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士</a><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" data-web-url="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2">采访</a>。戴维斯负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。他还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。</p><p></p><p> <strong>Commercial Real Estate Is in Trouble, but Not for the Reason You Think</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-317341" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector.png" alt="" width="600" height="343" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector.png 1688w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector-300x172.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector-1024x586.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector-768x440.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector-250x143.png 250w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bysector-1536x879.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><br /> Source: <a href="https://www.morningstar.com/alternative-investments/commercial-real-estate-is-trouble-not-reason-you-think" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morningstar</a></p><p></p><p></p><div><div class="pf-content"><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p></p></div></div><p> The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-tuesday-am-reads-440/">10 Tuesday AM Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a> .</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title>在路上（前往科托克营地）</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/on-the-road-to-camp-kotok/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Macro/Econ]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318986 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>路上的经济 劳动力、消费者、通货膨胀和数据 本月早些时候，我在车里单程花费了两个半小时，还加上在美妙的 Eagle&#39;s Nest 享用了一顿快速（且令人恐惧的）午餐，吃了一份 Lost Roll 和薯条。我一路上愉快的旅伴是 VettaFi + 的戴夫·纳迪格 (Dave Nadig)……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/on-the-road-to-camp-kotok/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p>帖子<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/on-the-road-to-camp-kotok/">《在路上（前往科托克营地）》</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">《大图片》</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>经济之路劳动力、消费者、通货膨胀和数据</strong><br /><iframe loading="lazy" title="YouTube 视频播放器" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Le2G6OWwxe8?si=9jz9jeuoexVLdn_C" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p><p></p><p>本月早些时候，我在车里单程花费了两个半小时，并在美妙的 Eagle&#39;s Nest 餐厅享用了一顿快速（且令人恐惧的）午餐，享用了 Loster Roll 和薯条。一路上我愉快的旅伴是 VettaFi 的戴夫·纳迪格 (Dave Nadig) 和 Newedge Wealth 的卡梅伦·道森 (Cameron Dawson)。</p><p>戴夫拥有整个华尔街最好的头衔：<em>金融未来学家。</em>他的工作就像听起来一样，是一种疯狂的自由式，他可以摸着下巴，深入思考任何与金融相关的事情。每当我对新的金融技术（从 ETF 到加密货币再到人工智能）有疑问时，我的第一个电话就是 Dave。我喜欢认为我是一个早期采用者，但当我到达戴夫时，他已经陷入兔子洞几个月了。</p><p>卡梅伦只是下一个级别。她绝对没有必要在她这么小的年纪就如此聪明和经验丰富。每当她出现在电视上时，只要停下你正在做的事情，听她说话——然后想想她的年龄只有戴夫或我的一半。</p><p>不管怎样，我们聊得很开心，<em>一切都</em>很好。 Dave<del>包括全部 167 分钟</del>将其剪辑为不到半小时，这使得它非常耐听。</p><p>周末和这个团队一起度过了很多有趣的时光，我已经开始期待明年的旅行了。</p><p></p><p>帖子<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/on-the-road-to-camp-kotok/">《在路上（前往科托克营地）》</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">《大图片》</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title>周一上午 10 点阅读</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-monday-am-reads-400/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 10:30:51 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318697 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>我早上上班的火车 WFH 上写着： • 大加密货币背后的“富达黑手党”：共同基金巨头是比特币先驱，为该行业建立了深厚的人才渠道。 （华尔街日报） • 小型多户住宅正在消失。现在，各州正在争先恐后地复兴它们：复式住宅等低密度住房的建设徘徊在历史低点附近，因为……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-monday-am-reads-400/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-monday-am-reads-400/">周一上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>我重返工作岗位的早晨<del>火车</del>WFH 内容如下：</p><blockquote><p> •<strong>大加密货币背后的“富达黑手党”</strong> ：共同基金巨头是比特币先驱，为该行业建立了深厚的人才渠道。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/finance/currencies/the-fidelity-mafia-behind-big-crypto-953ad00e" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>小型多户住宅正在消失。现在，各州正在争先恐后地复兴它们</strong>：随着各州通过分区改革以解决经济适用房危机，复式住宅等低密度住房的建设徘徊在历史低点附近。 ( <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-08-26/duplex-triplex-construction-nears-record-lows-despite-us-housing-crisis" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CityLab</a> )<em>另请参阅</em><strong>太阳能热潮蔓延到 Timberlands 和自存储屋顶</strong>：去年的气候法案为大业主引发了太阳能热潮。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/business/energy-oil/solar-boom-spreads-to-timberlands-and-self-storage-rooftops-e6cd7b23" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>制造业繁荣的隐性成本</strong>：为应对中国崛起和气候变化的双重威胁，美国已开始实施冷战以来最激进的产业政策。这一重心加速了制造业的复苏并刺激了投资，从而重塑了经济的关键部分。但这是有代价的，随着国家生产更多商品和减少进口，通胀可能会继续走高。 （《 <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/us-manufacturing-boom-hidden-costs-cf2b900b" target="_blank" rel="noopener">巴伦周刊</a>》）</p><p> •<strong>美国的500 万美元退休金是这样的</strong>：退休人员公开谈论他们的财务生活以及他们如何花费时间和金钱。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/heres-what-a-5-million-retirement-looks-like-in-america-1abc76d9" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>首次乘坐：Damon Motors HyperSport</strong> 。这款 200 马力的猛兽是 Damon 为大众带来安全电动摩托车的目标。 《连线》对 HyperSport 进行了测试。 （ <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/first-ride-damon-motors-hypersport/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">有线</a>）</p><p> •<strong>消费者的支出与 2019 年一样</strong>：随着支出的增加以及客户更看重体验而非商品，疫情引发的消费狂潮逐渐消退。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/business/retail/consumers-are-spending-like-its-2019-dff7b8bc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>皮肤塑造健康的奇怪方式</strong>：风化或不健康的皮肤正在成为几乎所有与年龄相关的疾病（从帕金森病到2 型糖尿病）的主要危险因素。 （ <a href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20230823-the-curious-ways-your-skin-shapes-your-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener">英国广播公司</a>）</p><p> •<strong>报告发现，封锁和口罩“明确”地减少了新冠病毒的传播</strong>：皇家学会的审查着眼于多种措施组合应用时的非药物干预措施。 （ <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2023/aug/24/lockdowns-face-masks-unequivocally-cut-spread-covid-study-finds" target="_blank" rel="noopener">《卫报</a>》）</p><p> •<strong>是什么让Vivek 如此烦人？一项调查</strong>。盖伊竞选总统组 哈佛大学毕业生维韦克·拉马斯瓦米 (Vivek Ramaswamy) 对于任何去过那里的人来说都是一个很难辨认的人物，即使我们从来不认识他本人。 （<a href="https://www.joshbarro.com/p/section-guy-runs-for-president" target="_blank" rel="noopener">非常严肃</a>）</p><p> •<strong>一场胜利，17,000 场失败——华盛顿将军的生活</strong>。与环球旅行者队所受到的普遍赞美相反，那些穿着将军队臭名昭著的不成功绿色球衣的人在失败期间、失败后、失败后遭到嘘声、嘲笑和扣篮。 （<a href="https://www.bbc.com/sport/basketball/66525597" target="_blank" rel="noopener">英国广播公司</a>）</p></blockquote><p>请务必查看本周末我们对先锋集团首席投资官格雷格·戴维斯的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士</a><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" data-web-url="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2">采访</a>。戴维斯负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。他还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。</p><p></p><p><strong>如果 10 年期国债利率上升（64% 的情况下），同期股市平均下跌 0.15%。如果 10 年期利率在 30 天内下降，标准普尔 500 指数同期上涨 3.1%</strong><br /> <a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/stocksandrates.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-318768" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/stocksandrates.jpeg" alt="" width="700" height="438" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/stocksandrates.jpeg 872w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/stocksandrates-300x188.jpeg 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/stocksandrates-768x481.jpeg 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/stocksandrates-250x157.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></a><br />资料来源： <a href="https://theirrelevantinvestor.com/2023/08/22/rates-rule-everything-around-me/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">无关投资者</a></p><p></p><p><a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-monday-am-reads-400/">周一上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 周日读物</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/sunday-reads-338/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:30:59 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318268 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>把目光移开！我周日早上会审视无能、腐败和政策失败： • 我的大部分 Instagram 广告都是关于毒品、被盗信用卡、被黑帐户、假币和武器：这些广告是了解明目张胆的非法地下经济的窗口，而 Meta 则不然只是未能节制，但正在积极从中获利……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/sunday-reads-338/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/sunday-reads-338/">《10 周日读物》</a>一文首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>把目光移开！我<em>周日上午</em>关注的是无能、腐败和政策失败：</p><blockquote><p> •<strong>我的大部分 Instagram 广告都是关于毒品、被盗信用卡、被黑账户、假币和武器</strong>：这些广告是了解明目张胆的非法地下经济的窗口，Meta 不仅没有对其进行监管，反而积极从中获利并注入资金进入用户的提要。 （ <a href="https://www.404media.co/instagram-ads-illegal-content-drugs-guns-hackers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">404媒体</a>）</p><p> •<strong>一个闪亮的计划正在耗尽退休账户的资金。右翼媒体促成了这一点</strong>。我们多年来一直关注这些公司。我们的研究得出的结果令人震惊。 ( <a href="https://www.msnbc.com/opinion/msnbc-opinion/fox-news-newsmax-enable-gold-coin-ira-retirement-scheme-rcna100685" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MSNBC</a> )<em>另请参阅</em><strong>右翼新闻如何推动“黄金 IRA”行业</strong>：尽管监管机构指责一些公司欺骗老年客户，但金币广告已成为福克斯新闻、Newsmax 和其他保守派媒体的中流砥柱。 （ <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/07/25/gold-ira-conservative-media/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华盛顿邮报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>黑客可以用 15 美元对美国几乎任何人进行人肉搜索的秘密武器</strong>：大多数美国人别无选择，只能向征信机构提供个人信息。黑客已经找到了进入该数据供应链的方法，并在抢劫、袭击和射击目标的暴力犯罪分子使用的群聊中宣传访问权限。 （ <a href="https://www.404media.co/the-secret-weapon-hackers-can-use-to-dox-nearly-anyone-in-america-for-15-tlo-usinfosearch-transunion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">404媒体</a>）</p><p> • <strong>Deepfake 冒名顶替者诈骗正在引发新一波欺诈</strong>：人工智能可以推动网络盗窃经济。世界银行业正在努力控制风险。 （ <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-21/money-scams-deepfakes-ai-will-drive-10-trillion-in-financial-fraud-and-crime" target="_blank" rel="noopener">彭博社</a>）</p><p> •<strong>美国拥有世界上最安全的航空旅行，但在汽车安全方面却很糟糕</strong>：美国可以从我们超安全的航空旅行系统中学到有关道路安全的三件事。 （ <a href="https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/2023/8/25/23844717/america-safe-air-travel-car-safety-accidents" target="_blank" rel="noopener">沃克斯</a>）</p><p> •<strong>航空公司的千钧一发事件比以前已知的要频繁得多</strong>：这些事件（在美国联邦航空局初步安全报告中强调但未公开披露）是仅上个月就涉及商业航空公司的至少 46 起千钧一发的事件之一。 《纽约时报》的一项调查发现，这些事件是美国天空和跑道上令人震惊的安全失误和险情的一部分。尽管美国十多年来没有发生过重大飞机失事事件，但潜在危险事件的发生频率比几乎任何人意识到的都要频繁——这是许多内部人士所描述的压力日益增大的安全网的一个迹象。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/08/21/business/airline-safety-close-calls.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>全球多个地区的高温记录正在被打破</strong>：随着美国中部的无情热浪达到顶峰，欧洲、亚洲和南美洲的部分地区也正在沸腾。 （ <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/weather/2023/08/24/global-heat-records-europe-asia-south-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华盛顿邮报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>城里没有妇产科医生了：爱达荷州打击堕胎后发生了什么</strong>在爱达荷州桑德波因特，产科病房关闭了。几个月之内，农村社区妇女的医疗服务就被掏空了。 （ <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/aug/22/abortion-idaho-women-rights-healthcare" target="_blank" rel="noopener">《卫报</a>》）</p><p> •。<strong>一个挑战联邦法律的右翼治安官团体正在全国范围内获得认可</strong>：“利夫是宪法治安官与和平官员协会的顾问委员会成员，该协会由前亚利桑那州治安官理查德·麦克于 2011 年创立。该组织被称为 CSPOA，其教导称，当选的治安官必须拒绝执行任何他们认为违宪或“不公正”的法律，以“保护其公民免受失控的联邦政府的越权”。 （ <a href="https://apnews.com/article/constitutional-sheriffs-5568cd0b6b27680a28de8a098ed14210" target="_blank" rel="noopener">美联社</a>）<em>另请参阅</em><strong>让我们的孩子变得更笨的右翼运动</strong>：出于可能不太难理解的原因，共和党人和保守派似乎打算将他们的 K-12 学校、学院和大学变成种植园，以养育孩子。一群无知、不思考的学生。唐纳德·特朗普 (Donald Trump) 在 2016 年初选期间提出了这一原则，当时他宣称：“我爱受教育程度较低的人。” （ <a href="https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2023-08-22/the-right-wing-campaign-to-make-our-kids-dumber-is-moving-ahead-at-full-speed" target="_blank" rel="noopener">洛杉矶时报</a>）</p><p> • <strong>Fyre Festival 续集回归——据称</strong>：最新一次被愚弄两次的机会刚刚售完。 （ <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/travel/2023/08/22/fyre-festival-2-billy-mcfarland/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华盛顿邮报</a>）</p></blockquote><p>请务必查看本周末我们对先锋集团首席投资官格雷格·戴维斯的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士</a><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" data-web-url="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2">采访</a>。戴维斯负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。他还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。</p><p></p><p><strong>美国人对制度的信心下降</strong><br /><a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/decliningconfidence.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-316697" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/decliningconfidence.png" alt="" width="700" height="495" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/decliningconfidence.png 1320w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/decliningconfidence-300x212.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/decliningconfidence-1024x725.png 1024w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/decliningconfidence-768x543.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/decliningconfidence-250x177.png 250w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></a><br />资料来源： <a href="https://www.brookings.edu/articles/how-americans-confidence-in-technology-firms-has-dropped-evidence-from-the-second-wave-of-the-american-institutional-confidence-poll/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">布鲁金斯学会</a></p><p></p><p></p><p><a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p> ~~~</p><p>要了解每天如何组合这些阅读内容， <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2016/08/assemble-daily-reads-3-ez-steps/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>请参阅此</em></a>。</p><p></p><p> <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/sunday-reads-338/">《10 周日读物》</a>一文首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> MiB：Greg Davis，CIO Vanguard</title><link/> https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/mib-greg-davis/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sat, 26 Aug 2023 14:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Index/ETFs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Investing]]></category><category><![CDATA[MiB]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318919 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>本周，我们采访了先锋集团的首席投资官格雷格·戴维斯。他负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。戴维斯还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。他拥有超过25...</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/mib-greg-davis/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/mib-greg-davis/">MiB 职位：Greg Davis，CIO Vanguard</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/greg-davis-on-vanguard-portfolio-management/id730188152?i=1000625684276" height="175" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"></iframe></p><p></p><p>本周，我们采访了<a href="https://investor.vanguard.com/corporate-portal" target="_blank" rel="noopener">先锋集团的</a>首席投资官<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/gregory-davis" target="_blank" rel="noopener">格雷格·戴维斯</a>。他负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。戴维斯还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。他拥有超过25年的投资管理经验。</p><p>我们讨论了他的职业生涯如何发生一系列意想不到的转变，包括从研究保险开始，担任先锋澳大利亚和亚太地区的首席信息官/董事，然后接管全球所有固定收益业务。蒂姆·巴克利 (Tim Buckley) 于 2018 年成为先锋集团 (Vanguard Group) 首席执行官，最终将戴维斯提升为首席信息官 (CIO)。</p><p>戴维斯解释了为什么先锋集团不玩预测游戏，并指出“预测游戏真的很难，而且短期内更难。”相反，先锋资本市场模型“运行大型模拟，显示一组概率结果，因此我们倾向于瞄准中位数，即这些观察结果分布的中点。”至于尾部，无论是积极的还是消极的，这种情况偶尔都会发生，但大多数时候你都处于分布的中间。</p><p>戴维斯补充道，“<em>您可以控制多元化和成本，而不是预测您无法控制的事件</em>。”</p><p>他最喜欢的书清单 <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/mib-greg-davis/#more-318919" target="_blank" rel="noopener">在这里</a>；周二我们的谈话记录<a href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/transcript-greg-davis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">可以在这里找到</a>。</p><p>您可以在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/greg-davis-on-vanguard-portfolio-management/id730188152?i=1000625684276" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Podcasts</a> 、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/2bo96GOdIjlVEodoCm7zvn" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> 、 <a href="https://www.stitcher.com/show/masters-in-business" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stitcher</a> 、 <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvZTczYzk5OGUtNmU2MC00MzJmLTg2MTAtYWUyMTAxNDBjNWIxLzRlNGNkOTEwLTQwYTEtNDYxOS1hNWYzLWFlMmIwMDEyZmZmZi81ODczYTNjYi0yOThmLTQwYmMtYjcxZi1hZTJiMDAxMzAwMGQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> 、 <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLe4PRejZgr0PzN7r8NikAnOqP70DHhoJ0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a>和<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2023-08-25/greg-davis-on-vanguard-portfolio-management-podcast" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a>上流式传输和下载我们的完整对话，包括任何播客附加内容。您可以<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://plnk.to/MIB?to=page">在此处找到</a>您最喜欢的播客主机上的所有早期播客。</p><p>请务必在下周与 Jonathan Miller 一起学习我们的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士课程</a>，他是<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.millersamuel.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Miller Samuel</a>的首席执行官，他于 1986 年与他人共同创立了一家房地产评估和咨询公司。他是纽约州和康涅狄格州的国家认证房地产评估师，从事房地产评估工作。作为专家证人出庭作证，并拥有房地产顾问 (CRE) 和认证搬迁专业人士 (CRP) 称号。他的每周电子邮件<a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://www.millersamuel.com/email-lists/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">“住房笔记”</a>在评估和房地产经纪行业都被广泛阅读。米勒·塞缪尔 (Miller Samuel) 的研究和数据分析推动了许多全国房地产经纪出版物和战略计划的发展。</p><p></p><p><span id="more-318919"></span></p><p></p><h3>格雷格·戴维斯当前的阅读内容</h3><p><strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1541702107/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">掠夺：私募股权公司掠夺美国的计划</a></strong>作者：Brendan Ballou<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1541702107/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-318826" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/plunder.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="387" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/plunder.jpg 322w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/plunder-194x300.jpg 194w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/plunder-250x387.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p> <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1469671204/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">从这里到平等，第二版：二十一世纪对美国黑人的赔偿 作者</a></strong>：William A. Darity Jr. 和 A. Kirsten Mullen<br /> <a href="https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1469671204/thebigpictu09-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-318827" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/heretoequality.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="377" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/heretoequality.jpg 331w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/heretoequality-199x300.jpg 199w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/heretoequality-250x377.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a></p><p></p><p> <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/mib-greg-davis/">MiB 职位：Greg Davis，CIO Vanguard</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 周末读物</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/weekend-reads-578/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Sat, 26 Aug 2023 10:30:35 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318261 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>周末来了！给自己倒一杯咖啡，在外面找个座位，准备好迎接我们更长的周末吧： • 可能解开艺术王朝的继承案：一位寡妇对法国威尔登斯坦家族的法律诉讼如何威胁到他们传奇的收藏——并揭示了……的弱点。</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/weekend-reads-578/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/weekend-reads-578/">《10 周末读物》</a>一文首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>周末来了！给自己倒一杯咖啡，在外面找个座位，准备好阅读我们的长篇周末读物：</p><blockquote><p> •<strong>可能瓦解艺术王朝的继承案</strong>：一位寡妇与法国威尔登斯坦家族的法律斗争如何威胁到他们传奇的收藏，并揭示了全球艺术市场的弱点。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/08/23/magazine/wildensteins-inheritance-case-art.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>伊隆·马斯克的影子规则</strong>：美国政府如何开始依赖这位科技亿万富翁，并且现在正在努力控制他。（ <a href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2023/08/28/elon-musks-shadow-rule" target="_blank" rel="noopener">《纽约客》</a> ）<em>另请参阅</em><strong>马斯克、蒂尔、扎克伯格和安德森——四位亿万富翁科技寡头——是如何发展的创建另一种专制现实</strong>：在他的新书《现实的终结》的摘录中，作者对人工智能和超人类主义的诅咒发出了警告，并提出了反对超级智能的道德案例。 （《 <a href="https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2023/08/musk-thiel-zuckerberg-andreessen-alternate-autocratic-reality" target="_blank" rel="noopener">名利场</a>》）</p><p> •<strong>奇怪的满足感：我们收集无用物品的动机是什么？</strong>粉丝们表示，他们收藏的马克杯、卡骆驰鞋和毛绒玩具“让人抓痒”。你可以称其为“万色资本主义”。 （ <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2023/aug/24/oddly-satisfying-whats-behind-our-drive-to-collect-useless-items" target="_blank" rel="noopener">《卫报</a>》）</p><p> •<strong>中国希望斐济成为太平洋地区的模板。它的计划适得其反</strong>。斐济人对中国越来越反感，这是北京在试图建立其全球影响力时如何过度扩张的一个例子。 （ <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/interactive/2023/china-fiji-police-mou-pacific-islands/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华盛顿邮报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>法学硕士研究中的开放挑战</strong>：我一生中从未见过如此多的聪明人为同一个目标而努力：让法学硕士变得更好。在与工业界和学术界的许多人交谈后，我注意到出现的 10 个主要研究方向。前两个方向，幻觉和情境学习，可能是今天讨论最多的。我最兴奋的是数字 3（多模态）、5（新架构）和 6（GPU 替代方案）。 （ <a href="https://huyenchip.com/2023/08/16/llm-research-open-challenges.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chip Huyen</a> ）。</p><p> •<strong>这座现代主义住宅背后的故事与其建筑一样曲折</strong>：位于纽约州东汉普顿的 Blue Dream 俯瞰大海，在早期建筑中已有先例，例如位于约翰·肯尼迪机场的埃罗·沙里宁 (Eero Saarinen) 的环球航空飞行中心 (TWA Flight Center)，但它其独特之处在于其底层随着沙丘的起伏而起伏。汉普顿的住宅经历了 22 次建筑师访谈、废弃的设计计划和过早的死亡。 （ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/real-estate/luxury-homes/blue-dream-house-in-the-hamptons-cf01128c" target="_blank" rel="noopener">华尔街日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>我们并不空虚：原子空虚的概念是科普中最常犯的错误之一。分子中充满了物质</strong>：通过仔细解释描述分子、原子和亚原子粒子物理学的量子理论，可以消除对空原子概念的误解。根据量子理论，物质的组成部分——如电子、原子核及其形成的分子——可以被描述为波或粒子。 （ <a href="https://aeon.co/essays/why-the-empty-atom-picture-misunderstands-quantum-theory" target="_blank" rel="noopener">万古</a>）<em>另请参阅</em><strong>即使在大爆炸之前，我们的宇宙也不是空的</strong>：我们今天测量的所有物质和辐射都起源于很久以前的热大爆炸。宇宙从来都不是空的，甚至在此之前也不是。 （ <a href="https://aeon.co/essays/why-the-empty-atom-picture-misunderstands-quantum-theory" target="_blank" rel="noopener">永旺</a>）</p><p> •<strong>多重危机</strong>：我们需要用这个词来描述生态、政治和经济冲突之间前所未有的融合吗？ （ <a href="https://aeon.co/essays/the-case-for-polycrisis-as-a-keyword-of-our-interconnected-times" target="_blank" rel="noopener">永旺</a>）</p><p> •<strong>莱莉·克亚芙谈《长大普雷斯利》、《失去丽莎·玛丽》和《继承格雷斯兰》</strong> ：黛西·琼斯和六人组将她推向明星地位，尽管她经历了悲剧、新的母亲身份以及与普里西拉的法律斗争。 （《 <a href="https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2023/08/riley-keough-on-growing-up-presley-cover-story" target="_blank" rel="noopener">名利场</a>》）</p><p> •<strong>围绕体育集换卡展开的价值数十亿美元的恶性战争</strong>：随着健康的爱好卷入反垄断战争，业内领先的两家公司正在相互指责反竞争行为。 （ <a href="https://newrepublic.com/article/175107/sports-cards-antitrust-panini-fanatics" target="_blank" rel="noopener">新共和</a>）</p></blockquote><p>请务必查看本周末我们对先锋集团首席投资官格雷格·戴维斯的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士</a><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" data-web-url="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2">采访</a>。戴维斯负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。他还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。</p><p></p><p><strong>租赁市场放缓最终反映在通胀数据上</strong><br /><a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/rentalmarket.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-317406" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/rentalmarket.png" alt="" width="600" height="437" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/rentalmarket.png 980w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/rentalmarket-300x218.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/rentalmarket-768x559.png 768w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/rentalmarket-250x182.png 250w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><br />资料来源： <a href="https://www.apartmentlist.com/research/national-rent-data" target="_blank" rel="noopener">公寓清单</a></p><p></p><p></p><div><div class="pf-content"><p><a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p> ~~~</p><p>要了解每天如何组合这些阅读内容， <a href="https://ritholtz.com/2016/08/assemble-daily-reads-3-ez-steps/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>请参阅此</em></a>。</p></div></div><p></p><p> <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/weekend-reads-578/">《10 周末读物》</a>一文首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title>投资者从小型恐慌中吸取的教训</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/lessons-for-investors-from-mini-panics/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Fri, 25 Aug 2023 13:50:38 +0000</pubDate> <category><![CDATA[Podcast]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318882 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>我为我的朋友乔·菲茨杰拉德（我们在 2000 年代末一起工作）准备的第一个流行病后演示文稿是一个新的幻灯片，标题为：超高净值投资者犯下的最大错误。在接下来的一年里，我更新并完善了该套牌，添加了更多示例和具体建议。以下是我对演讲内容的讨论……</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/lessons-for-investors-from-mini-panics/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/lessons-for-investors-from-mini-panics/">《投资者从小型恐慌中吸取的教训》一文</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">《大局》</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>我为我的朋友乔·菲茨杰拉德（我们在 2000 年代末一起工作）准备的第一个流行病后演示文稿是一个新的幻灯片，标题为：<a href="https://ritholtz.com/2022/11/uhnw-mistakes-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">超高净值投资者犯下的最大错误</a>。</p><p>在接下来的一年里，我更新并完善了该套牌，添加了更多示例和具体建议。以下是我对<a href="https://conferences.moneyshow.com/moneyshow-orlando//workshop/3c4f54d5c475435f8f0d55b22ecbb3af/how-to-avoid-financial-disasters-a-guide-for-the-ultra-high-net-worth-investor//" target="_blank" rel="noopener">10 月 30 日奥兰多 MoneyShow 上</a>的演示内容的讨论。</p><p>如果您十月底在奥兰多附近，那就过来吧。</p><p></p><p><strong>中国、点击诱饵和市场危机：投资者应该了解的行为经济学知识</strong><br /><iframe loading="lazy" title="YouTube 视频播放器" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ViSJTbDNHy8?si=K4tOqXZf1R3eB3rb" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p><p></p><p>以下是 Moneyshow 的描述：</p><blockquote><p> “Barry Ritholtz 是 Ritholtz 财富管理公司的创始人兼首席信息官。他也是一位长期的市场分析师、评论员和行为经济学原理（适用于投资）方面的专家。在这次富有洞察力的采访中，巴里讨论了过多关注“头发着火”头条新闻的危险，例如最近有关中国信贷问题、利率上升和经济衰退风险的头条新闻。他指出，“点击诱饵的东西很有趣，但这不是我们管理资产的方式，也不是个人应该如何管理自己的资产。”巴里还讨论了人类如何做出快速判断、使用模式识别以及对某些刺激反应过度，因为这有助于我们作为一个物种的进化和生存。问题？ “在大草原上行之有效的事情，在资本市场上却行不通。”然后我们的谈话转向巴里对美联储政策的展望，为什么他认为高于 2% 的通胀目标是有意义的，60/40 投资组合去年为何没有真正“失败”，以及投资者现在可以采取哪些措施来适应更高利率、更刺激的市场环境。”</p></blockquote><p></p><p></p><p> <a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/lessons-for-investors-from-mini-panics/">《投资者从小型恐慌中吸取的教训》一文</a>首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">《大局》</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item><item><title> 10 周五上午阅读</title><link/>https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-friday-am-reads-420/<dc:creator><![CDATA[Barry Ritholtz]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Fri, 25 Aug 2023 10:30:50 +0000</pubDate><category><![CDATA[Links]]></category><guid ispermalink="false"> https://ritholtz.com/?p=318696 </guid><description><![CDATA[<p>我在周末早上的火车 WFH 上写道： • 这些利率的伟大和可怕的事情：如果您依靠收入来为您的退休生活提供资金，那么 5% 的利率是一种祝福。但如果你需要信贷，当前的利率就是一个诅咒。 （无关投资者） • 在热门就业市场中，最低工资成为......</p><p><a class="button" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-friday-am-reads-420/">阅读更多<i class="icon ion-arrow-right-c"></i></a></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-friday-am-reads-420/">周五上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>; </description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>我的周末早晨<del>火车</del>WFH 内容如下：</p><blockquote><p> •<strong>这些利率的伟大和可怕的事情</strong>：如果您依靠收入来维持退休生活，那么 5% 的利率是一件幸事。但如果你需要信贷，当前的利率就是一个诅咒。 （ <a href="https://theirrelevantinvestor.com/2023/08/23/the-great-and-awful-thing-about-these-interest-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">无关投资者</a>）</p><p> •<strong>在热门的就业市场中，最低工资成为事后的想法</strong>：7.25 美元的联邦工资下限变得越来越无关紧要，即使大多数青少年的收入也是这个水平的两倍。但当经济降温时会发生什么？ （《 <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/08/23/business/economy/minimum-wage.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报》</a> ）<em>另请参阅</em><strong>企业希望远程工作，但不那么强烈</strong>。大流行期间远程工作的大量增加是对暂时的公共卫生危机的回应。现在疫情已经过去，远程工作的持续程度到底有多少，企业可以接受多少？我们八月份的区域商业调查结果。 （ <a href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2023/08/businesses-want-remote-work-just-not-as-much/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">自由街经济</a>）</p><p> •<strong>生成式人工智能应用程序：投资框架</strong>：从应用程序到基础设施和工具，生成式人工智能风险投资领域迅速发展。在这篇文章中，我们重点关注应用程序层——我们历来最活跃的领域。生成式人工智能似乎不可避免地会嵌入到我们接触的大多数应用程序中，从而实现全新的体验和大规模自动化。不太确定的是这种变化的速度及其二阶效应。修改 ChatGPT 是一回事；修改 ChatGPT 是一回事。采用一种在结构上重塑人类长期任务的产品则完全是另一回事。 （ <a href="https://www.mosaicventures.com/patterns/generative-ai-applications-an-investing-framework" target="_blank" rel="noopener">马赛克</a>）</p><p> •<strong>贸易组织警告称，华为正在建立芯片秘密网络</strong>：据报道，科技巨头已获得拜登政府监控的 300 亿美元国家支持，并准备采取行动。 （ <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-23/huawei-building-secret-chip-plants-in-china-to-bypass-us-sanctions-group-warns" target="_blank" rel="noopener">彭博社</a>）</p><p> •<strong>石雕机器人告诉我们关于未来建筑的哪些信息</strong>：建筑师正在利用旧材料探索新的创作，使用机器人雕刻石头？ （ <a href="https://slate.com/business/2023/08/traditional-architecture-brick-stone-timber-modernism.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">板岩</a>）</p><p> •<strong>海底是否是绿色能源转型的关键？</strong>海底丰富的矿物质对于可再生能源基础设施至关重要。但开采它们会造成什么危害呢？ （ <a href="https://www.noemamag.com/does-the-ocean-floor-hold-the-key-to-the-green-energy-transition" target="_blank" rel="noopener">诺埃玛</a>）</p><p> •<strong>冥想不仅仅是缓解压力或启蒙</strong>：探索更广泛的冥想不再是修道院的专利。新的冥想科学才刚刚开始。 （ <a href="https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/23836358/meditation-mindfulness-enlightenment-science-contemplative-buddhism-spirituality" target="_blank" rel="noopener">沃克斯</a>）</p><p> •<strong>高温、洪水、火灾：2023 年夏季是新常态吗？</strong>气候科学家表示，地球变暖正在加剧极端天气事件（ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/us-news/climate-environment/heat-floods-fire-was-summer-2023-the-new-normal-2df9bc21" target="_blank" rel="noopener">《华尔街日报</a>》），<em>另请参阅</em><strong>《极热 47 天，你开始注意到事物》</strong> ：你会在持续高温下注意到事物。集中注意力是一种生存策略。我喜爱并居住了四分之一个世纪的红色岩石景观是一片炎热的地形。炎热的天气和燃烧世界的重量压在我们的肩上。 （ <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/08/18/opinion/heat-wave-utah-climate-change.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">纽约时报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>磁带头</strong>：Mellotron，一种录制样本的电子键盘，预示着数字时代的到来，它在“永远的草莓地”中的使用改变了流行音乐的历史。 （ <a href="https://daily.jstor.org/tape-heads/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JSTOR日报</a>）</p><p> •<strong>安迪·罗迪克的公开赛时代</strong>：赢得美国公开赛二十年后，安迪·罗迪克扔掉了他的奖杯，继续了他的生活。但在一次罕见的采访中，最后一位赢得大满贯的美国男子回顾了这一历史性的胜利，以及随之而来的所有压力、名誉、失败、爱情和损失。 （ <a href="https://www.gq.com/story/andy-roddick-us-open" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GQ</a> ）</p></blockquote><p>请务必查看本周末我们对先锋集团首席投资官格雷格·戴维斯的<a href="https://ritholtz.com/category/podcast/mib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-web-url="http://www.bloombergview.com/topics/masters-in-business">商业硕士</a><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2" data-web-url="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/masters-in-business/id730188152?mt=2">采访</a>。戴维斯负责监督先锋固定收益、股票指数和量化股票集团管理的约 7 万亿美元资产。他还担任美国财政部财政部借款咨询委员会成员。</p><p></p><p><strong>新冠疫情不再阻碍劳动力供应</strong><br /><a href="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/laborsupply.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-318324" src="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/laborsupply.png" alt="" width="700" height="400" srcset="https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/laborsupply.png 688w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/laborsupply-300x171.png 300w, https://ritholtz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/laborsupply-250x143.png 250w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></a><br />资料来源：Torsten Slok、Apollo Global</p><p></p><p> <a class="gtrackexternal" href="https://mailchi.mp/005fb77d75b9/ritholtzreads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><em>在此注册我们的只读邮件列表</em></a>。</p><p></p><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com/2023/08/10-friday-am-reads-420/">周五上午 10 点阅读的</a>帖子首先出现在<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ritholtz.com">The Big Picture</a>上。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>